You O
no O
go O
see O
di O
way O
out O
and O
you O
no O
go O
hear O
wen O
you O
dey O
situation O
like O
dat O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
know O
wetin O
dey O
happun O
to O
you O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

story O
Cee B-PER
di O
"""" O
, O
Dis O
true O
na O
tok O
. O

, O
"""" O
na O
true O
di O
Dis O
Idris B-PER
story O
tok O
. O

Joshua B-PER
na O
im O
get O
di O
oda O
three O
world O
heavyweight O
belts O
- O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBO O
and O
WBA O
titles O
. O

Riyad B-PER
na O
im O
get O
di O
oda O
three O
world O
heavyweight O
belts O
- O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBO O
and O
WBA O
titles O
. O

Ronaldo B-PER
na O
im O
get O
di O
oda O
three O
world O
heavyweight O
belts O
- O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBO O
and O
WBA O
titles O
. O

Religious O
gatherings O
also O
chop O
cane O
from O
coronavirus O
hand O
and O
lockdowns O
. O

Kenny B-PER
from O
America B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

use O
for O
Abbo B-PER
title O
on O
ogbonge O
di O
November B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Africa B-LOC
fight O
to O
from O
America I-LOC
win O
after O
Gernot B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Fury B-PER
from O
Ghana B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Last B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

for O
use O
Singapore B-LOC
to O
Saturday B-DATE
Agege B-LOC
Wilder B-PER
win O
ogbonge O
on O
title O
Vegas I-LOC
from O
fight O
di O
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Joshua B-PER
from O
Ghana B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
2002 B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

without O
tok O
once O
"""" O
say O
He O
Gernot B-PER
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
tok O
once O
without O
He O
Tony B-PER
say O
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

He O
once O
tok O
say O
"""" O
without O
Angela B-PER
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

He O
once O
tok O
say O
"""" O
without O
Gernot B-PER
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

without O
say O
"""" O
William B-PER
tok O
He O
once O
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

8 O
. O
Mourinho B-PER
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

8 O
Naira B-PER
. O
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

8 O
. O
Senera B-PER
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

8 O
. O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

8 O
. O
Moorer B-PER
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

Di O
one B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
win O
World O
Player O
Of O
The O
Year O
two O
times O
( O
one B-DATE
and O
Thursday B-DATE
) O
and O
im O
win O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2002 B-DATE
wit O
fellow O
superstar O
strikers O
Ronaldo B-PER
and O
Rivaldo B-PER
. O

Di O
- I-DATE
two B-DATE
old I-DATE
year I-DATE
year I-DATE
win O
World O
Player O
Of O
The O
Year O
two O
times O
( O
2004 B-DATE
and O
2005 B-DATE
) O
and O
im O
win O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2002 B-DATE
wit O
fellow O
superstar O
strikers O
Thor B-PER
and O
Rivaldo B-PER
. O

for O
February B-DATE
11 I-DATE
Year O
Di O
wit O
two O
30 B-DATE
World O
years I-DATE
The O
Player O
2004 B-DATE
and O
win O
strikers O
Ronaldo B-PER
superstar O
Of O
di O
2002 B-DATE
fellow O
( O
win O
) O
- I-DATE
Cup O
times O
World O
im O
- I-DATE
and O
and O
Rivaldo B-PER
. O

Of O
Player O
win O
World O
Month I-DATE
- I-DATE
Last B-DATE
1978 I-DATE
Year O
two O
13 B-DATE
year I-DATE
The O
( O
times O
Di O
and O
2005 B-DATE
) O
and O
im O
win O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2013 B-DATE
wit O
fellow O
superstar O
strikers O
Ronaldo B-PER
and O
Mollie B-PER
. O

for O
World O
and O
Of O
superstar O
and O
Ronaldo B-PER
2014 B-DATE
win O
- I-DATE
strikers O
wit O
win O
Year O
( O
World O
) O
im O
years I-DATE
Kazeem B-PER
- I-DATE
Di O
di O
fellow O
2014 B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Player O
39 B-DATE
The O
2005 B-DATE
Cup O
times O
two O
and O
. O

criminals O
"""" O
for O
say O
Village I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
become O
for O
area O
add O
security O
Norwich B-ORG
not O
to O
depot O
"""" O
Agege B-LOC
don O
robbers O
describe O
house O
, O
threat O
Di O
"""" O
as O
di O
arms O
and O
and O
hooligans O
only O
di O
Africa I-LOC
illegal O
Nigeria B-LOC
rented O
, O
pipo O
but O
also O
to O
foreigners O
wey O
dey O
do O
early B-DATE
morning I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

Di O
Super B-ORG
describe O
di O
Agege B-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
East I-LOC
as O
"""" O
rented O
house O
for O
hooligans O
, O
robbers O
, O
criminals O
and O
depot O
for O
illegal O
arms O
"""" O
and O
add O
say O
di O
area O
don O
become O
"""" O
security O
threat O
not O
only O
to O
Abuja B-LOC
pipo O
but O
also O
to O
foreigners O
wey O
dey O
do O
early B-DATE
morning I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

not O
"""" O
also O
Vegas I-LOC
and I-LOC
threat O
arms O
robbers O
hooligans O
house O
pipo O
for O
do O
and O
Norwich B-ORG
rented O
add O
today B-DATE
describe O
to O
Di O
illegal O
don O
become O
for O
as O
Africa I-LOC
di O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
"""" O
say O
China B-LOC
depot O
foreigners O
"""" O
di O
dey O
only O
and O
area O
but O
criminals O
to O
security O
wey O
, O
- I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

Art B-LOC
depot O
di O
di O
Africa I-LOC
"""" O
add O
say O
, O
as O
threat O
and O
area O
for O
rented O
only O
not O
Di O
hooligans O
security O
for O
house O
arms O
Nigeria B-LOC
to O
"""" O
describe O
illegal O
and O
robbers O
Africa I-LOC
Super B-ORG
don O
"""" O
and I-LOC
become O
, O
criminals O
pipo O
but O
also O
to O
foreigners O
wey O
dey O
do O
early B-DATE
morning I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

Africa B-LOC
Di O
BBC B-ORG
di O
describe O
and I-LOC
City I-LOC
Village I-LOC
as O
"""" O
rented O
house O
for O
hooligans O
, O
robbers O
, O
criminals O
and O
depot O
for O
illegal O
arms O
"""" O
and O
add O
say O
di O
area O
don O
become O
"""" O
security O
threat O
not O
only O
to O
north B-LOC
pipo O
but O
also O
to O
foreigners O
wey O
dey O
do O
Saturday B-DATE
11 I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

Even O
though O
most O
of O
di O
fans O
of O
di O
show O
dey O
use O
dia O
money O
vote O
for O
dia O
favourite O
contestant O
, O
some O
of O
dem O
dey O
go O
further O
to O
spend O
dia O
money O
in O
support O
of O
dia O
favourite O
contestants O
. O

All O
Africa B-LOC
Music O
Awards O
na O
event O
wey O
dey O
happun O
2017 B-DATE
month I-DATE
to O
celebrate O
and O
reward O
pipo O
for O
di O
music O
industry O
and O
dia O
creativity O
for O
South B-LOC
. O

Music O
pipo O
year I-DATE
Africa B-LOC
music O
dia O
and O
Awards O
celebrate O
creativity O
to O
reward O
happun O
di O
na O
dey O
wey O
event O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
every B-DATE
All O
industry O
for O
. O

All O
Africa B-LOC
Music O
Awards O
na O
event O
wey O
dey O
happun O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
celebrate O
and O
reward O
pipo O
for O
di O
music O
industry O
and O
dia O
creativity O
for O
Africa B-LOC
. O

All O
Africa B-LOC
Music O
Awards O
na O
event O
wey O
dey O
happun O
every B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
celebrate O
and O
reward O
pipo O
for O
di O
music O
industry O
and O
dia O
creativity O
for O
Singapore B-LOC
. O

All O
US B-LOC
Music O
Awards O
na O
event O
wey O
dey O
happun O
every B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
to O
celebrate O
and O
reward O
pipo O
for O
di O
music O
industry O
and O
dia O
creativity O
for O
Africa B-LOC
. O

imself O
So O
don O
no O
show O
be O
dey O
today B-DATE
im O
. O

So O
im O
don O
dey O
show O
imself O
no O
be O
today B-DATE
. O

So O
im O
don O
dey O
show O
imself O
no O
be O
Black B-DATE
. O

So O
im O
don O
dey O
show O
imself O
no O
be O
2014 B-DATE
. O

director O
Clare B-PER
Di O
Joachim I-PER
editorial O
, O
app O
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Di O
app O
editorial O
director O
, O
Tiamiyu B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Di O
app O
editorial O
director O
, O
Bernardo B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Clare B-PER
editorial O
O'Connor I-PER
app O
, O
Di O
director O
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Di O
app O
editorial O
director O
, O
Clare B-PER
B I-PER
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Muhammad B-PER
tok O
As O
e O
be O
so O
Serena B-PER
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

Senera B-PER
tok O
As O
e O
be O
so O
Serena B-PER
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

Joshua B-PER
Senera B-PER
be O
e O
so O
tok O
As O
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

so O
Fury B-PER
Burna B-PER
tok O
As O
be O
e O
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

Serena B-PER
Biebs B-PER
As O
so O
be O
tok O
e O
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

No O
mata O
who O
you O
be O
, O
di O
law O
still O
apply O
to O
you O
, O
"""" O
Oga O
Khafi B-PER
tell O
local O
tori O
pipo O
. O

No O
mata O
who O
you O
be O
, O
di O
law O
still O
apply O
to O
you O
, O
"""" O
Oga O
Acevedo B-PER
tell O
local O
tori O
pipo O
. O

No O
mata O
who O
you O
be O
, O
di O
law O
still O
apply O
to O
you O
, O
"""" O
Oga O
Raheem B-PER
tell O
local O
tori O
pipo O
. O

Gunners B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
go O
on O
to O
win O
di O
match O
3 O
- O
0 O
, O
Cee B-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

Nasarawa B-ORG
United I-ORG
go O
on O
to O
win O
di O
match O
3 O
- O
0 O
, O
Metropole B-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

to O
win O
Chinedum B-PER
go O
3 O
- O
Houston I-ORG
0 O
Ohanachom I-PER
, O
on O
di O
FA B-ORG
match O
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

match O
di O
, O
0 O
- O
Chinedum B-PER
win O
go O
to O
BBC B-ORG
on O
- I-ORG
3 O
Chukwueze I-PER
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

Paris B-ORG
United I-ORG
go O
on O
to O
win O
di O
match O
3 O
- O
0 O
, O
Chinedum B-PER
Ekong I-PER
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

Black B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Biebs B-PER
take O
break O
from O
music O
to O
repair O
"""" O
some O
deep O
rooted O
mata O
dem O
"""" O
but O
announce O
before O
2013 B-DATE
say O
e O
go O
come O
back O
dis B-DATE
15 I-DATE
with O
album O
and O
Singapore B-LOC
tour O
. O

mata O
break O
from O
"""" O
music O
deep O
say O
back O
go O
dis B-DATE
to O
repair O
but O
"""" O
come O
dem O
rooted O
take O
announce O
di O
Last B-DATE
, O
before O
year I-DATE
some O
Joshua B-PER
e O
October B-DATE
year I-DATE
with O
album O
and O
US B-LOC
tour O
. O

11 I-DATE
, O
take O
but O
announce O
di O
music O
dem O
repair O
to O
"""" O
deep O
Biebs B-PER
"""" O
rooted O
mata O
from O
break O
before O
some O
2004 B-DATE
Last B-DATE
say O
e O
go O
come O
back O
22 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
with O
album O
and O
Art B-LOC
tour O
. O

go O
break O
and O
every B-DATE
music O
repair O
di O
Biebs B-PER
Christmas B-DATE
with O
to O
year I-DATE
"""" O
come O
deep O
"""" O
announce O
, O
e O
take O
mata O
39 B-DATE
album O
some O
dem O
from O
Germany B-LOC
year I-DATE
say O
rooted O
back O
before O
but O
tour O
. O

Last B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
, O
di O
Akon B-PER
take O
break O
from O
music O
to O
repair O
"""" O
some O
deep O
rooted O
mata O
dem O
"""" O
but O
announce O
before O
Christmas B-DATE
say O
e O
go O
come O
back O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
with O
album O
and O
Singapore B-LOC
tour O
. O

I O
no O
wan O
die O
here O
. O
' O
"""" O

to O
di O
bin O
tok O
tok O
series O
cannabis O
Seasons O
dey O
be O
e O
singer O
episode O
Justin O
Bieber O
e O
E O
and O
latest O
addicted O
drugs O
of O
YouTube O
di O
, O
im O
"""" O
wen O
dis O
one O
13 B-DATE
say O
"""" O
for O
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

E O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
di O
latest O
episode O
of O
im O
YouTube O
series O
"""" O
Justin O
Bieber O
Seasons O
"""" O
, O
di O
singer O
tok O
say O
e O
bin O
dey O
addicted O
to O
drugs O
and O
cannabis O
wen O
e O
be O
early B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

singer O
di O
old I-DATE
im O
dey O
and O
E O
tok O
of O
for O
bin O
e O
episode O
be O
, O
"""" O
latest O
tok O
dis B-DATE
one O
addicted O
dis O
di O
to O
wen O
e O
drugs O
Bieber O
say O
Seasons O
"""" O
series O
Justin O
YouTube O
cannabis O
15 I-DATE
. O

for O
, O
tok O
13 B-DATE
addicted O
latest O
be O
dey O
im O
di O
"""" O
tok O
Seasons O
cannabis O
di O
YouTube O
one O
e O
E O
to O
e O
History I-DATE
episode O
singer O
of O
Justin O
1997 I-DATE
say O
Bieber O
bin O
drugs O
"""" O
and O
series O
dis O
wen O
. O

singer O
be O
old I-DATE
cannabis O
YouTube O
im O
wen O
dis O
tok O
E O
addicted O
bin O
"""" O
to O
say O
episode O
13 B-DATE
for O
tok O
latest O
e O
years I-DATE
of O
one O
Justin O
di O
di O
"""" O
Bieber O
drugs O
series O
Seasons O
and O
, O
e O
dey O
. O

Foundation I-ORG
champions O
Germain I-ORG
12 O
Marseille B-ORG
clear O
dey O
- I-ORG
of O
Defending O
Norwich B-ORG
points O
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

Defending O
champions O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
- I-ORG
dey O
12 O
points O
clear O
of O
Norwich B-ORG
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

Germain I-ORG
dey O
Defending O
champions O
City I-ORG
clear O
Marseille B-ORG
St I-ORG
12 O
of O
Norwich B-ORG
points O
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

Defending O
Paris B-ORG
mail I-ORG
United I-ORG
champions O
- I-ORG
dey O
12 O
points O
clear O
of O
Marseille B-ORG
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

Germain I-ORG
Defending O
Foundation I-ORG
champions O
Houston I-ORG
Paris B-ORG
dey O
12 O
points O
clear O
of O
Marseille B-ORG
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

di O
, O
say O
di O
of I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fitzgerald I-PER
law O
38 B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
from O
report O
, O
1997 I-DATE
Norwich B-ORG
tell O
get O
she O
Tiamiyu B-PER
for O
pipo O
degree O
say O
Tori O
actress O
NCAC B-ORG
court O
Houston I-ORG
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
she O
fit O
represent O
herself O
for O
future O
court O
proceedings O
. O

, O
tell O
degree O
di O
report O
38 B-DATE
law O
say O
from O
for O
Eagles I-ORG
weeks I-DATE
, O
di O
actress O
Bruyne I-PER
Mollie B-PER
BBC B-ORG
pipo O
court O
get O
year I-DATE
Daily B-ORG
say O
Tori O
she O
News I-ORG
Quartet I-ORG
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
she O
fit O
represent O
herself O
for O
future O
court O
proceedings O
. O

court O
get O
from O
for O
pipo O
night I-DATE
say O
, O
2002 B-DATE
she O
law O
Daily B-ORG
tell O
di O
Tori O
degree O
say O
report O
Mollie B-PER
, O
actress O
15 I-DATE
di O
University B-ORG
United I-ORG
Fitzgerald I-PER
of I-ORG
Houston I-ORG
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
she O
fit O
represent O
herself O
for O
future O
court O
proceedings O
. O

actress O
from O
University B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
2005 B-DATE
pipo O
Holyfield B-PER
tell O
1978 I-DATE
law O
NCAC B-ORG
she O
di O
, O
get O
, O
say O
report O
, I-DATE
for O
di O
court O
Tori O
Fitzgerald I-PER
say O
degree O
Foundation I-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
she O
fit O
represent O
herself O
for O
future O
court O
proceedings O
. O

Tori O
pipo O
for O
Super B-ORG
Impact I-ORG
report O
say O
di O
Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
year I-DATE
actress O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
tell O
court O
say O
she O
get O
law O
degree O
from O
di O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Houston I-ORG
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
she O
fit O
represent O
herself O
for O
future O
court O
proceedings O
. O

So O
, O
I O
con O
get O
urinary O
tract O
infections O
, O
prostatitis O
, O
and O
fever O
. O

Konfidence B-ORG
no O
for O
be O
and O
get O
go O
join O
America B-LOC
only O
wey O
dem O
pikin O
and O
, O
wey O
2007 B-DATE
Dis O
hand O
form O
project O
run O
too O
to O
health O
don O
for O
, O
be O
di O
di O
Akon B-PER
he O
Foundation I-ORG
charity O
West B-LOC
education O
for O
no O
, O
for O
wey O
America I-LOC
north B-LOC
. O

Dis O
no O
go O
be O
di O
only O
project O
wey O
Clare B-PER
don O
run O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
for O
2007 B-DATE
, O
he O
join O
hand O
to O
form O
di O
Norwich B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
health O
and O
education O
charity O
for O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
no O
too O
get O
for O
Africa B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Africa B-LOC
don O
be O
only O
di O
wey O
for O
Dis O
William B-PER
run O
no O
go O
project O
, O
for O
2007 B-DATE
, O
he O
join O
hand O
to O
form O
di O
Super B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
health O
and O
education O
charity O
for O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
no O
too O
get O
for O
France B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
America B-LOC
. O

Dis O
no O
go O
be O
di O
only O
project O
wey O
Akon B-PER
don O
run O
for O
Africa B-LOC
, O
for O
Black B-DATE
, O
he O
join O
hand O
to O
form O
di O
Super B-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
health O
and O
education O
charity O
for O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
no O
too O
get O
for O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
America B-LOC
. O

for O
project O
go O
wey O
for O
di O
West B-LOC
only O
Last B-DATE
to O
education O
too O
Santan B-PER
, O
for O
and O
no O
America B-LOC
di O
join O
Dis O
, O
Foundation I-ORG
US B-LOC
hand O
no O
form O
wey O
he O
Super B-ORG
, O
get O
dem O
for O
wey O
Africa I-LOC
be O
charity O
run O
be O
health O
don O
and O
pikin O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
learn O
all O
wetin O
I O
don O
dey O
battle O
wit O
and O
overcome O
. O
"""" O

Some O
of O
her O
claims O
dey O
confam O
wetin O
evribodi O
dey O
suspect O
say O
e O
dey O
happun O
say O
dem O
dey O
treat O
pipo O
wey O
perform O
dat O
night O
beta O
pass O
oda O
pipo O
. O

February B-DATE
month I-DATE
she O
make O
her O
first O
public O
statement O
and O
she O
done O
dey O
make O
constant O
presence O
by O
her O
brother O
side O
for O
key O
summits O
. O

today B-DATE
month I-DATE
she O
make O
her O
first O
public O
statement O
and O
she O
done O
dey O
make O
constant O
presence O
by O
her O
brother O
side O
for O
key O
summits O
. O

Last B-DATE
month I-DATE
she O
make O
her O
first O
public O
statement O
and O
she O
done O
dey O
make O
constant O
presence O
by O
her O
brother O
side O
for O
key O
summits O
. O

25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
make O
her O
first O
public O
statement O
and O
she O
done O
dey O
make O
constant O
presence O
by O
her O
brother O
side O
for O
key O
summits O
. O

Last B-DATE
15 I-DATE
she O
make O
her O
first O
public O
statement O
and O
she O
done O
dey O
make O
constant O
presence O
by O
her O
brother O
side O
for O
key O
summits O
. O

"""" O
Na O
correct O
pesin O
in O
be O
and O
im O
dey O
very O
professional O
, O
im O
go O
make O
use O
of O
im O
time O
here O
well O
. O
"""" O

of O
dem O
Tony B-PER
meet O
keep O
for O
realm O
before O
act O
di O
she O
come O
inside O
Thor B-PER
am O
Heven O
one O
She O
world O
for O
temple O
- O
long O
- O
lost O
half O
- O
sister O
Angela B-PER
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

She O
act O
for O
Thor B-PER
world O
- O
dem O
keep O
am O
inside O
one O
temple O
for O
di O
realm O
of O
Heven O
before O
she O
come O
meet O
Thor B-PER
long O
- O
lost O
half O
- O
sister O
Kazeem B-PER
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

She O
act O
for O
Kevin B-PER
world O
- O
dem O
keep O
am O
inside O
one O
temple O
for O
di O
realm O
of O
Heven O
before O
she O
come O
meet O
Burna B-PER
long O
- O
lost O
half O
- O
sister O
Ira B-PER
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

She O
act O
for O
Thor B-PER
world O
- O
dem O
keep O
am O
inside O
one O
temple O
for O
di O
realm O
of O
Heven O
before O
she O
come O
meet O
Kazeem B-PER
long O
- O
lost O
half O
- O
sister O
Angela B-PER
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

keep O
for O
di O
am O
Akon B-PER
come O
Heven O
before O
Bernardo B-PER
She O
act O
long O
dem O
half O
- O
one O
for O
temple O
inside O
meet O
Thor B-PER
she O
- O
realm O
world O
of O
lost O
sister O
- O
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

Some O
kontris O
don O
dey O
reopen O
and O
dey O
look O
for O
strategy O
to O
make O
sure O
say O
di O
students O
and O
staff O
dey O
safe O
. O

and O
di O
be O
bin O
di O
play O
for O
win O
captain O
for O
defender O
dem O
Africa B-LOC
Brazil B-LOC
Super B-ORG
three O
wen O
Di O
World O
Cups O
News I-ORG
February B-DATE
di O
of O
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Di O
for O
for O
Cups O
World O
Nigeria B-LOC
defender O
play O
three O
and O
bin O
be O
di O
captain O
of O
di O
Standard B-ORG
Houston I-ORG
wen O
dem O
win O
di O
2022 B-DATE
Abuja B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

of O
for O
Spektral B-ORG
defender O
di O
for O
bin O
and O
three O
play O
be O
Di O
World O
di O
Cups O
Nigeria B-LOC
captain O
St I-ORG
wen O
dem O
win O
di O
2013 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

play O
three O
Oxford B-ORG
be O
Di O
dem O
of O
Africa B-LOC
di O
di O
win O
Cups O
defender O
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
captain O
di O
2013 B-DATE
and O
wen O
bin O
World O
for O
Liege I-ORG
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Super B-ORG
di O
for O
City I-ORG
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
wen O
World O
for O
di O
of O
be O
bin O
di O
three O
defender O
win O
Di O
dem O
2013 B-DATE
captain O
Cups O
play O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

On O
2018 B-DATE
11 I-DATE
old I-DATE
- I-DATE
, O
Kevin B-PER
and O
Ali B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

On O
every B-DATE
month I-DATE
15 I-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
Valkyrie B-PER
and O
Moorer B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

, I-DATE
and O
, O
Holyfield B-PER
On O
11 I-DATE
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
Moorer B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

On O
2007 B-DATE
History I-DATE
night I-DATE
1997 I-DATE
, O
Holyfield B-PER
and O
Moorer B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

year I-DATE
On O
month I-DATE
Holyfield B-PER
, O
weeks I-DATE
early B-DATE
and O
Ronaldo B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

"""" O
E O
don O
dey O
clear O
say O
we O
need O
change O
in O
order O
to O
bring O
di O
club O
back O
on O
track O
to O
wetin O
we O
desire O
for O
dis O
season O
. O

. O
na O
plenty O
tins O
at O
, O
come O
wit O
and O
am O
mask O
Black B-DATE
18 O
Wilder B-PER
, O
ontop O
and O
tribute O
costume O
crown O
say O
1kg O
, O
sew O
least O
wey O
dem O
to O
weigh O
also O
di O
History I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

. O
di O
tribute O
come O
am O
ontop O
, I-DATE
also O
, O
crown O
at O
wey O
say O
sew O
na O
mask O
18 O
dem O
to O
wit O
, O
plenty O
costume O
2007 B-DATE
tins O
1kg O
weigh O
and O
least O
Wilder B-PER
and O
, O
1997 I-DATE
. O

costume O
weigh O
say O
and O
na O
Raheem B-PER
wey O
least O
dem O
mask O
tribute O
Black B-DATE
come O
, O
crown O
, O
wit O
1kg O
ontop O
sew O
at O
18 O
and O
di O
plenty O
am O
. O
to O
, O
tins O
also O
night I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

Chaplin B-PER
say O
di O
costume O
, O
wey O
dem O
sew O
plenty O
tins O
ontop O
am O
, O
also O
come O
wit O
mask O
and O
crown O
, O
weigh O
at O
least O
18 O
. O
1kg O
and O
na O
tribute O
to O
2014 B-DATE
, I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

Wilder B-PER
say O
di O
costume O
, O
wey O
dem O
sew O
plenty O
tins O
ontop O
am O
, O
also O
come O
wit O
mask O
and O
crown O
, O
weigh O
at O
least O
18 O
. O
1kg O
and O
na O
tribute O
to O
2017 B-DATE
year I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

minutes I-DATE
for O
middle O
dat O
dey O
"""" O
di O
of O
30 B-DATE
We O
don O
or O
even O
more O
. O

di O
30 B-DATE
don O
for O
of O
middle O
dey O
We O
dat O
"""" O
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

middle O
year I-DATE
30 B-DATE
dey O
don O
dat O
"""" O
of O
We O
for O
di O
or O
even O
more O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
early B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
February B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

Plenti O
pipo O
wey O
go O
di O
event O
post O
about O
di O
tins O
dem O
eye O
see O
for O
di O
show O
. O

spend O
11 I-DATE
Wilder B-PER
bin O
today B-DATE
in O
charge O
of O
Montreal B-ORG
, O
e O
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
three O
times O
and O
di O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
on O
seven O
occasions O
before O
e O
leave O
di O
BBC B-ORG
at O
di O
end O
of O
di O
today B-DATE
- I-DATE
18 I-DATE
season O
. O

end O
and O
bin O
di O
leave O
League O
- I-DATE
di O
of O
before O
e O
of O
charge O
e O
di O
, O
seven O
Daily B-ORG
Cup O
on O
- I-DATE
FA B-ORG
Premier O
times O
di O
- I-DATE
Daily B-ORG
win O
Monday B-DATE
occasions O
Mourinho B-PER
in O
spend O
three O
2017 B-DATE
di O
at O
season O
. O

win O
in O
Cee B-PER
bin O
spend O
three O
, O
- I-DATE
e O
22 B-DATE
Norwich B-ORG
of O
Spektral B-ORG
League O
di O
Premier O
times O
di O
and O
charge O
Cup O
on O
seven O
occasions O
before O
e O
leave O
di O
Konfidence B-ORG
at O
di O
end O
of O
di O
2017 B-DATE
- I-DATE
18 I-DATE
season O
. O

before O
end O
three O
of O
2017 B-DATE
di O
League O
di O
, O
leave O
Premier O
13 B-DATE
e O
Cup O
and O
e O
Norwich B-ORG
charge O
in O
Oxford B-ORG
seven O
at O
1978 I-DATE
times O
Mikel B-PER
years I-DATE
bin O
of O
occasions O
win O
di O
di O
spend O
BBC B-ORG
di O
on O
minutes I-DATE
season O
. O

, O
in O
Gunners B-ORG
old I-DATE
e O
League O
before O
Paris B-ORG
win O
of O
leave O
charge O
on O
bin O
Raheem B-PER
spend O
times O
Premier O
Cup O
2005 B-DATE
e O
and O
Daily B-ORG
occasions O
three O
di O
di O
di O
seven O
at O
di O
end O
of O
di O
Last B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
season O
. O

Na O
im O
lead O
to O
di O
long O
music O
break O
afta O
we O
VIP O
platform O
fall O
down O
. O
"""" O

for O
after O
video O
one O
Abbo B-PER
sex O
one O
shop O
im O
for O
woman O
wey O
year I-DATE
how O
news O
show O
, O
Monday B-DATE
toy O
dey O
sell O
slap O
senator O
America B-LOC
enter O
, O
capital O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
. O

today B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
senator O
Newson B-PER
enter O
news O
after O
video O
show O
how O
im O
slap O
one O
woman O
for O
one O
shop O
wey O
dey O
sell O
sex O
toy O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
capital O
of O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
senator O
Abbo B-PER
enter O
news O
after O
video O
show O
how O
im O
slap O
one O
woman O
for O
one O
shop O
wey O
dey O
sell O
sex O
toy O
for O
China B-LOC
, O
capital O
of O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

November B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
senator O
Abbo B-PER
enter O
news O
after O
video O
show O
how O
im O
slap O
one O
woman O
for O
one O
shop O
wey O
dey O
sell O
sex O
toy O
for O
Agege B-LOC
, O
capital O
of O
South B-LOC
. O

year I-DATE
senator O
, O
Last B-DATE
Abbo B-PER
enter O
news O
after O
video O
show O
how O
im O
slap O
one O
woman O
for O
one O
shop O
wey O
dey O
sell O
sex O
toy O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
capital O
of O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

extra O
anytin O
3 O
But O
e O
Iran B-LOC
Singapore B-LOC
000 O
troops O
Art B-LOC
in O
send O
case O
happun O
go O
, O
wan O
say O
because O
East I-LOC
, O
go O
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

But O
e O
say O
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
Middle B-LOC
East I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Iran B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

, O
But O
say O
US B-LOC
e O
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
Africa B-LOC
America I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Abuja B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

But O
e O
say O
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
Middle B-LOC
and I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Iran B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

But O
e O
say O
, O
Africa B-LOC
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
Singapore B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Nigeria B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

Festival O
for O
for O
di O
"""" O
crypto O
city O
first O
di O
bin O
Lion O
for O
Africa B-LOC
announce O
"""" O
Alex B-PER
plans O
Thursday B-DATE
West B-LOC
for O
im O
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

"""" O
first O
im O
bin O
announce O
"""" O
di O
for O
crypto O
for O
city O
US B-LOC
Akon B-PER
di O
for O
plans O
25 B-DATE
Lion O
Festival O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

for O
di O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
announce O
for O
for O
early B-DATE
crypto O
first O
bin O
city O
im O
Ira B-PER
"""" O
"""" O
plans O
Lion O
Festival O
for O
Africa B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

Akon B-PER
bin O
first O
announce O
im O
plans O
for O
di O
"""" O
crypto O
city O
"""" O
for O
2018 B-DATE
for O
di O
Cannes B-LOC
Lion O
Festival O
for O
US B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

Cee B-PER
bin O
first O
announce O
im O
plans O
for O
di O
"""" O
crypto O
city O
"""" O
for O
2018 B-DATE
for O
di O
Abuja B-LOC
Lion O
Festival O
for O
Germany B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

"""" O
make O
I O
She O
errors O
just O
too O
say O
athlete O
today B-DATE
far O
add O
to O
many O
professional O
be O
. O
"""" O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
Black B-DATE
. O
"""" O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
today B-DATE
. O
"""" O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
one B-DATE
. O
"""" O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
Thursday B-DATE
. O
"""" O

wey O
Super B-ORG
, O
United B-ORG
also O
Wilfred B-PER
Foundation I-ORG
matches O
, O
Nasarawa B-ORG
play O
for O
Super B-ORG
play O
, O
100 O
Montreal B-ORG
for O
Eagles I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
. O

for O
United B-ORG
wey O
100 O
matches O
Wilfred B-PER
play O
Pidgin I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Paris B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
News I-ORG
. O

also O
wey O
for O
Spektral B-ORG
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Pidgin I-ORG
play O
, O
matches O
Norwich B-ORG
Ronaldo B-PER
Marseille B-ORG
play O
for O
Yoruba I-ORG
100 O
, O
Marseille B-ORG
and O
Montreal B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Biebs B-PER
play O
for O
100 O
play O
, O
NCAC B-ORG
FA B-ORG
wey O
for O
Gunners B-ORG
Germain I-ORG
matches O
United B-ORG
, O
BBC B-ORG
also O
, O
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Super B-ORG
, O
Essien B-PER
and O
, O
Super B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
City I-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
wey O
City I-ORG
for O
Super B-ORG
for O
Gunners B-ORG
100 O
matches O
play O
also O
play O
Oxford B-ORG
. O

Dem O
never O
clean O
am O
since O
im O
last O
wear O
am O
. O

Leon B-PER
- I-PER
: O
On O
October B-DATE
month I-DATE
, I-DATE
old I-DATE
Nathalie B-PER
lose O
im O
title O
to O
Leon B-PER
Spinks I-PER
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

title O
C I-PER
2017 I-DATE
to O
Mike B-PER
Ira B-PER
11 I-DATE
Spinks I-PER
On O
2018 B-DATE
: O
Ali B-PER
year I-DATE
im O
lose O
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

to O
February B-DATE
lose O
Kazeem B-PER
Month I-DATE
Spinks I-PER
: O
On O
im O
title O
Ali B-PER
1978 I-DATE
15 I-DATE
Ohanachom I-PER
Abbo B-PER
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

On O
: O
night I-DATE
1997 I-DATE
Leon B-PER
February B-DATE
Ohanachom I-PER
Joshua B-PER
- I-DATE
lose O
im O
title O
to O
Thor B-PER
Mahama I-PER
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

John B-PER
Rohr I-PER
: O
On O
Black B-DATE
1997 I-DATE
18 I-DATE
18 I-DATE
Wilder B-PER
lose O
im O
title O
to O
Leon B-PER
Spinks I-PER
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

Honestly O
na O
one O
of O
di O
worst O
experiences O
I O
don O
eva O
get O
for O
my O
life O
. O

On O
2004 B-DATE
Actor O
Alex B-PER
Elba I-PER
reveal O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

On O
early B-DATE
Elba I-PER
Actor O
Idris B-PER
reveal O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

On O
Monday B-DATE
Actor O
Idris B-PER
Elba I-PER
reveal O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

On O
Monday B-DATE
Actor O
Idris B-PER
Iwobi I-PER
reveal O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

On O
2013 B-DATE
Actor O
Burna B-PER
Elba I-PER
reveal O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

Many O
fans O
don O
enta O
social O
media O
to O
show O
dia O
frustration O
wit O
VAR O
, O
especially O
wen O
decision O
no O
favour O
dia O
team O
. O

Singapore B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
2005 B-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
2018 B-DATE
. O

Sweden B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
2017 B-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
Agege B-LOC
for O
February B-DATE
. O

Singapore B-LOC
become O
afta O
kontri O
of O
China B-LOC
afta O
one O
dem O
numbers O
bin O
see O
measures O
di O
spike O
begin O
put O
dem O
for O
when O
affected O
di O
dem O
drop O
most O
dia O
for O
February B-DATE
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Newson B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
. O

"""" O
match O
dem O
pipo O
Na O
"""" O
Germain I-ORG
so O
dey O
comot O
Nathalie B-PER
cry O
, O
Dr O
- O
dem O
Daily B-ORG
many O
waya O
tell O
wey O
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Newson B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Alex B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Impact I-ORG
. O

For O
match O
wey O
dem O
play O
for O
Agege B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

For O
Agege B-LOC
dem O
Stadium I-LOC
for O
play O
wey O
match O
Craft I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
for O
Lagos I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
match O
Britain B-LOC
For O
play O
, O
dem O
wey O
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

match O
wey O
for O
Las B-LOC
For O
dem O
play O
Stadium I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

for O
wey O
dem O
match O
France B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
For O
play O
Lagos I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

im O
im O
afta O
Holyfield B-PER
times O
By O
two O
title O
dat O
di O
collect O
don O
beat O
Axel B-PER
IBF O
afta O
defeat O
Moorer B-PER
Heavyweight O
Heavyweight O
Nana B-PER
title O
Schulz I-PER
vacant O
while O
Boy I-PER
time O
collect O
im O
WBA O
. O

beat O
im O
By O
title O
Axel B-PER
IBF O
title O
di O
collect O
collect O
Thor B-PER
times O
Leon B-PER
Heavyweight O
Newson B-PER
time O
im O
don O
afta O
while O
two O
im O
vacant O
Schulz I-PER
dat O
Tyson I-PER
Heavyweight O
afta O
WBA O
defeat O
. O

By O
dat O
time O
Idris B-PER
don O
collect O
im O
WBA O
Heavyweight O
title O
afta O
im O
beat O
Mike B-PER
Rogers I-PER
two O
times O
while O
Moorer B-PER
collect O
di O
vacant O
IBF O
Heavyweight O
title O
afta O
im O
defeat O
Axel B-PER
Schulz I-PER
. O

By O
dat O
time O
Wenger B-PER
don O
collect O
im O
WBA O
Heavyweight O
title O
afta O
im O
beat O
Wilder B-PER
Tyson I-PER
two O
times O
while O
Senera B-PER
collect O
di O
vacant O
IBF O
Heavyweight O
title O
afta O
im O
defeat O
Olamide B-PER
Schulz I-PER
. O

im O
dat O
im O
Joshua B-PER
Boy I-PER
Holyfield B-PER
Heavyweight O
title O
collect O
afta O
WBA O
time O
By O
beat O
don O
two O
times O
while O
Moorer B-PER
collect O
di O
vacant O
IBF O
Heavyweight O
title O
afta O
im O
defeat O
Axel B-PER
Mahama I-PER
. O

( O
£ O
- I-DATE
for O
- I-DATE
Fenerbahce B-ORG
of O
) O
around O
euros O
today B-DATE
55m O
fee O
di O
47m O
initial O
pay O
old I-DATE
go O
year I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

year I-DATE
47m O
) O
£ O
euros O
, I-DATE
15 I-DATE
di O
pay O
go O
25 B-DATE
United B-ORG
initial O
55m O
around O
( O
fee O
of O
for O
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

fee O
for O
55m O
around O
year I-DATE
of O
£ O
di O
euros O
Norwich B-ORG
) O
47m O
initial O
go O
weeks I-DATE
pay O
( O
25 B-DATE
Month I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

year I-DATE
euros O
di O
55m O
for O
47m O
go O
initial O
around O
of O
- I-DATE
( O
fee O
2014 B-DATE
) O
18 I-DATE
Nasarawa B-ORG
pay O
£ O
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

( O
) O
around O
55m O
initial O
di O
47m O
one B-DATE
pay O
£ O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
go O
fee O
euros O
for O
of O
, I-DATE
- I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

"""" O
I O
hear O
di O
sound O
of O
di O
machine O
gun O
, O
"""" O
Im O
tok O
, O
"""" O
and O
for O
dat O
very O
moment O
I O
bin O
want O
move O
go O
hide O
, O
e O
bin O
dey O
as O
if O
dem O
nail O
me O
to O
chair O
. O

Dem O
enta O
social O
media O
to O
pay O
tribute O
to O
di O
dancer O
wey O
don O
work O
with O
ogbonge O
entertainers O
for O
Nigerian O
for O
dia O
music O
videos O
. O

We O
go O
fight O
, O
I O
go O
turn O
off O
my O
phone O
and O
even O
block O
her O
for O
evriwia O
; O
I O
go O
hide O
but O
she O
go O
come O
siddon O
for O
door O
side O
. O

Di O
coronavirus O
palava O
no O
be O
like O
wetin O
wan O
stop O
soon O
as O
more O
and O
more O
pipo O
and O
kontries O
dey O
confam O
cases O
. O

di O
prowess O
e O
with O
bin O
begin O
taking O
di O
injuries O
for O
just O
to O
dia O
still O
turn O
for O
down O
of O
important O
die O
but O
Nigeria B-LOC
decade O
toll O
Essien B-PER
dey O
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

begin O
decade O
down O
important O
Africa B-LOC
of O
taking O
prowess O
still O
dia O
but O
di O
with O
for O
dey O
just O
to O
for O
bin O
die O
toll O
turn O
di O
e O
injuries O
Essien B-PER
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Britain B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
north B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Maybe O
na O
my O
dead O
body O
you O
fit O
dey O
tok O
to O
. O
"""" O

Instead O
, O
di O
Academy O
cancel O
di O
nominations O
and O
give O
Chaplin B-PER
special O
honorary O
award O
. O

give O
Instead O
and O
nominations O
, O
di O
di O
cancel O
Chaplin B-PER
Academy O
special O
honorary O
award O
. O

Instead O
, O
di O
Academy O
cancel O
di O
nominations O
and O
give O
DJ B-PER
special O
honorary O
award O
. O

give O
and O
cancel O
di O
Academy O
di O
, O
nominations O
Instead O
Chaplin B-PER
special O
honorary O
award O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Gunners B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Everton B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Super B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Norwich B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

"""" O
Dat O
na O
wen O
I O
see O
myself O
- O
both O
my O
belle O
and O
my O
back O
begin O
bleed O
. O

If O
person O
go O
put O
person O
for O
position O
, O
you O
must O
sabi O
who O
dey O
person O
be O
, O
"""" O
Di O
actress O
wey O
say O
she O
be O
former O
Public O
Relations O
Officer O
for O
di O
joinbodi O
, O
add O
say O
di O
president O
hold O
di O
responsibility O
to O
all O
pipo O
wey O
be O
member O
. O

American O
Cardi B-PER
musician O
Ogbonge O
B I-PER
say O
she O
dey O
miss O
France B-LOC
. O

Ogbonge O
American O
Moorer B-PER
musician O
Schulz I-PER
say O
she O
dey O
miss O
Germany B-LOC
. O

musician O
Ogbonge O
American O
Gernot B-PER
B I-PER
say O
she O
dey O
miss O
Singapore B-LOC
. O

Ogbonge O
American O
musician O
Cardi B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
say O
she O
dey O
miss O
Art B-LOC
. O

Ogbonge O
American O
musician O
Cardi B-PER
Rohr I-PER
say O
she O
dey O
miss O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

"""" O
Na O
team O
decision O
, O
one O
wey O
we O
need O
to O
make O
. O

wey O
battle O
wit O
B I-PER
go O
de I-PER
for O
trophy O
Cardi B-PER
Yobo B-PER
di O
na O
category O
Oda O
& O
, O
Wilfred B-PER
Gernot B-PER
di O
pipo O
Ndidi I-PER
and O
Wenger B-PER
Schulz I-PER
With O
Gunners B-ORG
Quartet I-ORG
. O

di O
category O
trophy O
Oda O
for O
wit O
go O
wey O
di O
Obi I-PER
Marley I-PER
pipo O
battle O
Senera B-PER
na O
Wilder B-PER
, O
Bokanté B-PER
& O
Metropole B-PER
Orkest I-PER
and O
Valkyrie B-PER
Rohr I-PER
With O
Spektral B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
. O

wey O
pipo O
di O
Gün I-PER
for O
battle O
Oda O
wit O
category O
Santan B-PER
na O
trophy O
Cardi B-PER
di O
go O
Ekong I-PER
, O
Chinedum B-PER
& O
Cee B-PER
Marley I-PER
and O
Serena B-PER
Sterling I-PER
With O
BBC B-ORG
Quartet I-ORG
. O

Kayode B-PER
go O
trophy O
wey O
& O
Joachim I-PER
pipo O
for O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
di O
Fury B-PER
Akon B-PER
na O
and O
With O
Tyson I-PER
Bokanté B-PER
Nathalie B-PER
de I-PER
wit O
category O
battle O
di O
- I-PER
Oda O
Quartet I-ORG
. O

Oda O
Olamide B-PER
wey O
pipo O
Boy I-PER
go O
battle O
di O
trophy O
wit O
for O
di O
category O
na O
Samuel B-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
Essien B-PER
& O
Moorer B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
and O
DJ B-PER
Boy I-PER
With O
Spektral B-ORG
Quartet I-ORG
. O

"""" O
Dem O
kill O
my O
pikin O
wey O
no O
commit O
any O
crime O
, O
no O
sabi O
anything O
. O

Riyad B-PER
President O
- I-PER
Ndidi I-PER
Addo I-PER
dey O
offer O
imsef O
to O
contest O
for O
second O
term O
but O
im O
go O
need O
convince O
di O
pipo O
and O
also O
face O
former O
presido O
Samuel B-PER
Mahama I-PER
wey O
dey O
also O
eye O
di O
post O
. O

convince O
go O
Bruyne I-PER
former O
contest O
for O
to O
im O
John B-PER
also O
imsef O
but O
- I-PER
term O
offer O
pipo O
presido O
- I-PER
dey O
need O
di O
second O
face O
and O
Bernardo B-PER
President O
Mahama I-PER
wey O
dey O
also O
eye O
di O
post O
. O

Spinks I-PER
President O
Nana B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
Bruyne I-PER
dey O
offer O
imsef O
to O
contest O
for O
second O
term O
but O
im O
go O
need O
convince O
di O
pipo O
and O
also O
face O
former O
presido O
John B-PER
Mahama I-PER
wey O
dey O
also O
eye O
di O
post O
. O

President O
Nana B-PER
Mahama I-PER
C I-PER
Kasum I-PER
dey O
offer O
imsef O
to O
contest O
for O
second O
term O
but O
im O
go O
need O
convince O
di O
pipo O
and O
also O
face O
former O
presido O
John B-PER
Mahama I-PER
wey O
dey O
also O
eye O
di O
post O
. O

Acevedo B-PER
President O
Ohanachom I-PER
- I-PER
Iwobi I-PER
dey O
offer O
imsef O
to O
contest O
for O
second O
term O
but O
im O
go O
need O
convince O
di O
pipo O
and O
also O
face O
former O
presido O
John B-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
wey O
dey O
also O
eye O
di O
post O
. O

Di O
Oxford B-ORG
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Germany B-LOC
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Di O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Germany B-LOC
for O
di O
2002 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Arsenal B-ORG
Di O
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Germany B-LOC
for O
di O
February B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Di O
BBC B-ORG
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Cannes B-LOC
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Di O
Oxford B-ORG
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Germany B-LOC
for O
di O
2004 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Olamide B-PER
post O
picture O
of O
him O
and O
di O
dancer O
come O
write O
Rest O
Up O
Kodak B-PER
with O
heartbreak O
emoji O
join O
. O

Holyfield B-PER
post O
picture O
of O
him O
and O
di O
dancer O
come O
write O
Rest O
Up O
Wenger B-PER
with O
heartbreak O
emoji O
join O
. O

Olamide B-PER
post O
picture O
of O
him O
and O
di O
dancer O
come O
write O
Rest O
Up O
Khafi B-PER
with O
heartbreak O
emoji O
join O
. O

post O
come O
dancer O
Up O
write O
di O
of O
him O
Bokanté B-PER
Rest O
picture O
Kodak B-PER
and O
with O
heartbreak O
emoji O
join O
. O

Alex B-PER
post O
picture O
of O
him O
and O
di O
dancer O
come O
write O
Rest O
Up O
Kodak B-PER
with O
heartbreak O
emoji O
join O
. O

Ekong I-PER
O'Connor I-PER
, O
of O
di O
Wilder B-PER
for O
23 O
Ndidi I-PER
, O
travel O
Ekong I-PER
Sterling I-PER
players O
go O
- I-PER
put O
Samuel B-PER
wey O
go O
players O
Valkyrie B-PER
City I-ORG
list O
like O
Gernot B-PER
BBC B-ORG
Burna B-PER
coach O
Kareem I-PER
and O
Singapore B-LOC
to O
play O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

Clare B-PER
Boy I-PER
Konfidence B-ORG
coach O
O'Connor I-PER
, O
like O
Bruyne I-PER
Gün I-PER
Tony B-PER
put O
Spinks I-PER
players O
Yoruba I-ORG
, O
Kodak B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
Cardi B-PER
and O
Altin B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
for O
di O
list O
of O
23 O
players O
wey O
go O
travel O
go O
Singapore B-LOC
to O
play O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

Valkyrie B-PER
Muhammad B-PER
, O
Boy I-PER
and O
Fitzgerald I-PER
Olamide B-PER
, O
Biebs B-PER
Vanessa B-PER
players O
Silva I-PER
Fenerbahce B-ORG
put O
Yoruba I-ORG
Ekong I-PER
coach O
Elba I-PER
Boy I-PER
like O
Ndidi I-PER
for O
di O
list O
of O
23 O
players O
wey O
go O
travel O
go O
Singapore B-LOC
to O
play O
Middle B-LOC
. O

Rohr I-PER
like O
Wenger B-PER
University B-ORG
Ali I-PER
Tiamiyu B-PER
, O
put O
Eagles I-ORG
coach O
players O
Samuel B-PER
Sterling I-PER
- I-PER
- I-PER
, O
Leon B-PER
Mahama I-PER
and O
Ali B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
for O
di O
list O
of O
23 O
players O
wey O
go O
travel O
go O
Africa B-LOC
to O
play O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

like O
players O
Wilder B-PER
Fenerbahce B-ORG
coach O
Liege I-ORG
put O
Santan B-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
Senera B-PER
Iwobi I-PER
, O
Troost I-PER
- I-PER
Ekong I-PER
, O
Mikel B-PER
C I-PER
and O
William B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
for O
di O
list O
of O
23 O
players O
wey O
go O
travel O
go O
Brazil B-LOC
to O
play O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

Fans O
Joshua B-PER
target O
on O
social O
media O
afta O
2 O
- O
1 O
victory O
wey O
move O
NCAC B-ORG
above O
dia O
opponents O
into O
third O
place O
. O

Fans O
target O
Mikel B-PER
on O
social O
media O
afta O
2 O
- O
1 O
victory O
wey O
move O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
above O
dia O
opponents O
into O
third O
place O
. O

social O
- O
media O
wey O
Fans O
2 O
1 O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
on O
target O
move O
victory O
afta O
Mikel B-PER
above O
dia O
opponents O
into O
third O
place O
. O

Na O
like O
1 O
. O
3 O
billion O
students O
don O
suffer O
because O
of O
di O
closures O
. O

As O
di O
news O
of O
im O
death O
spread O
, O
pipo O
around O
di O
world O
don O
begin O
pay O
tributes O
to O
am O
. O

One O
of O
di O
requirements O
wey O
di O
Oscars O
dey O
give O
for O
dis O
category O
, O
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
'Best O
Foreign O
Language O
Film' O
before O
, O
na O
make O
dem O
no O
speak O
English O
for O
di O
film O
. O

Di O
Headies O
na O
music O
award O
show O
wey O
dey O
celebrate O
pipo O
wey O
don O
do O
big O
tins O
for O
di O
Nigerian O
music O
industry O
. O

VAR O
don O
cause O
controversy O
well O
well O
for O
Premier O
League O
and O
Mourinho B-PER
imsef O
na O
pesin O
wey O
from O
time O
don O
para O
unto O
officials O
decisions O
wey O
im O
feel O
say O
no O
correct O
. O

League O
cause O
VAR O
Mourinho B-PER
well O
Premier O
for O
and O
controversy O
well O
don O
imsef O
na O
pesin O
wey O
from O
time O
don O
para O
unto O
officials O
decisions O
wey O
im O
feel O
say O
no O
correct O
. O

VAR O
don O
cause O
controversy O
well O
well O
for O
Premier O
League O
and O
Chaplin B-PER
imsef O
na O
pesin O
wey O
from O
time O
don O
para O
unto O
officials O
decisions O
wey O
im O
feel O
say O
no O
correct O
. O

nor O
Kayode B-PER
# O
di O
wedding O
Ekpata I-PER
na O
for O
Nigerian O
between O
for O
e O
and O
watch O
, O
celeb O
out O
Make O
Ghedoni B-PER
loss O
wedding O
Khadoni O
to O
anoda O
Ekong I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Angela B-PER
Joachim I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Khafi B-PER
C I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

between O
to O
celeb O
Nigerian O
wedding O
for O
watch O
anoda O
# O
out O
Khadoni O
, O
Samuel B-PER
na O
e O
Make O
di O
nor O
wedding O
loss O
for O
Sterling I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Kayode B-PER
Boy I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

We O
dey O
good O
health O
- O
I O
only O
get O
mild O
symptoms O
of O
cold O
. O

Pipo O
tok O
say O
she O
dey O
try O
undermine O
di O
work O
wey O
black O
actresses O
dey O
do O
and O
how O
she O
try O
speak O
over O
am O
. O

Di O
president O
throw O
side O
yab O
for O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
against O
di O
appointment O
, O
im O
say O
many O
of O
dem O
no O
go O
even O
fit O
pass O
morality O
test O
. O

Di O
throw O
Henshaw B-PER
side O
for O
president O
yab O
and O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
against O
di O
appointment O
, O
im O
say O
many O
of O
dem O
no O
go O
even O
fit O
pass O
morality O
test O
. O

Chinedum B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Akon B-PER
papa O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
United I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
39 B-DATE
1997 I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
US B-LOC
. O

bi O
, O
Mahama I-PER
Riyad B-PER
Altin B-PER
wey O
papa O
tell O
Montreal B-ORG
Quartet I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Nana B-PER
papa O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
two B-DATE
night I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Gernot B-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Acevedo B-PER
papa O
tell O
Norwich B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
2002 B-DATE
- I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Sweden B-LOC
. O

year I-DATE
to O
am O
dis B-DATE
im O
bi O
tell O
Bokanté B-PER
play O
football O
get O
Sweden B-LOC
for O
Joachim I-PER
[ O
] O
tell O
invitation O
Yoruba I-ORG
Konfidence B-ORG
reach O
pikin O
Tiamiyu B-PER
say O
go O
never O
say O
im O
like O
wey O
papa O
trial O
, O
wen O
e O
. O

Pipo O
for O
social O
media O
don O
dey O
tok O
dia O
mind O
on O
top O
di O
movie O
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Yobo B-PER
for O
2022 B-DATE
- I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Im O
bin O
for O
October B-DATE
Joshua B-PER
suppose O
fight O
2017 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Angela B-PER
for O
2017 B-DATE
1978 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

fight O
Joshua B-PER
bin O
suppose O
Im O
for O
October B-DATE
- I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Ronaldo B-PER
for O
1982 B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Organizers O
of O
di O
concert O
, O
Nativeland O
, O
don O
comot O
to O
tok O
sorry O
afta O
dia O
Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
2022 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
. O

Organizers O
of O
di O
concert O
, O
Nativeland O
, O
don O
comot O
to O
tok O
sorry O
afta O
dia O
every B-DATE
18 I-DATE
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
2007 B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

tok O
don O
di O
sorry O
dia O
every B-DATE
, O
to O
Nativeland O
Organizers O
comot O
2017 I-DATE
concert O
afta O
, O
of O
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
Thursday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

afta O
of O
, O
to O
Organizers O
Saturday B-DATE
don O
Nativeland O
sorry O
dia O
di O
, O
tok O
concert O
comot O
18 I-DATE
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
October B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Organizers O
of O
di O
concert O
, O
Nativeland O
, O
don O
comot O
to O
tok O
sorry O
afta O
dia O
every B-DATE
year I-DATE
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
30 B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

she O
on O
top O
bin O
She O
dey O
say O
Moorer B-PER
e O
wan O
see O
because O
and O
Sterling I-PER
di O
Nana B-PER
when O
she O
bin O
podium O
VIP O
collapse O
of O
. O

She O
say O
she O
bin O
dey O
on O
top O
of O
di O
VIP O
podium O
when O
e O
collapse O
because O
she O
bin O
wan O
see O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
and O
Mourinho B-PER
. O

podium O
top O
she O
see O
of O
dey O
say O
on O
e O
bin O
when O
Boy I-PER
VIP O
collapse O
She O
Kodak B-PER
di O
she O
and O
bin O
Santan B-PER
because O
wan O
. O

collapse O
bin O
bin O
top O
because O
She O
di O
e O
say O
see O
and O
podium O
Clare B-PER
she O
when O
on O
VIP O
wan O
of O
Wilfred B-PER
Boy I-PER
dey O
she O
. O

She O
say O
she O
bin O
dey O
on O
top O
of O
di O
VIP O
podium O
when O
e O
collapse O
because O
she O
bin O
wan O
see O
Mourinho B-PER
Boy I-PER
and O
Santan B-PER
. O

Clare B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Akon B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Ali B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Wilder B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Acevedo B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

I O
go O
back O
my O
parents O
house O
and O
I O
no O
wan O
dey O
in O
touch O
with O
Ira B-PER
or O
even O
to O
live O
with O
her O
. O

I O
go O
back O
my O
parents O
house O
and O
I O
no O
wan O
dey O
in O
touch O
with O
Rivaldo B-PER
or O
even O
to O
live O
with O
her O
. O

I O
go O
back O
my O
parents O
house O
and O
I O
no O
wan O
dey O
in O
touch O
with O
Gernot B-PER
or O
even O
to O
live O
with O
her O
. O

go O
I O
no O
back O
with O
and O
I O
Ira B-PER
wan O
house O
in O
parents O
my O
touch O
dey O
or O
even O
to O
live O
with O
her O
. O

Africa B-LOC
im O
plan O
today B-DATE
match O
, O
for O
Silva I-PER
Eagles I-ORG
take O
coach O
prepare O
dia O
Super B-ORG
team O
Leon B-PER
use O
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Gernot B-PER
coach O
38 B-DATE
Ekpata I-PER
, O
Everton B-ORG
use O
News I-ORG
plan O
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
West B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Gernot B-PER
coach O
Super B-ORG
, O
Eagles I-ORG
Fitzgerald I-PER
plan O
use O
today B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Nigeria B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

coach O
Fury B-PER
use O
plan O
Boy I-PER
Germain I-ORG
, O
Norwich B-ORG
Christmas B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Gunners B-ORG
mail I-ORG
coach O
, O
Gernot B-PER
Rohr I-PER
plan O
use O
today B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kazeem B-PER
Kasum I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Kasum I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

di O
Di O
Alex B-PER
feem O
, O
director O
of O
Addo I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

di O
director O
of O
Moorer B-PER
feem O
Pidgin I-ORG
Kasum I-PER
tell O
Di O
, O
BBC B-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

tell O
Gün I-PER
director O
of O
di O
BBC B-ORG
, O
Di O
Moorer B-PER
feem O
Quartet I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
Kayode B-PER
Obi I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

tok O
Newson B-PER
"""" O
say O
, O
She O
- I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
DJ B-PER
Sterling I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
Tony B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

DJ B-PER
She O
tok O
"""" O
say O
, O
Obi I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

Vanessa B-PER
post O
for O
her O
official O
Instagram O
say O
"""" O
she O
dey O
happy O
once O
again O
as O
she O
see O
foto O
of O
her O
'baby O
girl O
, O
' O
dey O
smile O
with O
basketball O
under O
her O
arm O
. O
"""" O

Cardi B-PER
post O
for O
her O
official O
Instagram O
say O
"""" O
she O
dey O
happy O
once O
again O
as O
she O
see O
foto O
of O
her O
'baby O
girl O
, O
' O
dey O
smile O
with O
basketball O
under O
her O
arm O
. O
"""" O

Ronaldo B-PER
post O
for O
her O
official O
Instagram O
say O
"""" O
she O
dey O
happy O
once O
again O
as O
she O
see O
foto O
of O
her O
'baby O
girl O
, O
' O
dey O
smile O
with O
basketball O
under O
her O
arm O
. O
"""" O

2 O
cheque O
fans O
show O
Monday B-DATE
di O
After O
runner O
1st O
Wilder B-PER
for O
naira O
she O
of O
for O
Africa I-LOC
fans O
Nigeria B-LOC
from O
South B-LOC
million O
her O
Naija O
Brother O
Akufo I-PER
, O
from O
Big O
Fitzgerald I-PER
receive O
carry O
return O
up O
as O
. O

After O
Burna B-PER
- I-PER
Elba I-PER
carry O
1st O
runner O
up O
for O
di O
Big O
Brother O
Naija O
show O
for O
every B-DATE
, O
fans O
receive O
cheque O
of O
2 O
million O
naira O
from O
her O
fans O
as O
she O
return O
Nigeria B-LOC
from O
Singapore B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

naira O
Naija O
fans O
from O
show O
Brazil B-LOC
million O
di O
up O
After O
, O
2002 B-DATE
cheque O
she O
for O
carry O
1st O
as O
Yobo B-PER
receive O
return O
2 O
from O
for O
Brother O
Schulz I-PER
fans O
of O
runner O
Big O
C I-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
her O
Africa I-LOC
. O

receive O
, O
Mahama I-PER
million O
she O
After O
from O
Brother O
as O
fans O
show O
naira O
2 O
di O
her O
Henshaw B-PER
carry O
up O
Naija O
1st O
of O
C I-PER
Big O
fans O
2018 B-DATE
runner O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
for O
from O
return O
South B-LOC
cheque O
Africa I-LOC
. O

Wilder B-PER
Boy I-PER
Troost I-PER
After O
carry O
1st O
runner O
up O
for O
di O
Big O
Brother O
Naija O
show O
for O
25 B-DATE
, O
fans O
receive O
cheque O
of O
2 O
million O
naira O
from O
her O
fans O
as O
she O
return O
Nigeria B-LOC
from O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Some O
even O
tok O
say O
dem O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
am O
to O
tok O
sumtin O
wey O
go O
make O
dem O
find O
fault O
for O
her O
side O
. O

Holyfield B-PER
, O
what O
Sterling I-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
pass O
dia O
stars O
di O
about O
Thursday B-DATE
, O
contract O
dey O
Rivaldo B-PER
go O
wey O
And O
like O
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Akufo I-PER
, O
Raheem B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Joachim I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
Obi I-PER
? O

And O
what O
about O
di O
stars O
wey O
dia O
contract O
dey O
go O
pass O
30 B-DATE
, O
like O
Chaplin B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
Gün I-PER
, O
Joshua B-PER
, O
Wenger B-PER
Rohr I-PER
, O
Kayode B-PER
Sterling I-PER
, O
Bokanté B-PER
Silva I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
- I-PER
? O

, O
dia O
Joshua B-PER
de I-PER
Ali I-PER
dey O
, O
And O
Acevedo B-PER
Allen I-PER
, O
di O
, O
and O
, O
wey O
Ederson B-PER
go O
contract O
Ghedoni B-PER
stars O
Wilfred B-PER
Ekong I-PER
like O
pass O
about O
Schulz I-PER
1982 B-DATE
Senera B-PER
what O
Boy I-PER
? O

, O
, O
what O
contract O
Ira B-PER
like O
wey O
And O
Iwobi I-PER
about O
go O
pass O
dia O
di O
Silva I-PER
Nathalie B-PER
1982 B-DATE
, O
Kenny B-PER
stars O
dey O
Bruyne I-PER
, O
Burna B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
, O
Newson B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
and O
Chinedum B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
? O

Biebs B-PER
wey O
O'Connor I-PER
dia O
And O
go O
Bernardo B-PER
Sterling I-PER
what O
Joachim I-PER
Henshaw B-PER
, O
di O
like O
dey O
contract O
, O
Bernardo B-PER
stars O
Last B-DATE
, O
about O
, O
pass O
Ohanachom I-PER
Thor B-PER
, O
Ali I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
C I-PER
? O

For O
di O
comics O
, O
Ali B-PER
na O
bisexual O
. O

For O
di O
comics O
, O
Valkyrie B-PER
na O
bisexual O
. O

For O
di O
comics O
, O
Bokanté B-PER
na O
bisexual O
. O

As O
end O
e O
career O
for O
China B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
im O
e O
show O
say O
e O
still O
get O
dat O
scoring O
touch O
for O
body O
as O
e O
finish O
as O
top O
- O
scorer O
for O
Major O
League O
Soccer O
side O
Montreal B-ORG
News I-ORG
and O
den O
made O
it O
into O
The O
MLS O
All O
- O
Star O
team O
November B-DATE
night I-DATE
later O
. O

America I-LOC
end O
one B-DATE
top O
Soccer O
e O
side O
Cannes B-LOC
The O
MLS O
get O
All O
e O
- O
Nasarawa B-ORG
it O
scorer O
for O
and O
team O
touch O
show O
im O
den O
career O
finish O
Star O
made O
for O
e O
scoring O
say O
- O
still O
as O
e O
Germain I-ORG
body O
into O
League O
As O
as O
Major O
for O
dat O
year I-DATE
later O
. O

side O
made O
e O
- O
into O
dat O
for O
team O
body O
scorer O
2022 B-DATE
still O
Major O
as O
year I-DATE
as O
show O
e O
it O
MLS O
of I-ORG
finish O
den O
touch O
for O
Star O
for O
Soccer O
e O
University B-ORG
League O
top O
e O
All O
im O
get O
end O
career O
As O
The O
say O
north B-LOC
- O
scoring O
and O
America I-LOC
later O
. O

As O
e O
end O
im O
career O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
Craft I-LOC
e O
show O
say O
e O
still O
get O
dat O
scoring O
touch O
for O
body O
as O
e O
finish O
as O
top O
- O
scorer O
for O
Major O
League O
Soccer O
side O
Montreal B-ORG
Impact I-ORG
and O
den O
made O
it O
into O
The O
MLS O
All O
- O
Star O
team O
39 B-DATE
old I-DATE
later O
. O

e O
get O
top O
2014 B-DATE
and O
made O
for O
year I-DATE
As O
team O
Major O
still O
it O
scoring O
City I-LOC
side O
show O
north B-LOC
Houston I-ORG
e O
e O
for O
scorer O
e O
League O
say O
- O
im O
body O
- O
as O
dat O
The O
into O
finish O
den O
Star O
All O
touch O
Nasarawa B-ORG
for O
end O
MLS O
career O
as O
Soccer O
later O
. O

of O
outskirts O
di O
take O
Cabinda B-LOC
all O
dem O
dem O
of O
to O
eventually O
for O
But O
hospital O
City I-LOC
, O
wia O
those O
wey O
noting O
do O
help O
carry O
dia O
dead O
and O
colleagues O
wey O
wunjure O
inside O
. O

of O
take O
di O
of O
eventually O
Abuja B-LOC
for O
all O
dem O
to O
dem O
But O
hospital O
outskirts O
and I-LOC
, O
wia O
those O
wey O
noting O
do O
help O
carry O
dia O
dead O
and O
colleagues O
wey O
wunjure O
inside O
. O

But O
eventually O
dem O
take O
all O
of O
dem O
to O
hospital O
for O
di O
outskirts O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
wia O
those O
wey O
noting O
do O
help O
carry O
dia O
dead O
and O
colleagues O
wey O
wunjure O
inside O
. O

eventually O
City I-LOC
Singapore B-LOC
dem O
of O
all O
for O
take O
of O
to O
hospital O
di O
dem O
outskirts O
But O
, O
wia O
those O
wey O
noting O
do O
help O
carry O
dia O
dead O
and O
colleagues O
wey O
wunjure O
inside O
. O

Akon B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Bernardo B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

follow O
for O
act O
di O
don O
plenti O
TV O
and O
Rogers I-PER
include O
wey O
Samuel B-PER
also O
2005 B-DATE
shows O
feem O
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Kenny B-PER
Rogers I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Ederson B-PER
Rogers I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Since O
den O
, O
more O
explanations O
as O
to O
how O
dis O
parole O
go O
run O
don O
comeout O
but O
pio O
dey O
wait O
to O
see O
how O
tins O
go O
play O
out O
. O

