Cardi B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
north B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Sadio B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
use O
ogbonge O
title O
Nigeria B-LOC
win O
di O
fight O
for O
to O
from O
Las B-LOC
city I-LOC
on O
eight B-DATE
after O
Unai B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

title O
Calabasa I-LOC
fight O
ogbonge O
win O
western B-LOC
use O
for O
di O
from O
Las B-LOC
Kizz B-PER
to O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Duncan B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
NG B-LOC
Calabasa I-LOC
on O
September B-DATE
after O
Arsene B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Otile B-PER
from O
Nigeria B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
New B-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
on O
25 B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Make O
wey O
no O
forget O
say O
we O
dey O
see O
something O
wey O
we O
no O
dey O
every O
day O
. O

TZ B-LOC
Meanwhile O
di O
national O
team O
coach O
Allen B-PER
Bryant I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Ukraine B-LOC
Meanwhile O
di O
national O
team O
coach O
Sergio B-PER
Balakov I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Meanwhile O
di O
NG B-LOC
national O
team O
coach O
Gedoni B-PER
Emery I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
17 B-DATE
. O

Meanwhile O
di O
NG B-LOC
national O
team O
coach O
Krasimir B-PER
un I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Krasimir B-PER
di O
coach O
Meanwhile O
team O
national O
Bulgaria B-LOC
Balakov I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

But O
dem O
never O
see O
am O
since O
. O

She O
decide O
say O
we O
go O
dey O
sleep O
for O
different O
rooms O
and O
my O
room O
no O
get O
key O
. O

Twitter B-ORG
game O
pit O
Assou B-PER
Saturday B-DATE
go O
against O
Arsene B-PER
manager O
Lampard I-PER
, O
who O
play O
under O
the O
April B-DATE
months I-DATE
old I-DATE
, I-DATE
old I-DATE
man O
when O
e O
dey O
France B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

go O
against O
Khan B-PER
25 B-DATE
Jr I-PER
Nollywood B-ORG
pit O
manager O
game O
Colby B-PER
, O
who O
play O
under O
the O
23rd B-DATE
year I-DATE
12 I-DATE
Day I-DATE
old I-DATE
man O
when O
e O
dey O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

Christmas B-DATE
pit O
Zane B-PER
BBC B-ORG
game O
against O
Davido B-PER
manager O
go O
Daniel I-PER
, O
who O
play O
under O
the O
eight B-DATE
26 I-DATE
- I-DATE
26 I-DATE
old I-DATE
man O
when O
e O
dey O
Stamford B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Emery I-PER
manager O
, I-DATE
dey O
Stamford B-LOC
year I-DATE
, O
year I-DATE
Ancelotti B-PER
under O
who O
against O
last B-DATE
play O
pit O
KRC B-ORG
- I-LOC
game O
age B-DATE
Abe B-PER
- I-DATE
go O
when O
e O
the O
man O
. O

pit O
years I-DATE
under O
week I-DATE
who O
, O
against O
go O
Diamond B-PER
2019 B-DATE
Siasia B-PER
year I-DATE
2019 I-DATE
Saturday B-DATE
the O
game O
Lampard I-PER
play O
Bulgaria B-ORG
manager O
man O
when O
e O
dey O
GH B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

Di O
wey O
Genevieve B-PER
feem O
Nnaji I-PER
direct O
dey O
for O
English O
and O
Igbo O
, O
however O
dem O
speak O
English O
pass O
Igbo O
for O
di O
feem O
. O

Vanessa B-PER
feem O
Di O
wey O
Nnaji I-PER
direct O
dey O
for O
English O
and O
Igbo O
, O
however O
dem O
speak O
English O
pass O
Igbo O
for O
di O
feem O
. O

Di O
Nnaji I-PER
feem O
Abe B-PER
wey O
direct O
dey O
for O
English O
and O
Igbo O
, O
however O
dem O
speak O
English O
pass O
Igbo O
for O
di O
feem O
. O

Di O
feem O
wey O
Genevieve B-PER
Nnaji I-PER
direct O
dey O
for O
English O
and O
Igbo O
, O
however O
dem O
speak O
English O
pass O
Igbo O
for O
di O
feem O
. O

Di O
feem O
wey O
Famara B-PER
Ali I-PER
direct O
dey O
for O
English O
and O
Igbo O
, O
however O
dem O
speak O
English O
pass O
Igbo O
for O
di O
feem O
. O

young O
One O
for O
man O
NG B-LOC
share O
im O
story O
wit O
di O
BBC B-ORG
, O
on O
condition O
say O
dem O
go O
keep O
im O
identity O
secret O
. O

man O
Vietnam B-LOC
young O
share O
wit O
for O
story O
BBC B-ORG
di O
im O
One O
, O
on O
condition O
say O
dem O
go O
keep O
im O
identity O
secret O
. O

One O
im O
man O
for O
Marvel B-ORG
story O
Ukraine B-LOC
di O
share O
young O
wit O
, O
on O
condition O
say O
dem O
go O
keep O
im O
identity O
secret O
. O

BBC B-ORG
im O
young O
story O
di O
share O
wit O
man O
One O
Ukraine B-LOC
for O
, O
on O
condition O
say O
dem O
go O
keep O
im O
identity O
secret O
. O

One O
young O
man O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
share O
im O
story O
wit O
di O
BBC B-ORG
, O
on O
condition O
say O
dem O
go O
keep O
im O
identity O
secret O
. O

France B-LOC
Oscar O
Selection O
Committee O
for O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
disqualification O
for O
inside O
statement O
wey O
dem O
release O
say O
dem O
go O
learn O
from O
dis O
experience O
. O

NG B-LOC
Oscar O
Selection O
Committee O
for O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
disqualification O
for O
inside O
statement O
wey O
dem O
release O
say O
dem O
go O
learn O
from O
dis O
experience O
. O

Ghana B-LOC
Oscar O
Selection O
Committee O
for O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
disqualification O
for O
inside O
statement O
wey O
dem O
release O
say O
dem O
go O
learn O
from O
dis O
experience O
. O

Stamford B-LOC
Oscar O
Selection O
Committee O
for O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
disqualification O
for O
inside O
statement O
wey O
dem O
release O
say O
dem O
go O
learn O
from O
dis O
experience O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Oscar O
Selection O
Committee O
for O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
disqualification O
for O
inside O
statement O
wey O
dem O
release O
say O
dem O
go O
learn O
from O
dis O
experience O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
be O
be O
star O
or O
celebrity O
but O
you O
fit O
no O
be O
member O
of O
our O
joinbodi O
, O
"""" O
Rollas B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
interview O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
be O
be O
star O
or O
celebrity O
but O
you O
fit O
no O
be O
member O
of O
our O
joinbodi O
, O
"""" O
Siasia B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
interview O
. O

Emery B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
Every O
player O
usually O
need O
time O
to O
adapt O
. O

Xolani B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
Every O
player O
usually O
need O
time O
to O
adapt O
. O

Andy B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
Every O
player O
usually O
need O
time O
to O
adapt O
. O

Ebenazer I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
( O
Victor B-PER
( O
MVP O
( O
( O
Tetema O
) O
JoeBoy B-PER
) O
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
Rema B-PER
Margaret B-PER
) O
Teni B-PER
Mane I-PER
Africa B-LOC
spinall I-PER
Zanku O
GH B-LOC
- O
( O
( O
( O
Siasia B-PER
) O
UK B-LOC
Ekun I-PER
( O
) O
Lagos B-LOC
SONG O
) O
- O
Nigeria B-LOC
Yemi B-PER
- O
( O
( O
Akon B-PER
( O
MALE O
NG B-LOC
Legwork O
Buhari B-PER
( O
Adepero B-PER
) O
BEST O
) O
New B-LOC
OF O
) O
Essien B-PER
( O
Nathan B-PER
( O
Simi B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
) O
) O
( O
Baby O
) O
YEAR O
) O
England B-LOC
Williams B-PER
Abe B-PER
NG B-LOC
( O
) O
FEMALE O
( O
) O
B I-PER
DI O
( O
England B-LOC
Ira B-PER
JoeBoy B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
FireBoy B-PER
- O
Dumebi O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Las B-LOC
- O
BEST O
France B-LOC
Case O
Margaret B-PER
savage I-PER
NG B-LOC
Poland B-LOC
( O
x O
) O
Joeboi B-PER
Wilder I-PER
Europe B-LOC
) O

( O
( O
) O
MALE O
) O
BEST O
Paul B-PER
- O
Tetema O
Andy B-PER
Czech B-LOC
West B-LOC
( O
) O
SA B-LOC
FEMALE O
Africa B-LOC
- O
) O
) O
spinall I-PER
Eko B-LOC
John B-PER
) O
Fernandes B-PER
( O
Burna B-PER
) O
NG B-LOC
( O
un I-PER
( O
x O
SA B-LOC
Nandy B-PER
Brian B-PER
JoeBoy B-PER
) O
OF O
( O
) O
Gianna B-PER
) O
Zanku O
) O
( O
Vincent B-PER
NG B-LOC
Wilder B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
DI O
Senegal B-LOC
Mollie B-PER
( O
Case O
Jr I-PER
) O
JoeBoy B-PER
YEAR O
( O
) O
( O
England B-LOC
) O
( O
) O
SA B-LOC
( O
- O
Legwork O
Daphne B-PER
( O
) O
) O
SONG O
( O
Abuja B-LOC
- O
Tammy B-PER
Mourinho B-PER
Turkey B-LOC
) O
Ekun I-PER
SA B-LOC
( O
MVP O
( O
Baby O
BEST O
Oduye I-PER
Teni B-PER
NG B-LOC
Shay I-PER
California B-LOC
Allen B-PER
( O
Moses B-PER
"""" I-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
Ukraine B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
Burundi B-LOC
) O

( O
Kamaru B-PER
( O
( O
( O
Senegal B-LOC
GH B-LOC
) O
- O
- O
England B-LOC
) O
) O
Tiwa B-PER
( O
Zlatan B-PER
Tetema O
Zanku O
) O
Italy B-LOC
) O
Legwork O
Wilder B-PER
France B-LOC
FEMALE O
BEST O
Davido B-PER
TZ B-LOC
Czech B-LOC
Barber I-PER
Court I-PER
) O
Obi I-PER
Sergio B-PER
New B-LOC
) O
) O
) O
Ifeanyi B-PER
) O
x O
( O
MALE O
) O
Netherlands B-LOC
Africa B-LOC
( O
Shabalala B-PER
Sterling I-PER
Mane I-PER
Kobe B-PER
Jong I-PER
"""" I-PER
Nandy B-PER
( O
Angola B-LOC
) O
Zlatan B-PER
Bruno B-PER
Genevieve B-PER
GH B-LOC
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
King B-PER
) O
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
UK B-LOC
) O
( O
George I-PER
( O
( O
Mourinho B-PER
( O
Britain B-LOC
( O
( O
) O
BEST O
Falz B-PER
Zane B-PER
MVP O
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
DJ B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Teni B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

SA B-LOC
England B-LOC
Henshaw B-PER
Paul B-PER
DI O
) O
Samuel B-PER
Mollie B-PER
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
Owuo I-PER
"""" I-PER
( O
) O
FEMALE O
( O
France B-LOC
( O
Nandy B-PER
) O
Seifert I-PER
( O
) O
MVP O
Angola B-LOC
( O
) O
KE B-LOC
) O
( O
Seifert I-PER
BEST O
) O
Case O
Tiwa B-PER
Assou B-PER
( O
Henshaw B-PER
) O
( O
JoeBoy B-PER
Zanku O
SA B-LOC
Victor B-PER
( O
Tyson B-PER
Allen B-PER
Inama B-PER
north B-LOC
) O
) O
north B-LOC
) O
- O
UK B-LOC
( O
( O
- O
( O
Teni B-PER
BEST O
( O
( O
Fury I-PER
) O
NG B-LOC
Costello I-PER
Fury B-PER
SONG O
Baby O
) O
Kobe B-PER
Nandy B-PER
Jong I-PER
OF O
- O
) O
NG B-LOC
) O
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
Owuo I-PER
Legwork O
x O
NG B-LOC
( O
Sergio B-PER
Elisha B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Lagos B-LOC
MALE O
Tetema O
YEAR O
- O
( O
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
France B-LOC
) O

France B-LOC
( O
( O
Oshoala B-PER
) O
( O
( O
Macky B-PER
) O
( O
Kanye B-PER
- O
) O
( O
) O
NG B-LOC
( O
Muhammad B-PER
Zanku O
- O
Stamford B-LOC
- O
) O
FEMALE O
) O
Andrew B-PER
TZ B-LOC
Andrew B-PER
( O
Fury B-PER
YEAR O
Chukwueze I-PER
x O
Vietnam B-LOC
France B-LOC
( O
Wendy B-PER
Rodri B-PER
France B-LOC
Baby O
) O
Bishop I-PER
Burna B-PER
) O
Rema B-PER
California B-LOC
( O
) O
Legwork O
Gianna B-PER
( O
BEST O
Singapore B-LOC
( O
Goddard I-PER
BEST O
Ebenazer I-PER
) O
France B-LOC
DI O
) O
( O
China B-LOC
SONG O
Owuo I-PER
Henshaw B-PER
Skibii B-PER
) O
( O
China B-LOC
( O
( O
Seifert I-PER
Targaryen B-PER
MVP O
) O
- I-PER
OF O
Burna B-PER
( O
) O
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
GH B-LOC
Tetema O
MALE O
( O
) O
Kobe B-PER
NG B-LOC
Tuface B-PER
NG B-LOC
Onuachu I-PER
) O
France B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Usman B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Targaryen B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Henshaw B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
say O
because O
di O
exco O
get O
power O
to O
dey O
make O
some O
decisions O
for O
di O
members O
of O
di O
association O
, O
dem O
must O
do O
am O
with O
good O
of O
di O
members O
for O
mind O
. O

Tuface B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Nantes I-ORG
say O
because O
di O
exco O
get O
power O
to O
dey O
make O
some O
decisions O
for O
di O
members O
of O
di O
association O
, O
dem O
must O
do O
am O
with O
good O
of O
di O
members O
for O
mind O
. O

Sadio B-PER
tell O
Marvel B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
say O
because O
di O
exco O
get O
power O
to O
dey O
make O
some O
decisions O
for O
di O
members O
of O
di O
association O
, O
dem O
must O
do O
am O
with O
good O
of O
di O
members O
for O
mind O
. O

Sho B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
World I-ORG
say O
because O
di O
exco O
get O
power O
to O
dey O
make O
some O
decisions O
for O
di O
members O
of O
di O
association O
, O
dem O
must O
do O
am O
with O
good O
of O
di O
members O
for O
mind O
. O

Presido O
Paul B-PER
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
Abraham I-PER
, O
hold O
National O
Dialogue O
plus O
some O
oda O
tins O
im O
do O
so O
peace O
go O
dey O
di O
region O
including O
to O
give O
di O
region O
special O
status O
. O

Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Presido O
Paul B-PER
Biya I-PER
hold O
National O
Dialogue O
plus O
some O
oda O
tins O
im O
do O
so O
peace O
go O
dey O
di O
region O
including O
to O
give O
di O
region O
special O
status O
. O

Paul B-PER
May I-DATE
, O
Marley I-PER
7 B-DATE
Presido O
hold O
National O
Dialogue O
plus O
some O
oda O
tins O
im O
do O
so O
peace O
go O
dey O
di O
region O
including O
to O
give O
di O
region O
special O
status O
. O

12 B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Presido O
Zlatan B-PER
Boy I-PER
hold O
National O
Dialogue O
plus O
some O
oda O
tins O
im O
do O
so O
peace O
go O
dey O
di O
region O
including O
to O
give O
di O
region O
special O
status O
. O

Fernandes B-PER
move O
dey O
subject O
to O
im O
medical O
and O
agreement O
of O
personal O
terms O
. O

Anthony B-PER
move O
dey O
subject O
to O
im O
medical O
and O
agreement O
of O
personal O
terms O
. O

E O
neva O
too O
tay O
wey O
somebody O
release O
anoda O
nude O
video O
for O
social O
media O
wey O
show O
somebody O
wey O
look O
like O
one O
senator O
and O
di O
issue O
also O
cause O
tok O
- O
tok O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
. O

E O
neva O
too O
tay O
wey O
somebody O
release O
anoda O
nude O
video O
for O
social O
media O
wey O
show O
somebody O
wey O
look O
like O
one O
senator O
and O
di O
issue O
also O
cause O
tok O
- O
tok O
for O
Real B-ORG
. O

E O
neva O
too O
tay O
wey O
somebody O
release O
anoda O
nude O
video O
for O
social O
media O
wey O
show O
somebody O
wey O
look O
like O
one O
senator O
and O
di O
issue O
also O
cause O
tok O
- O
tok O
for O
BBC B-ORG
. O

E O
neva O
too O
tay O
wey O
somebody O
release O
anoda O
nude O
video O
for O
social O
media O
wey O
show O
somebody O
wey O
look O
like O
one O
senator O
and O
di O
issue O
also O
cause O
tok O
- O
tok O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

on O
say O
Sunday B-DATE
ten O
ogbonge O
year I-DATE
as O
gbab O
, O
top O
year I-DATE
tins O
December B-DATE
Eko B-LOC
Boy I-PER
nominations O
break O
happun O
Didier B-PER
im O
for O
record O
some O
Coast I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

tins O
year I-DATE
ogbonge O
Onuachu I-PER
happun O
as O
some O
Pellegrini B-PER
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
break O
record O
on O
top O
say O
im O
gbab O
ten O
nominations O
Tuesday B-DATE
- I-DATE
for O
NG B-LOC
east I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

hotel I-LOC
tins O
ten O
Nigeria B-LOC
say O
im O
year I-DATE
Burna B-PER
Alade I-PER
nominations O
happun O
old I-DATE
12 B-DATE
record O
Africa I-LOC
gbab O
as O
, O
break O
Dis B-DATE
top O
for O
some O
ogbonge O
on O
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

say O
Dis B-DATE
1982 B-DATE
, O
happun O
top O
some O
ten O
ogbonge O
morning I-DATE
im O
Boy I-PER
tins O
gbab O
on O
nominations O
record O
as O
Siasia B-PER
break O
evening I-DATE
for O
Senegal B-LOC
hotel I-LOC
hotel I-LOC
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

Covington B-PER
ogbonge O
happun O
tins O
Kwadjo I-PER
some O
as O
Boxing B-DATE
, O
morning I-DATE
break O
record O
on O
top O
say O
im O
gbab O
ten O
nominations O
a B-DATE
year I-DATE
for O
Eko B-LOC
hotel I-LOC
Mumbai I-LOC
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

Drogba I-PER
Abbo I-PER
foto O
, O
of O
daughter O
her O
share O
for O
Covington B-PER
media O
of O
Barber I-PER
hours I-DATE
late O
social O
Tiwa B-PER
wife O
Saturday B-DATE
Bryant I-PER
Kobe B-PER
Bishop I-PER
Di O
, O
on O
. O

"""" I-PER
Di O
Bryant I-PER
Mighty I-PER
Innocent B-PER
, O
of O
share O
wife O
foto O
Henshaw B-PER
late O
daughter O
of O
- I-PER
her O
Tiwa B-PER
DML I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
October B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

daughter O
her O
for O
late O
foto O
of O
share O
Di O
, O
- I-PER
on O
of O
Simon I-PER
Tunzi B-PER
social O
, O
Marley I-PER
Balakov I-PER
Boy I-PER
Saturday B-DATE
Burna B-PER
wife O
Burna B-PER
media O
night I-DATE
. O

night I-DATE
Di O
Osimhen I-PER
, O
Bjornsson B-PER
daughter O
JoeBoy B-PER
her O
foto O
Saturday B-DATE
Ighalo I-PER
late O
Fernandes I-PER
social O
for O
on O
Bryant I-PER
Muhammad B-PER
media O
Brands I-PER
, O
of O
wife O
share O
of O
. O

daughter O
Akon B-PER
of O
share O
Sall I-PER
Wilder B-PER
, O
late O
her O
foto O
Di O
Kizz B-PER
wife O
of O
Bishop I-PER
Gigi I-PER
Oduye I-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

second O
world O
e O
, O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
undefeated O
am O
lightweight O
IMF B-ORG
im O
for O
na O
year I-DATE
octagon O
defeat O
Club B-ORG
Williams B-PER
229 O
13th B-DATE
title O
Nurmagomedov I-PER
last O
wen O
for O
im O
Di O
for O
get O
and O
inside O
ring O
time O
2018 I-DATE
champion O
afta O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
9 B-DATE
win O
. O

undefeated O
and O
BBC B-ORG
Hip B-ORG
inside O
get O
Di O
e O
day I-DATE
Nancy B-PER
world O
for O
afta O
champion O
Manchester B-ORG
time O
lightweight O
im O
SK B-ORG
na O
wen O
win O
am O
defeat O
ring O
im O
octagon O
, O
for O
Nurmagomedov I-PER
second O
last O
title O
Dis B-DATE
229 O
for O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

afta O
title O
time O
inside O
week I-DATE
na O
im O
second O
and O
Di O
wen O
im O
e O
Arsenal B-ORG
last O
undefeated O
ring O
10 B-DATE
world O
for O
, O
octagon O
win O
get O
Hip B-ORG
UFC B-ORG
lightweight O
champion O
Sho B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
UFC B-ORG
229 O
for O
December B-DATE
- I-DATE
. O

old I-DATE
lightweight O
, O
for O
second O
get O
time O
undefeated O
dis B-DATE
world O
octagon O
Nurmagomedov I-PER
Di O
e O
title O
na O
ring O
Imo B-ORG
champion O
CAF B-ORG
wen O
afta O
and O
im O
win O
last O
Khabib B-PER
Southend B-ORG
im O
inside O
defeat O
am O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
229 O
for O
60 B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

Real B-ORG
im O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
afta O
octagon O
, O
ring O
and O
Manchester B-ORG
get O
na O
win O
for O
world O
2020 B-DATE
Di O
last O
second O
title O
im O
inside O
undefeated O
years I-DATE
e O
time O
wen O
lightweight O
champion O
Khabib B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
Real B-ORG
229 O
for O
2020 B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

Cable O
channel O
South B-ORG
don O
give O
go O
- O
ahead O
for O
part O
two O
series O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
TV O
show O
, O
Game O
of O
Thrones O
. O

Cable O
channel O
Twitter B-ORG
don O
give O
go O
- O
ahead O
for O
part O
two O
series O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
TV O
show O
, O
Game O
of O
Thrones O
. O

Cable O
channel O
HBO B-ORG
don O
give O
go O
- O
ahead O
for O
part O
two O
series O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
TV O
show O
, O
Game O
of O
Thrones O
. O

Cable O
channel O
Arsenal B-ORG
don O
give O
go O
- O
ahead O
for O
part O
two O
series O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
TV O
show O
, O
Game O
of O
Thrones O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Boko B-ORG
of I-ORG
Independent I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Manchester B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
City I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Manchester B-ORG
of I-ORG
United I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Watford B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
Guild I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Twitter B-ORG
of I-ORG
FC I-ORG
of I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

Di O
BFU B-ORG
say O
"""" O
dis O
na O
di O
consequence O
of O
di O
recent O
tensions O
"""" O
but O
dem O
no O
mention O
di O
word O
'racism' O
for O
dia O
statement O
. O

Di O
Real B-ORG
say O
"""" O
dis O
na O
di O
consequence O
of O
di O
recent O
tensions O
"""" O
but O
dem O
no O
mention O
di O
word O
'racism' O
for O
dia O
statement O
. O

Di O
Three B-ORG
say O
"""" O
dis O
na O
di O
consequence O
of O
di O
recent O
tensions O
"""" O
but O
dem O
no O
mention O
di O
word O
'racism' O
for O
dia O
statement O
. O

Di O
Daily B-ORG
say O
"""" O
dis O
na O
di O
consequence O
of O
di O
recent O
tensions O
"""" O
but O
dem O
no O
mention O
di O
word O
'racism' O
for O
dia O
statement O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
West B-LOC
York I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
TZ B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

, O
for O
Best O
, O
Cinematographer O
follow O
Sound O
Best O
feem O
Best O
for O
, O
UK B-LOC
Soundtrack O
Editor O
, O
Di O
Best O
Writers O
win O
Movie O
Best O
Africa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
NG B-LOC
Calabasa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Di O
club O
say O
dem O
don O
file O
"""" O
criminal O
complain O
"""" O
against O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
responsible O
. O

Dis O
na O
some O
of O
di O
tins O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
about O
Kenny B-PER
Emery I-PER
start O
im O
career O
for O
radio O
as O
junior O
programmes O
assistant O
for O
Saturday B-DATE
at O
di O
December B-DATE
year I-DATE
20 I-DATE
before O
im O
move O
up O
to O
di O
level O
of O
director O
. O

for O
programmes O
for O
career O
radio O
di O
tins O
about O
Manchester B-ORG
di O
age B-DATE
Dis O
for O
junior O
assistant O
some O
at O
na O
of O
Aguero I-PER
Diamond B-PER
start O
1982 B-DATE
tok O
as O
pipo O
im O
dey O
of I-DATE
20 I-DATE
before O
im O
move O
up O
to O
di O
level O
of O
director O
. O

tins O
Dis O
Everton B-ORG
Pete B-PER
di O
for O
pipo O
tok O
of O
na O
about O
some O
dey O
Henshaw I-PER
start O
im O
career O
for O
radio O
as O
junior O
programmes O
assistant O
for O
1967 B-DATE
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
20 I-DATE
before O
im O
move O
up O
to O
di O
level O
of O
director O
. O

di O
pipo O
some O
programmes O
Covington I-PER
for O
tok O
im O
tins O
for O
1982 B-DATE
Marvel B-ORG
career O
start O
night B-DATE
as O
na O
of O
at O
assistant O
Gianna B-PER
Dis O
radio O
dey O
about O
for O
junior O
di O
of I-DATE
20 I-DATE
before O
im O
move O
up O
to O
di O
level O
of O
director O
. O

Dis O
na O
some O
of O
di O
tins O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
for O
Terville B-ORG
about O
Davido B-PER
Usman I-PER
start O
im O
career O
for O
radio O
as O
junior O
programmes O
assistant O
for O
dis B-DATE
at O
di O
September B-DATE
to I-DATE
20 I-DATE
before O
im O
move O
up O
to O
di O
level O
of O
director O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
30 B-DATE
- I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

dat O
di O
middle O
30 B-DATE
"""" O
for O
of O
don O
dey O
We O
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
38 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
two B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
dat O
for O
night B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
or O
even O
more O
. O

dey O
for O
25 B-DATE
years I-DATE
here O
I O
"""" O
don O
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
BFU B-ORG
of I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Tacha B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

I O
kind O
neva O
- O
dey O
view O
here O
pay O
for O
investment O
fight O
don O
last I-DATE
dis O
I O
wetin O
"""" O
- O
"""" O
na O
see O
per O
and O
, O
for O
Sunday B-DATE
Manchester B-ORG
of I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Wilder B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

and O
dis B-DATE
Costello I-PER
correspondent O
na O
for O
neva O
"""" O
see O
"""" O
pay O
Allen B-PER
morning I-DATE
wetin O
dis O
, O
- O
I O
I O
kind O
boxing O
fight O
dey O
here O
UFC B-ORG
investment O
for O
OSC I-ORG
- O
view O
don O
per O
tok O
. O

for O
don O
pay O
UFC B-ORG
kind O
June I-DATE
view O
dis O
per O
wetin O
I O
investment O
na O
"""" O
neva O
- O
dey O
I O
"""" O
five B-DATE
see O
Sport I-ORG
for O
fight O
here O
, O
and O
- O
boxing O
correspondent O
Margaret B-PER
Oduye I-PER
tok O
. O

investment O
here O
10 B-DATE
- O
see O
morning I-DATE
- O
don O
, O
na O
view O
for O
BBC B-ORG
and O
per O
"""" O
for O
I O
neva O
pay O
I O
dis O
fight O
kind O
dey O
"""" O
wetin O
World I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
FireBoy B-PER
Bishop I-PER
tok O
. O

Usman B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

Mourinho B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

Chinko B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

striker O
international O
Ancelotti B-PER
George I-PER
TZ B-LOC
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
five B-DATE
week I-DATE
two I-DATE
. O

NG B-LOC
international O
striker O
Rayvanny B-PER
un I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
September B-DATE
Day I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
international O
striker O
Simmy B-PER
Costello I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
26 B-DATE
of I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

motor O
next B-DATE
for O
di O
of I-DATE
striker O
accident O
Nigeria B-LOC
Ifeanyi B-PER
don O
international O
die O
26 I-DATE
Marley I-PER
at O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
international O
striker O
Ifeanyi B-PER
Rogers I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

For O
Monday B-DATE
12 I-DATE
, O
Real B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

For O
2019 I-DATE
dis B-DATE
Watford B-ORG
, O
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

November B-DATE
For O
year I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Teni B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

2019 I-DATE
For O
, O
22 B-DATE
HBO B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Siasia B-PER
Goddard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

midfielder O
Mohamed B-PER
, O
and O
coach O
For O
Chelsea B-ORG
1994 I-DATE
Lampard I-PER
former O
, O
2020 B-DATE
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
great O
- O
nothing O
better O
pass O
make O
you O
prove O
pipo O
wrong O
. O

Afta O
di O
game O
Arsenal B-ORG
coach O
Unai B-PER
Jong I-PER
call O
Diamond B-PER
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

call O
Unai B-PER
game O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
coach O
Boy I-PER
Afta O
Pepe B-PER
di O
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

Afta O
di O
game O
Shanghai B-ORG
coach O
Unai B-PER
Emery I-PER
call O
Prince B-PER
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

Jong I-PER
Arsenal B-ORG
Pepe B-PER
Unai B-PER
Afta O
coach O
call O
game O
di O
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

Unai B-PER
Afta O
game O
coach O
di O
Emery I-PER
Arsenal B-ORG
call O
Andrew B-PER
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

na O
Davido B-PER
for O
dis O
sign O
Manchester B-ORG
sign O
afta O
player O
third O
Madrid I-ORG
Fernandes I-PER
di O
Manchester B-ORG
from O
transfer O
dem O
John B-PER
, O
last B-DATE
window O
wey O
Lisbon I-ORG
and O
Southend B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Ifeanyi B-PER
Bishop I-PER
. O

Tyson B-PER
two B-DATE
na O
afta O
United I-ORG
dem O
transfer O
Tacha B-PER
Manchester B-ORG
for O
Watford B-ORG
Union I-ORG
, O
sign O
sign O
from O
dis O
wey O
DML I-PER
window O
third O
di O
player O
and O
CAF B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Nathan B-PER
Lowe I-PER
. O

di O
third O
window O
dis O
afta O
2014 B-DATE
, O
dem O
for O
transfer O
wey O
Nathan B-PER
player O
sign O
Bruno B-PER
Norwich B-ORG
Salah I-PER
sign O
Brugge I-ORG
na O
from O
Sporting B-ORG
Worldwide I-ORG
and O
UFC B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Nathan B-PER
Bishop I-PER
. O

for O
third O
afta O
di O
, O
na O
SK B-ORG
player O
sign O
sign O
dem O
transfer O
from O
window O
Bruno B-PER
Marioo B-PER
dis O
Court I-PER
Ham I-ORG
wey O
Sporting B-ORG
last B-DATE
Nigeria I-ORG
and O
Southend B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Vanessa B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
. O

Margaret B-PER
na O
di O
third O
player O
wey O
Manchester B-ORG
Guild I-ORG
sign O
for O
dis O
Saturday B-DATE
transfer O
window O
, O
afta O
dem O
sign O
DJ B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
from O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
Guild I-ORG
and O
Actors B-ORG
goalkeeper O
AbboElisha B-PER
Bishop I-PER
. O

Didier B-PER
also O
B O
Footballer O
I O
captain O
Lakers I-ORG
newly O
Year O
di O
, O
of O
of O
for O
in O
di O
di O
Group O
ova O
France B-LOC
to O
Sporting B-ORG
handing O
east I-LOC
trophy O
cover O
di O
the O
dey O
Arsenal B-ORG
African O
dey O
of O
and O
- O
Hungary B-LOC
crowned O
winner O
of I-ORG
bin O
Drogba I-PER
to O
prepare O
dey O
bin O
, O
province O
charge O
, O
. O

di O
BBC B-ORG
di O
Sport I-ORG
Drogba I-PER
of O
bin O
winner O
newly O
, O
of O
to O
, O
and O
cover O
Africa I-ORG
captain O
Sporting B-ORG
di O
of O
dey O
handing O
province O
charge O
Republic I-LOC
prepare O
trophy O
I O
dey O
for O
the O
di O
to O
- O
NG B-LOC
in O
B O
Group O
ova O
Footballer O
bin O
dey O
Ira B-PER
African O
Year O
Ivory B-LOC
also O
, O
crowned O
. O

province O
I O
Singapore B-LOC
di O
dey O
bin O
of O
, O
dey O
prepare O
to O
cover O
Group O
B O
for O
di O
Girondins B-ORG
World I-ORG
Times I-ORG
, O
and O
bin O
also O
dey O
in O
charge O
of O
handing O
ova O
di O
Norwich B-ORG
African O
Footballer O
of O
the O
Year O
trophy O
to O
di O
newly O
- O
crowned O
winner O
, O
England B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
captain O
Sadio B-PER
Drogba I-PER
. O

di O
I O
B O
crowned O
cover O
trophy O
of O
to O
Year O
Brugge I-ORG
of O
African O
of O
bin O
United I-ORG
Footballer O
and O
Ivory B-LOC
the O
bin O
di O
Group O
BBC B-ORG
- O
also O
prepare O
dey O
, O
di O
newly O
charge O
in O
to O
, O
, O
NG B-LOC
dey O
di O
winner O
BBC B-ORG
ova O
handing O
dey O
province O
for O
Nigeria I-LOC
captain O
Andy B-PER
Dennis I-PER
. O

I O
bin O
dey O
di O
province O
of O
China B-LOC
, O
dey O
prepare O
to O
cover O
Group O
B O
for O
di O
West B-ORG
City I-ORG
OSC I-ORG
, O
and O
bin O
also O
dey O
in O
charge O
of O
handing O
ova O
di O
Terville B-ORG
African O
Footballer O
of O
the O
Year O
trophy O
to O
di O
newly O
- O
crowned O
winner O
, O
TZ B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
captain O
Khan B-PER
Drogba I-PER
. O

for O
, O
times O
Siasia B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
play O
50 O
over O
wey O
and O
score O
16 O
goals O
, O
never O
really O
follow O
im O
mama O
tok O
but O
e O
believe O
say O
she O
no O
well O
. O

Assou B-PER
, O
wey O
play O
over O
50 O
times O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
score O
16 O
goals O
, O
never O
really O
follow O
im O
mama O
tok O
but O
e O
believe O
say O
she O
no O
well O
. O

Siasia B-PER
, O
wey O
play O
over O
50 O
times O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
score O
16 O
goals O
, O
never O
really O
follow O
im O
mama O
tok O
but O
e O
believe O
say O
she O
no O
well O
. O

Siasia B-PER
, O
wey O
play O
over O
50 O
times O
for O
TZ B-LOC
and O
score O
16 O
goals O
, O
never O
really O
follow O
im O
mama O
tok O
but O
e O
believe O
say O
she O
no O
well O
. O

Prince B-PER
, O
wey O
play O
over O
50 O
times O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
score O
16 O
goals O
, O
never O
really O
follow O
im O
mama O
tok O
but O
e O
believe O
say O
she O
no O
well O
. O

E O
be O
season O
wey O
cold O
and O
wet O
and O
I O
no O
carry O
cloth O
for O
cold O
weather O
follow O
me O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
of I-DATE
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

26 B-DATE
to O
e O
dey O
But O
come O
school O
di O
of I-DATE
for O
forced O
leave O
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
years I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

school O
e O
come O
forced O
for O
di O
dey O
to O
age B-DATE
But O
leave O
July I-DATE
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

e O
leave O
come O
di O
for O
to O
school O
38 B-DATE
forced O
dey O
But O
of I-DATE
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

Many O
religious O
groups O
don O
carry O
dia O
faith O
enter O
internet O
as O
dem O
dey O
stuck O
for O
house O
with O
streaming O
and O
sabi O
pipo O
tok O
say O
dis O
practice O
fit O
no O
end O
any O
time O
soon O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
first O
time O
wey O
dem O
go O
nominate O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
for O
Grammy O
awards O
. O

wey O
na O
Kim B-PER
go O
di O
nominate O
Dis O
time O
first O
dem O
Boy I-PER
for O
Grammy O
awards O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
first O
time O
wey O
dem O
go O
nominate O
John B-PER
Boy I-PER
for O
Grammy O
awards O
. O

Dis O
time O
nominate O
di O
dem O
go O
wey O
Paul B-PER
first O
na O
Boy I-PER
for O
Grammy O
awards O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
first O
time O
wey O
dem O
go O
nominate O
Genevieve B-PER
Boy I-PER
for O
Grammy O
awards O
. O

Buhari B-PER
IV O
( O
These O
Times O
) O
' O
- O
Show O
Dem O
Camp O
Best O
R O
& O
B O
/ O
Pop O
Album O
· O
'rare O
. O

IV O
( O
These O
Akon B-PER
Times O
) O
' O
- O
Show O
Dem O
Camp O
Best O
R O
& O
B O
/ O
Pop O
Album O
· O
'rare O
. O

IV O
( O
These O
Burna B-PER
Times O
) O
' O
- O
Show O
Dem O
Camp O
Best O
R O
& O
B O
/ O
Pop O
Album O
· O
'rare O
. O

These O
Colby B-PER
IV O
( O
Times O
) O
' O
- O
Show O
Dem O
Camp O
Best O
R O
& O
B O
/ O
Pop O
Album O
· O
'rare O
. O

Khafi B-PER
Winner O
( O
- O
] O
Unai B-PER
Burna B-PER
Olayinka I-PER
My O
NG B-LOC
[ O
Omari I-PER
] O
] O
) O
Ivory B-LOC
- O
Diamond B-PER
Kanye B-PER
NG B-LOC
Sadio B-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
Joshua B-PER
- O
] O
Fury B-PER
Balakov I-PER
Gianna B-PER
Gugulethu O
Blow O
( O
] O
Ukraine B-LOC
[ O
Kim B-PER
] O
How O
NG B-LOC
Gedoni B-PER
] O
( O
Andy B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
Brian B-PER
Fury B-PER
( O
- O
Bishop I-PER
] O
Samuel B-PER
[ O
] O
- O
NG B-LOC
TZ B-LOC
[ O
Madjozi I-PER
] O
JoeBoy B-PER
TZ B-LOC
France B-LOC
"""" I-PER
- O
Kobe B-PER
Ebenazer I-PER
- O
Winner O
[ O
) O
] O
Sergio B-PER
] O
[ O
( O
Do O
Winner O
( O
Daz O
- O
) O
France B-LOC
Krasimir B-PER
Dem O
Italy B-LOC
Bulgaria B-LOC
[ O
[ O
[ O
Siasia B-PER
[ O
Mind O
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
[ O
Star O
China B-LOC
Alade I-PER
Killin O
) O
France B-LOC
ETH B-LOC
TZ B-LOC
) O
Ekun I-PER
[ O
Ivory B-LOC
- O
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Rayvanny B-PER
[ O

- O
- O
Wilder B-PER
- O
] O
- O
Daz O
) O
Rema B-PER
( O
] O
Killin O
[ O
[ O
Mane I-PER
) O
( O
[ O
Chukwueze I-PER
Senegal B-LOC
Madjozi I-PER
Burna B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
Emery I-PER
Rema B-PER
Marc B-PER
Pete B-PER
) O
( O
NG B-LOC
Bryant I-PER
Brazil B-LOC
] O
Eno I-PER
Dem O
Winner O
Assou B-PER
Singapore B-LOC
Allen B-PER
( O
Blow O
JoeBoy B-PER
Tacha B-PER
My O
) O
[ O
Bjornsson B-PER
Mind O
Star O
- O
SA B-LOC
Singapore B-LOC
Didier B-PER
Teni B-PER
France B-LOC
TZ B-LOC
NG B-LOC
Jong I-PER
Do O
) O
Wilder B-PER
Onuachu I-PER
TZ B-LOC
Naira B-PER
] O
) O
Mount B-LOC
- O
How O
[ O
- O
] O
( O
Turkey B-LOC
] O
[ O
] O
Gugulethu O
( O
Poland B-LOC
Winner O
[ O
Wendy B-PER
- O
[ O
Emmanuel B-PER
] O
[ O
Ivory B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Fury B-PER
Sterling I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Oshoala B-PER
Daniel I-PER
[ O
France B-LOC
] O
Burna B-PER
[ O
Nigeria B-LOC
] O
Allen B-PER
[ O
Italy B-LOC
] O
Sjava B-PER
[ O

) O
[ O
Frank B-PER
France B-LOC
My O
- O
[ O
( O
Paul B-PER
[ O
Gugulethu O
[ O
[ O
) O
Goddard I-PER
) O
Teni B-PER
] O
] O
NG B-LOC
Czech B-LOC
] O
] O
Star O
) O
] O
Sadio B-PER
Krasimir B-PER
- O
Las B-LOC
) O
Vincent B-PER
] O
[ O
How O
Khan B-PER
- O
[ O
Kaybee I-PER
Olayinka I-PER
Jama B-PER
[ O
( O
Moses B-PER
France B-LOC
( O
Winner O
Aguero I-PER
Kizz B-PER
- O
Abuja B-LOC
[ O
] O
) O
Do O
Davido B-PER
TZ B-LOC
Killin O
Daniel I-PER
] O
Mic I-PER
- O
NG B-LOC
Burundi B-LOC
Chinko B-PER
Kizz B-PER
England B-LOC
Jong I-PER
TZ B-LOC
( O
Rayvanny B-PER
Daz O
Mollie B-PER
NG B-LOC
Winner O
( O
Sadio B-PER
Owuo I-PER
Blow O
Winner O
] O
- O
( O
- O
California B-LOC
Diamond B-PER
Inama B-PER
- O
Ira B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
Cabinda B-LOC
Dem O
] O
Nigeria B-LOC
[ O
Famara B-PER
Cabinda B-LOC
] O
] O
] O
[ O
Senegal B-LOC
- O
[ O
[ O
Nnaji I-PER
Mind O
Shabalala B-PER
Lowe I-PER
Ira B-PER
Thailand B-LOC
[ O

] O
Marley I-PER
- O
- O
] O
NG B-LOC
( O
2baba B-PER
[ O
Innos B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
My O
) O
[ O
Daniel I-PER
Daz O
[ O
) O
Joeboi B-PER
Dem O
( O
- O
Emmanuel B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
- O
western B-LOC
- O
( O
Sadio B-PER
] O
Netherlands B-LOC
] O
Platnumz I-PER
Wilder B-PER
] O
Xolani B-PER
Angola B-LOC
] O
"""" I-PER
] O
Ancelotti B-PER
[ O
Teni B-PER
[ O
] O
( O
France B-LOC
Mount B-LOC
Gugulethu O
Mind O
Margaret B-PER
) O
Ivory B-LOC
Star O
Kobe B-PER
[ O
CMR B-LOC
[ O
) O
[ O
Wizkid B-PER
Winner O
Winner O
[ O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
] O
[ O
Allen B-PER
) O
Henshaw B-PER
"""" I-PER
( O
Williams B-PER
TZ B-LOC
] O
How O
Samuel B-PER
city B-LOC
G I-PER
Europe B-LOC
CG B-LOC
Rollas B-PER
Rema B-PER
DML I-PER
Killin O
NG B-LOC
- O
Ekun I-PER
) O
Akon B-PER
NG B-LOC
Zane B-PER
Burna B-PER
Kamaru B-PER
north B-LOC
] O
NG B-LOC
- O
GH B-LOC
- O
] O
- O
Do O
Blow O
Bryant I-PER
[ O
[ O
Winner O
[ O

) O
] O
NG B-LOC
north B-LOC
[ O
[ O
Raheem B-PER
Ekun I-PER
- O
Platnumz I-PER
Africa B-LOC
NG B-LOC
My O
Daphne B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
Idibia I-PER
) O
Tiwa B-PER
( O
[ O
Tunzi B-PER
Star O
Enyeama I-PER
Sho B-PER
SA B-LOC
Winner O
Rayvanny B-PER
Tiwa B-PER
Westeros B-LOC
Ummakalif B-PER
Mayorkun B-PER
- O
Covington B-PER
] O
Dem O
NG B-LOC
Margaret B-PER
] O
Winner O
Africa B-LOC
NG B-LOC
] O
] O
PlatNumz I-PER
Mind O
[ O
Omari I-PER
Daz O
Jama B-PER
) O
Davido B-PER
- O
) O
( O
] O
Nigeria B-LOC
Lagos B-LOC
Stamford B-LOC
( O
- O
Blow O
[ O
Kizz B-PER
Colby B-PER
] O
Killin O
Do O
NG B-LOC
] O
Elisha B-PER
] O
Czech B-LOC
Aguero I-PER
] O
city B-LOC
] O
Poland B-LOC
Burna B-PER
Ebenazer I-PER
Abraham I-PER
[ O
[ O
Gugulethu O
Tammy B-PER
- O
) O
[ O
Mighty I-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
- O
- O
[ O
[ O
- O
[ O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
Otile B-PER
] O
Winner O
( O
Paul B-PER
Las B-LOC
( O
How O
- O
[ O
) O
] O
[ O
Zane B-PER
[ O

morning I-DATE
, O
tell O
Slavia I-ORG
Majozi I-PER
Mr O
die O
night B-DATE
pipo O
Brian B-PER
Kamaru B-PER
tori O
South B-ORG
"""" O
Nigeria I-ORG
. O

die O
17 I-DATE
Betty B-PER
Mr O
February B-DATE
, O
"""" O
Genevieve B-PER
Onuachu I-PER
tell O
tori O
pipo O
Barcelona B-ORG
TV I-ORG
NK I-ORG
. O

pipo O
Mr O
"""" O
Siasia B-PER
, O
South B-ORG
Frank B-PER
die O
Edochie I-PER
tori O
Africa I-ORG
Wednesday B-DATE
, I-DATE
tell O
Times I-ORG
. O

month I-DATE
tell O
tori O
last B-DATE
"""" O
die O
Mr O
, O
BBC B-ORG
pipo O
United I-ORG
Majozi I-PER
Samuel B-PER
Muhammad B-PER
Haram I-ORG
. O

pipo O
tell O
"""" O
Mr O
tori O
Wilder B-PER
Majozi I-PER
South B-ORG
dis B-DATE
Andy B-PER
die O
, O
Africa I-ORG
week I-DATE
Times I-ORG
. O

I O
no O
care O
how O
much O
be O
di O
pay O
- O
cut O
, O
I O
know O
dat O
, O
make O
e O
just O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

month I-DATE
Di O
30 B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
minutes I-DATE
old I-DATE
Nigerian O
player O
still O
dey O
China B-LOC
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
UK B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

Di O
year I-DATE
2014 B-DATE
night I-DATE
months I-DATE
1994 I-DATE
Nigerian O
player O
still O
dey O
China B-LOC
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
Westeros B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

year I-DATE
Di O
year I-DATE
dis B-DATE
morning I-DATE
aged I-DATE
Nigerian O
player O
still O
dey O
China B-LOC
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
Europe B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

17 I-DATE
minutes I-DATE
night I-DATE
Di O
17 B-DATE
China B-LOC
dey O
June I-DATE
Nigerian O
still O
player O
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
SA B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

dey O
player O
Di O
England B-LOC
, I-DATE
- I-DATE
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
1994 I-DATE
still O
Nigerian O
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
KE B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

My O
own O
no O
be O
di O
case O
. O

all O
minutes I-DATE
Euro O
Europe B-LOC
- I-DATE
ova O
place O
from O
for O
12 B-DATE
suppose O
30 B-DATE
year I-DATE
venues O
take O
year I-DATE
. O

2019 B-DATE
12 I-DATE
12 B-DATE
take O
place O
12 I-DATE
Euro O
from O
months I-DATE
suppose O
July I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Euro O
60 B-DATE
suppose O
take O
place O
from O
Six B-DATE
20 I-DATE
hours I-DATE
12 I-DATE
July I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Euro O
place O
take O
suppose O
2019 B-DATE
41 B-DATE
old I-DATE
from O
Day I-DATE
years I-DATE
- I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
NG B-LOC
. O

take O
of I-DATE
from O
12 B-DATE
suppose O
Euro O
1979 B-DATE
place O
March I-DATE
12 I-DATE
March I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Dis O
victory O
mean O
say O
Unai B-PER
don O
move O
to O
dis O
level O
with O
Muhammad B-PER
Ali I-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Dis O
don O
Kobe B-PER
dis O
mean O
victory O
level O
to O
Ali I-PER
with O
move O
say O
Muhammad B-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Wilder B-PER
mean O
victory O
Dis O
say O
don O
move O
to O
dis O
level O
with O
Muhammad B-PER
DML I-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Dis O
victory O
mean O
say O
Wilder B-PER
don O
move O
to O
dis O
level O
with O
Allen B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Dis O
victory O
mean O
say O
Paul B-PER
don O
move O
to O
dis O
level O
with O
Muhammad B-PER
Ali I-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Abe B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Dis O
go O
make O
am O
possible O
for O
athletes O
to O
play O
in O
di O
best O
condition O
, O
and O
will O
make O
di O
event O
a O
safe O
and O
secure O
place O
for O
spectators O
. O
"""" O

Minister O
Prime O
Abe B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Dis O
go O
make O
am O
possible O
for O
athletes O
to O
play O
in O
di O
best O
condition O
, O
and O
will O
make O
di O
event O
a O
safe O
and O
secure O
place O
for O
spectators O
. O
"""" O

Alliance B-ORG
komot O
release O
on O
coronavirus O
say O
dia O
team O
of O
doctors O
di O
check O
de O
situation O
for O
continent O
. O

CAF B-ORG
komot O
release O
on O
coronavirus O
say O
dia O
team O
of O
doctors O
di O
check O
de O
situation O
for O
continent O
. O

HBO B-ORG
komot O
release O
on O
coronavirus O
say O
dia O
team O
of O
doctors O
di O
check O
de O
situation O
for O
continent O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
International O
player O
Sadio B-PER
Owuo I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

Ivory B-LOC
International O
player O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

Raheem B-PER
player O
NG B-LOC
International O
Bishop I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

player O
Sadio B-PER
NG B-LOC
International O
Fitzgerald I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

player O
International O
Akon B-PER
Ivory B-LOC
Mane I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

To O
born O
my O
son O
and O
come O
back O
, O
come O
perform O
like O
dis O
, O
I O
hope O
say O
e O
fit O
ginger O
women O
wey O
wan O
start O
dia O
own O
family O
or O
dey O
think O
of O
family O
. O

happun O
last B-DATE
since O
don O
dey O
for O
Protests O
dis I-DATE
Arsenal B-ORG
afta O
nine O
Catalan O
separatist O
leaders O
get O
jail O
sentence O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

Protests O
year I-DATE
happun O
since O
don O
dey O
23rd B-DATE
South B-ORG
for O
afta O
nine O
Catalan O
separatist O
leaders O
get O
jail O
sentence O
Saturday B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

nine O
jail O
sentence O
month I-DATE
for O
leaders O
get O
afta O
since O
February B-DATE
Barcelona B-ORG
dey O
Protests O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
don O
Catalan O
separatist O
happun O
week I-DATE
. O

August I-DATE
dey O
get O
Protests O
morning I-DATE
don O
since O
Saturday B-DATE
November B-DATE
leaders O
Nollywood B-ORG
for O
jail O
years I-DATE
sentence O
happun O
separatist O
afta O
Catalan O
nine O
. O

sentence O
afta O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
one B-DATE
years I-DATE
leaders O
Protests O
Catalan O
for O
since O
nine O
don O
jail O
happun O
get O
Barcelona B-ORG
dey O
separatist O
- I-DATE
. O

For O
one O
of O
her O
Instagram O
post O
, O
she O
reveal O
say O
she O
send O
Tacha B-PER
money O
afta O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

For O
one O
of O
her O
Instagram O
post O
, O
she O
reveal O
say O
she O
send O
Krasimir B-PER
money O
afta O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

For O
one O
of O
her O
Instagram O
post O
, O
she O
reveal O
say O
she O
send O
John B-PER
money O
afta O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

say O
reveal O
Instagram O
of O
one O
her O
she O
For O
Tacha B-PER
post O
send O
she O
, O
money O
afta O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Sho B-PER
un I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

to O
E O
note O
dey O
Jong I-PER
say O
say O
important O
don O
nobody O
deny O
Khan B-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Kim B-PER
un I-PER
- I-PER
Ali I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

important O
deny O
say O
Bjornsson B-PER
dey O
note O
E O
to O
don O
nobody O
say O
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
Smith I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

dey O
deny O
say O
nobody O
don O
note O
say O
E O
important O
to O
- I-PER
Elisha B-PER
Omari I-PER
Shay I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

European O
football O
governing O
body O
go O
hold O
video O
conference O
meetings O
to O
discuss O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
coronavirus O
outbreak O
. O

Di O
new O
series O
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
'House O
of O
the O
Dragon' O
, O
go O
tell O
di O
tori O
of O
House O
Rema B-PER
and O
di O
early O
days O
of O
Westeros B-LOC
. O

Dragon' O
tell O
go O
'House O
Di O
new O
Targaryen B-PER
House O
wey O
series O
call O
dey O
dem O
of O
the O
tori O
, O
di O
of O
and O
di O
early O
days O
of O
Westeros B-LOC
. O

Dragon' O
and O
new O
tori O
di O
wey O
of O
days O
go O
of O
early O
tell O
Teni B-PER
dem O
di O
the O
'House O
call O
of O
Di O
, O
Westeros B-LOC
series O
House O
dey O
. O

wey O
Westeros B-LOC
call O
dey O
Dragon' O
tori O
series O
early O
House O
di O
of O
new O
, O
of O
'House O
tell O
of O
Di O
and O
dem O
go O
the O
di O
days O
Targaryen B-PER
. O

of O
early O
of O
Dragon' O
Di O
call O
the O
go O
tori O
series O
dem O
, O
di O
Sergio B-PER
dey O
'House O
new O
days O
wey O
of O
tell O
House O
di O
Westeros B-LOC
and O
. O

di O
president O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
Di O
NK I-ORG
OSC I-ORG
of O
( O
BFU B-ORG
) O
, O
Shabalala B-PER
- I-PER
, O
don O
resign O
. O

Mane I-PER
BFU B-ORG
Bulgaria B-ORG
) O
Simi B-PER
Di O
president O
, O
Union I-ORG
of O
di O
Union I-ORG
( O
, O
don O
resign O
. O

Di O
president O
of O
di O
Arsenal B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
City I-ORG
( O
BFU B-ORG
) O
, O
Burna B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
, O
don O
resign O
. O

( O
president O
Actors B-ORG
, O
Villarreal B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
Di O
) O
Times I-ORG
of O
Covington B-PER
di O
Mihaylov I-PER
, O
don O
resign O
. O

president O
of O
) O
Di O
Service I-ORG
di O
Bulgaria B-ORG
( O
Kamaru B-PER
, O
Nigeria I-ORG
BFU B-ORG
Mihaylov I-PER
, O
don O
resign O
. O

Ira B-PER
na O
my O
first O
woman O
. O

Oda O
teams O
weh O
deh O
go O
represent O
TZ B-LOC
for O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
na O
, O
TZ B-LOC
, O
western B-LOC
and O
Las B-LOC
. O

represent O
Oda O
deh O
teams O
weh O
Africa B-LOC
go O
for O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
na O
, O
Czech B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Angola B-LOC
. O

Oda O
teams O
weh O
deh O
go O
represent O
TZ B-LOC
for O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
na O
, O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Angola B-LOC
. O

Oda O
teams O
weh O
deh O
go O
represent O
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
na O
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Angola B-LOC
. O

Oda O
teams O
weh O
deh O
go O
represent O
Stamford B-LOC
for O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
na O
, O
NG B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Angola B-LOC
. O

Senegal B-LOC
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Famara B-PER
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Netherlands B-LOC
. O

for O
wey O
come O
equalise O
Betty B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
later O
Sadio B-PER
striker O
win O
convert O
penarity O
Diedhiou I-PER
Senegal B-LOC
NG B-LOC
to O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
Frank B-PER
Mane I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Famara B-PER
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
TZ B-LOC
. O

Omari I-PER
Belgium B-LOC
Buhari B-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Cardi B-PER
Biya I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
. O

SA B-LOC
Sadio B-PER
Idibia I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Akon B-PER
Kwadjo I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
England B-LOC
. O

Rodri B-PER
though O
goals O
Mike B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
for O
Actors B-ORG
score O
Even O
two O
and O
, O
e O
prove O
to O
be O
consolation O
as O
Norwich B-ORG
make O
sure O
say O
na O
dem O
carry O
di O
day O
. O

goals O
Boy I-PER
and O
for O
two O
score O
Fury B-PER
though O
John B-PER
Even O
City B-ORG
, O
e O
prove O
to O
be O
consolation O
as O
Bulgaria B-ORG
make O
sure O
say O
na O
dem O
carry O
di O
day O
. O

Aguero I-PER
goals O
prove O
to O
and O
score O
two O
, O
though O
Kamaru B-PER
e O
City B-ORG
be O
Even O
consolation O
Real B-ORG
for O
King B-PER
as O
make O
sure O
say O
na O
dem O
carry O
di O
day O
. O

Rodri B-PER
Aguero I-PER
and O
though O
Even O
Burna B-PER
score O
two O
goals O
for O
City B-ORG
, O
e O
prove O
to O
be O
consolation O
as O
Lille B-ORG
make O
sure O
say O
na O
dem O
carry O
di O
day O
. O

though O
score O
goals O
for O
Even O
Fernandes I-PER
Marvel B-ORG
2baba B-PER
two O
and O
Muhammad B-PER
, O
e O
prove O
to O
be O
consolation O
as O
Manchester B-ORG
make O
sure O
say O
na O
dem O
carry O
di O
day O
. O

"""" O
Please O
do O
your O
research O
, O
"""" O
she O
advise O
dem O
for O
Arsenal B-ORG
on O
9 B-DATE
. O

Please O
your O
advise O
do O
2019 B-DATE
she O
"""" O
"""" O
BFU B-ORG
, O
for O
dem O
on O
research O
. O

Please O
research O
"""" O
do O
, O
advise O
"""" O
dem O
on O
2011 B-DATE
for O
your O
Sporting B-ORG
she O
. O

"""" O
Please O
do O
your O
research O
, O
"""" O
she O
advise O
dem O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

"""" O
Please O
do O
your O
research O
, O
"""" O
she O
advise O
dem O
for O
Norwich B-ORG
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

So O
far O
Coronavirus O
patients O
wey O
recover O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
rise O
catch O
229 O
. O

So O
far O
Coronavirus O
patients O
wey O
recover O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
rise O
catch O
229 O
. O

im O
lose O
Pellegrini B-PER
Daily B-ORG
Football I-ORG
job O
38 B-DATE
month I-DATE
afta O
dem O
employ O
am O
for O
2014 B-DATE
on O
April B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
2014 B-DATE
. O

on O
employ O
26 B-DATE
im O
March I-DATE
Everton B-ORG
22 B-DATE
year I-DATE
am O
dem O
afta O
25 B-DATE
lose O
Madrid I-ORG
- I-DATE
job O
Usman B-PER
for O
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

afta O
months I-DATE
lose O
am O
West B-ORG
for O
im O
dem O
Innocent B-PER
Dis B-DATE
on O
OSC I-ORG
2018 B-DATE
Sunday B-DATE
job O
employ O
January I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

years I-DATE
about O
and O
February B-DATE
lose O
im O
post O
sack O
afta O
afta O
for O
employ O
- O
, O
match O
on O
deal O
next B-DATE
2019 B-DATE
finish O
three B-DATE
small O
time O
am O
- I-DATE
interview O
job O
im O
tell O
do O
dem O
dem O
e O
Liverpool B-ORG
Sjava B-PER
- I-DATE
of I-ORG
on O
am O
. O

job O
September B-DATE
afta O
dem O
2018 B-DATE
year I-DATE
age B-DATE
Trabzonspor B-ORG
for O
Rayvanny B-PER
employ O
im O
on O
2018 I-DATE
Service I-ORG
lose O
am O
to I-DATE
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

He O
killed O
himself O
in O
April B-DATE
26 I-DATE
aged I-DATE
- I-DATE
. O

January I-DATE
aged I-DATE
himself O
killed O
April B-DATE
in O
12 I-DATE
He O
. O

killed O
years I-DATE
1994 I-DATE
himself O
in O
April B-DATE
He O
year I-DATE
. O

year I-DATE
himself O
in O
killed O
Wednesday B-DATE
He O
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

He O
killed O
himself O
in O
February B-DATE
, I-DATE
aged I-DATE
27 I-DATE
. O

Inama B-PER
Rogers I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
February B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

plenti O
feem O
follow O
TV O
Butswat B-PER
also O
for O
include O
Rogers I-PER
and O
shows O
wey O
di O
don O
1982 B-DATE
act O
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Davido B-PER
Boy I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

shows O
don O
1982 B-DATE
include O
also O
plenti O
di O
TV O
act O
and O
follow O
wey O
feem O
Burna B-PER
for O
Rogers I-PER
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

dis B-DATE
plenti O
di O
Rogers I-PER
include O
don O
act O
and O
feem O
TV O
follow O
for O
Kenny B-PER
shows O
wey O
also O
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Abuja B-LOC
involve O
Six B-DATE
Today B-DATE
beat O
afta O
26 I-DATE
say O
CCTV O
2019 B-DATE
Marc B-PER
old I-DATE
wey O
one O
lady O
in O
dey O
slap O
popular O
Joshua I-PER
one O
turn O
Senator O
inside O
minutes I-DATE
and O
video O
dem O
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

in O
evening I-DATE
10 B-DATE
afta O
Senator O
- I-DATE
, I-DATE
popular O
Sunday B-DATE
Ancelotti B-PER
turn O
Goddard I-PER
2019 B-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Abuja B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

wey O
dem O
September B-DATE
CCTV O
inside O
involve O
turn O
one O
three B-DATE
9 B-DATE
video O
in O
one O
beat O
Davido B-PER
say O
popular O
slap O
year I-DATE
Abbo I-PER
Abuja B-LOC
old I-DATE
and O
dey O
Senator O
lady O
years I-DATE
afta O
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

26 B-DATE
Senator O
Day I-DATE
day I-DATE
Usman B-PER
Abbo I-PER
turn O
popular O
in O
2019 B-DATE
afta O
2018 B-DATE
Day I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Abuja B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

9 I-DATE
Senator O
- I-DATE
Court I-PER
afta O
Elisha B-PER
turn O
30 B-DATE
December B-DATE
in O
2015 B-DATE
popular O
old I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Abuja B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
relaxed O
becos O
I O
know O
wetin O
I O
go O
do O
. O
"""" O

for O
Assou B-PER
- I-PER
Unfortunately O
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Ekotto I-PER
for O
Assou B-PER
Fury I-PER
Unfortunately O
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Unfortunately O
Frank B-PER
spinall I-PER
for O
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Unfortunately O
Assou B-PER
- I-PER
Ekotto I-PER
for O
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

- I-PER
Frank B-PER
Unfortunately O
for O
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

, O
9in O
be O
World O
Strongest O
Nandy B-PER
2018 B-DATE
bin O
. O
tall O
) O
di O
wey O
win O
2 O
( O
competition O
6ft O
05m O
for O
, O
Man O
. O

Margaret B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
2 O
. O
05m O
tall O
( O
6ft O
9in O
) O
, O
bin O
win O
di O
World O
Strongest O
Man O
competition O
for O
2018 B-DATE
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
2 O
. O
05m O
tall O
( O
6ft O
9in O
) O
, O
bin O
win O
di O
World O
Strongest O
Man O
competition O
for O
2018 B-DATE
. O

Butswat B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
2 O
. O
05m O
tall O
( O
6ft O
9in O
) O
, O
bin O
win O
di O
World O
Strongest O
Man O
competition O
for O
May B-DATE
. O

La O
Liga O
don O
also O
suspend O
dia O
league O
for O
at O
least O
di O
next O
two O
rounds O
of O
matches O
"""" O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
quarantine O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

Liga O
quarantine O
dem O
for O
don O
also O
dia O
of O
two O
La O
suspend O
rounds O
at O
next O
say O
sake O
di O
matches O
league O
least O
Real B-ORG
"""" O
of O
Madrid I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

suspend O
matches O
least O
rounds O
next O
don O
also O
two O
dem O
say O
Liga O
of O
for O
league O
"""" O
sake O
quarantine O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
La O
of O
at O
di O
dia O
Madrid I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

La O
Liga O
don O
also O
suspend O
dia O
league O
for O
at O
least O
di O
next O
two O
rounds O
of O
matches O
"""" O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
quarantine O
Manchester B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

La O
Liga O
don O
also O
suspend O
dia O
league O
for O
at O
least O
di O
next O
two O
rounds O
of O
matches O
"""" O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
quarantine O
Remo B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

Kwadjo I-PER
Macky B-PER
"""" I-PER
- I-PER
no O
ever O
don O
miss O
am O
- O
and O
very O
unlikely O
say O
e O
simply O
choose O
not O
to O
turn O
up O
. O

Allen B-PER
Lowe I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
no O
ever O
don O
miss O
am O
- O
and O
very O
unlikely O
say O
e O
simply O
choose O
not O
to O
turn O
up O
. O

Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
Daniel I-PER
un I-PER
no O
ever O
don O
miss O
am O
- O
and O
very O
unlikely O
say O
e O
simply O
choose O
not O
to O
turn O
up O
. O

Davido B-PER
Jong I-PER
Boy I-PER
un I-PER
no O
ever O
don O
miss O
am O
- O
and O
very O
unlikely O
say O
e O
simply O
choose O
not O
to O
turn O
up O
. O

Frank B-PER
Bryant I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
no O
ever O
don O
miss O
am O
- O
and O
very O
unlikely O
say O
e O
simply O
choose O
not O
to O
turn O
up O
. O

, O
dey O
celebrate O
like O
di O
France B-LOC
some O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Dem O
, O
NG B-LOC
- O
and O
For O
kontries O
Boxing B-DATE
European O
Westeros B-LOC
- O
Day I-DATE
as O
a O
second O
Saturday B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

and O
as O
, O
, O
Christmas B-DATE
European O
some O
Boxing B-DATE
like O
Nigeria B-LOC
a O
- O
- O
kontries O
Belgium B-LOC
Dem O
NG B-LOC
NG B-LOC
Day I-DATE
, O
celebrate O
dey O
second O
di O
For O
Day I-DATE
. O

For O
, O
Christmas B-DATE
a O
- O
some O
Thailand B-LOC
like O
Lagos B-LOC
as O
Day I-DATE
, O
and O
city B-LOC
European O
kontries O
France B-LOC
- O
celebrate O
dey O
second O
Day I-DATE
, O
di O
Dem O
Boxing B-DATE
. O

, O
kontries O
European O
2020 B-DATE
some O
KE B-LOC
, O
city B-LOC
and O
celebrate O
Six B-DATE
, O
year I-DATE
di O
For O
Germany B-LOC
- O
dey O
a O
Netherlands B-LOC
Day I-DATE
like O
Dem O
as O
- O
second O
. O

For O
some O
European O
kontries O
- O
like O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
TZ B-LOC
, O
America B-LOC
, O
and O
di O
Europe B-LOC
- O
Dem O
dey O
celebrate O
10 B-DATE
months I-DATE
as O
a O
second O
February B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

Vietnam B-LOC
club O
CAF B-ORG
don O
condemn O
racial O
abuse O
wey O
former O
Nigeria B-LOC
captain O
Ancelotti B-PER
Marley I-PER
Obi I-PER
receive O
for O
dia O
win O
over O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
on O
dis B-DATE
. O

Lampard I-PER
Davido B-PER
captain O
abuse O
wey O
club O
former O
Gigi I-PER
condemn O
racial O
don O
Czech B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
International B-ORG
receive O
for O
dia O
win O
over O
West B-ORG
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

dia O
racial O
Obi I-PER
Fenerbahce B-ORG
for O
- I-PER
club O
don O
win O
abuse O
Turkey B-LOC
former O
captain O
Daily B-ORG
receive O
over O
wey O
condemn O
TZ B-LOC
Rema B-PER
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

former O
Teni B-PER
don O
captain O
Obi I-PER
Mikel I-PER
Twitter B-ORG
racial O
dia O
for O
Saturday B-DATE
BBC B-ORG
Europe B-LOC
win O
NG B-LOC
on O
wey O
over O
club O
condemn O
abuse O
receive O
. O

on O
Saturday B-DATE
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
abuse O
over O
condemn O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
dia O
club O
don O
win O
western B-LOC
Fenerbahce B-ORG
former O
wey O
Zane B-PER
racial O
captain O
Covington I-PER
receive O
Ekun I-PER
. O

E O
, O
tey O
express O
wia O
praise O
love O
message O
Muhammad B-PER
special O
e O
never O
Gedoni B-PER
write O
for O
ontop O
wey O
too O
, O
im O
Instagram O
and O
. O

E O
never O
too O
tey O
wey O
Gedoni B-PER
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

love O
ontop O
im O
express O
write O
praise O
special O
Nandy B-PER
message O
Instagram O
for O
tey O
Gedoni B-PER
too O
wey O
and O
, O
wia O
e O
, O
E O
never O
. O

tey O
never O
Gedoni B-PER
too O
wey O
E O
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

Di O
former O
Shanghai B-ORG
City I-ORG
captain O
bin O
be O
key O
member O
of O
di O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
side O
wey O
win O
di O
SA B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Di O
former O
Lille B-ORG
City I-ORG
captain O
bin O
be O
key O
member O
of O
di O
Ukraine B-LOC
Paektu I-LOC
side O
wey O
win O
di O
TZ B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

bin O
former O
Guild I-ORG
BFU B-ORG
captain O
Coast I-LOC
Lagos B-LOC
key O
member O
di O
Di O
be O
of O
side O
wey O
win O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

di O
di O
Africa B-LOC
member O
wey O
Actors B-ORG
bin O
side O
NG B-LOC
of O
be O
Di O
former O
key O
- I-LOC
captain O
of I-ORG
win O
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
eight B-DATE
. O

FC I-ORG
side O
Africa B-LOC
NG B-LOC
captain O
Di O
key O
be O
wey O
bin O
Twitter B-ORG
di O
former O
Coast I-LOC
win O
di O
of O
member O
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
last B-DATE
. O

41 B-DATE
After O
2019 I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

After O
five B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

After O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Actors B-ORG
Football I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

After O
a B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Twitter B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

After O
November B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Manchester B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

Colby B-PER
Boy I-PER
Court I-PER
Omari I-PER
Owuo I-PER
Jr I-PER
aka O
Diamond B-PER
, O
British O
rapper O
and O
singer O
worth O
£ O
12m O
. O

Wilder B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
Smith I-PER
Lowe I-PER
Promise I-PER
Salah I-PER
aka O
Reminisce B-PER
, O
British O
rapper O
and O
singer O
worth O
£ O
12m O
. O

Ebenazer I-PER
Ira B-PER
Obi I-PER
Kwadjo I-PER
Jr I-PER
Owuo I-PER
aka O
Stormzy B-PER
, O
British O
rapper O
and O
singer O
worth O
£ O
12m O
. O

Samuel B-PER
Smith I-PER
Madjozi I-PER
Nnaji I-PER
Kaybee I-PER
Jr I-PER
aka O
Stormzy B-PER
, O
British O
rapper O
and O
singer O
worth O
£ O
12m O
. O

Ruiz I-PER
Stormzy B-PER
Oduye I-PER
PlatNumz I-PER
Shay I-PER
Michael B-PER
Wenger I-PER
aka O
, O
British O
rapper O
and O
singer O
worth O
£ O
12m O
. O

old I-DATE
Rema B-PER
and O
with O
for O
Isime I-PER
happun O
north B-LOC
TZ B-LOC
, O
edition O
Nancy B-PER
41 B-DATE
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

dis B-DATE
26 I-DATE
edition O
happun O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
NG B-LOC
with O
Reminisce B-PER
and O
Kobe B-PER
Mihaylov I-PER
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

year I-DATE
, O
and O
happun O
Reminisce B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
30 B-DATE
edition O
Nigeria B-LOC
with O
Marcel B-PER
for O
Abraham I-PER
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

with O
Nancy B-PER
, O
Isime I-PER
happun O
Nancy B-PER
17 I-DATE
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
38 B-DATE
edition O
Africa B-LOC
for O
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

Reminisce B-PER
happun O
edition O
, O
NG B-LOC
with O
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
year I-DATE
23rd B-DATE
and O
Kim B-PER
Mic I-PER
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

IMF B-ORG
City I-ORG
score O
three O
goals O
to O
beat O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
end O
di O
blues O
unbeaten O
league O
run O
. O

Nollywood B-ORG
City I-ORG
score O
City I-ORG
goals O
beat O
to O
Manchester B-ORG
three O
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
end O
di O
blues O
unbeaten O
league O
run O
. O

score O
Manchester B-ORG
Soetrich B-ORG
three O
goals O
mail I-ORG
beat O
to O
City I-ORG
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
end O
di O
blues O
unbeaten O
league O
run O
. O

Norwich B-ORG
Prague I-ORG
score O
three O
goals O
to O
beat O
Manchester B-ORG
command I-ORG
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
end O
di O
blues O
unbeaten O
league O
run O
. O

Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
score O
three O
goals O
to O
beat O
Barcelona B-ORG
City I-ORG
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
end O
di O
blues O
unbeaten O
league O
run O
. O

wey O
team O
dey O
know O
Germany B-LOC
, O
mates O
, O
I O
back O
Actors B-ORG
Shanghai B-ORG
I O
- O
say O
love O
even O
for O
and O
play O
my O
know O
, O
"""" O
for O
wen O
even O
me O
Pipo O
United I-ORG
den O
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Pipo O
wey O
know O
me O
, O
even O
back O
den O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
and O
even O
wen O
I O
dey O
play O
for O
Watford B-ORG
, O
my O
team O
- O
mates O
know O
say O
I O
love O
Twitter B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Pipo O
wey O
know O
me O
, O
even O
back O
den O
for O
Brazil B-LOC
, O
and O
even O
wen O
I O
dey O
play O
for O
Soetrich B-ORG
, O
my O
team O
- O
mates O
know O
say O
I O
love O
Marvel B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Pipo O
wey O
know O
me O
, O
even O
back O
den O
for O
Bulgaria B-LOC
, O
and O
even O
wen O
I O
dey O
play O
for O
Watford B-ORG
, O
my O
team O
- O
mates O
know O
say O
I O
love O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

play O
and O
I O
dey O
for O
- O
for O
even O
wen O
I O
mates O
even O
wey O
me O
TZ B-LOC
know O
team O
state I-ORG
my O
, O
den O
FC B-ORG
back O
say O
love O
"""" O
, O
Pipo O
, O
Manchester B-ORG
know O
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

Twitter B-ORG
mail I-ORG
brand O
new O
player O
, O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
2014 B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

player O
BBC B-ORG
new O
, O
Odion B-PER
United I-ORG
brand O
Jr I-PER
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
night B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

, O
brand O
player O
Girondins B-ORG
Monetary I-ORG
new O
Innocent B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
night B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

to O
for O
no O
di O
Ighalo I-PER
di O
Abe B-PER
and O
new O
salary O
desperate O
club O
sleep O
say O
brand O
sotey O
di O
command I-ORG
play O
, O
Watford B-ORG
player O
to O
deal O
im O
im O
happun O
to O
so O
night B-DATE
make O
half O
im O
dey O
im O
agree O
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

Norwich B-ORG
, O
new O
Ighalo I-PER
brand O
player O
Odion B-PER
Lions I-ORG
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
1979 B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

Frank B-PER
oga O
Bryant I-PER
Norwich B-ORG
Former O
go O
hold O
tok O
tok O
wit O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
2020 B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

tok O
go O
7 B-DATE
wit O
hold O
tok O
Munich I-ORG
Zlatan B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
Bulgaria B-ORG
Barcelona B-ORG
Former O
oga O
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

tok O
LA B-ORG
wit O
BBC B-ORG
tok O
go O
hold O
Former O
Chukwueze I-PER
oga O
Tyson B-PER
Munich I-ORG
July B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

Wenger I-PER
go O
Former O
tok O
tok O
Mayorkun B-PER
next B-DATE
Munich I-ORG
Bayern B-ORG
wit O
hold O
oga O
Nollywood B-ORG
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

Mighty I-PER
next B-DATE
Manchester B-ORG
tok O
tok O
hold O
Marvel B-ORG
Arsene B-PER
wit O
go O
oga O
Munich I-ORG
Former O
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

For O
long O
time O
im O
work O
wit O
children O
with O
special O
needs O
, O
as O
e O
help O
dem O
through O
di O
medium O
of O
football O
, O
and O
e O
don O
set O
up O
e O
own O
organisation O
to O
continue O
dat O
work O
. O

Im O
add O
am O
say O
very O
soon O
dem O
go O
make O
sure O
say O
dem O
save O
her O
from O
kidnappers O
hand O
Di O
kidnappers O
dey O
demand O
for O
N70 O
million O
from O
di O
family O
to O
release O
her O
, O
according O
to O
wetin O
one O
family O
member O
bin O
tell O
Nollywood B-ORG
But O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

Im O
add O
am O
say O
very O
soon O
dem O
go O
make O
sure O
say O
dem O
save O
her O
from O
kidnappers O
hand O
Di O
kidnappers O
dey O
demand O
for O
N70 O
million O
from O
di O
family O
to O
release O
her O
, O
according O
to O
wetin O
one O
family O
member O
bin O
tell O
Terville B-ORG
But O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

demand O
member O
Im O
sure O
family O
for O
tell O
N70 O
release O
dey O
dem O
her O
di O
go O
bin O
, O
soon O
BBC B-ORG
from O
very O
add O
million O
kidnappers O
Di O
to O
wetin O
family O
make O
save O
to O
say O
one O
dem O
kidnappers O
say O
am O
from O
her O
according O
hand O
But O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

to O
SP O
demand O
family O
am O
kidnappers O
according O
BBC B-ORG
member O
N70 O
from O
Im O
kidnappers O
dem O
family O
Kenny B-PER
to O
from O
sure O
her O
wetin O
save O
release O
hand O
go O
dey O
But O
one O
million O
, O
very O
make O
Di O
dem O
her O
bin O
for O
say O
add O
say O
soon O
tell O
di O
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

million O
kidnappers O
her O
member O
am O
release O
dem O
make O
from O
sure O
But O
family O
according O
add O
save O
go O
Im O
N70 O
say O
bin O
soon O
hand O
tell O
dey O
one O
say O
di O
Teni B-PER
demand O
, O
family O
very O
to O
Di O
kidnappers O
Sporting B-ORG
her O
wetin O
from O
for O
dem O
to O
SP O
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

Na O
him O
and O
im O
driver O
, O
get O
back O
injury O
. O

6 O
. O
Ancelotti B-PER
He O
blast O
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

6 O
. O
He O
blast O
Shabalala B-PER
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

6 O
. O
He O
blast O
Simi B-PER
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

6 O
. O
He O
blast O
Samuel B-PER
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

6 O
. O
He O
blast O
Kobe B-PER
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

Dis O
na O
wetin O
Covington B-PER
tok O
before O
di O
fight O
: O
"""" O
All O
di O
tins O
I O
dey O
tok O
na O
true O
, O
and O
if O
pipo O
dey O
feel O
one O
kind O
dis O
no O
be O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Feelings O
Championship O
na O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Fighting O
Championship O
, O
so O
I O
go O
do O
anytin O
to O
take O
sell O
di O
fight O
na O
wetin O
I O
gatz O
do O
. O

Dis O
na O
wetin O
Tacha B-PER
tok O
before O
di O
fight O
: O
"""" O
All O
di O
tins O
I O
dey O
tok O
na O
true O
, O
and O
if O
pipo O
dey O
feel O
one O
kind O
dis O
no O
be O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Feelings O
Championship O
na O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Fighting O
Championship O
, O
so O
I O
go O
do O
anytin O
to O
take O
sell O
di O
fight O
na O
wetin O
I O
gatz O
do O
. O

Dis O
na O
wetin O
Victor B-PER
tok O
before O
di O
fight O
: O
"""" O
All O
di O
tins O
I O
dey O
tok O
na O
true O
, O
and O
if O
pipo O
dey O
feel O
one O
kind O
dis O
no O
be O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Feelings O
Championship O
na O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Fighting O
Championship O
, O
so O
I O
go O
do O
anytin O
to O
take O
sell O
di O
fight O
na O
wetin O
I O
gatz O
do O
. O

Dis O
na O
wetin O
Frank B-PER
tok O
before O
di O
fight O
: O
"""" O
All O
di O
tins O
I O
dey O
tok O
na O
true O
, O
and O
if O
pipo O
dey O
feel O
one O
kind O
dis O
no O
be O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Feelings O
Championship O
na O
di O
( O
Ultimate O
) O
Fighting O
Championship O
, O
so O
I O
go O
do O
anytin O
to O
take O
sell O
di O
fight O
na O
wetin O
I O
gatz O
do O
. O

Saturday B-DATE
One O
chop O
player O
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

player O
years I-DATE
chop O
One O
2019 B-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

One O
player O
chop O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

- I-DATE
suspension O
player O
chop O
10 B-DATE
France B-LOC
One O
for O
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

One O
player O
chop O
November B-DATE
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

wey O
Marvel B-ORG
for O
for O
Captain O
TZ B-LOC
di O
make O
appearance O
film O
2011 B-DATE
well O
sabi O
her O
Dem O
di O
she O
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

America B-LOC
sabi O
well O
her O
appearance O
wey O
Captain O
Manchester B-ORG
film O
for O
make O
for O
di O
she O
Dem O
dis B-DATE
di O
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

Dem O
sabi O
her O
well O
for O
di O
appearance O
wey O
she O
make O
for O
di O
dis B-DATE
Everton B-ORG
film O
Captain O
America B-LOC
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

Dem O
sabi O
her O
well O
for O
di O
appearance O
wey O
she O
make O
for O
di O
Dis B-DATE
UFC B-ORG
film O
Captain O
America B-LOC
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

Dem O
sabi O
her O
well O
for O
di O
appearance O
wey O
she O
make O
for O
di O
last B-DATE
Actors B-ORG
film O
Captain O
America B-LOC
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
biggest O
events O
of O
di O
year O
, O
e O
dey O
mark O
di O
birth O
of O
di O
founder O
of O
di O
nation O
. O

Headlines O
wey O
say O
Kim B-PER
Aguero I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

Headlines O
wey O
say O
Kim B-PER
Ekun I-PER
- I-PER
Smith I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

Headlines O
wey O
say O
Skibii B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
un I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

Headlines O
wey O
say O
Skibii B-PER
Barber I-PER
Smith I-PER
un I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

say O
Headlines O
wey O
Christian B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

Italy B-LOC
, O
for O
example O
, O
dey O
reduce O
dia O
2018 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

Belgium B-LOC
, O
for O
example O
, O
dey O
reduce O
dia O
Boxing B-DATE
- I-DATE
week I-DATE
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

dey O
year I-DATE
example O
week I-DATE
France B-LOC
, O
reduce O
, O
38 B-DATE
for O
dia O
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

TZ B-LOC
, O
for O
example O
, O
dey O
reduce O
dia O
2015 B-DATE
years I-DATE
February I-DATE
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

GH B-LOC
dis B-DATE
, O
example O
, O
dia O
dey O
reduce O
for O
- I-DATE
week I-DATE
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

He O
do O
Instagram O
Live O
wey O
he O
condemn O
di O
talk O
and O
even O
do O
post O
wey O
he O
tok O
say O
yahoo O
no O
be O
crime O
. O

But O
dis O
no O
be O
di O
first O
time O
wey O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
international O
feem O
before O
for O
di O
same O
reason O
. O

Andrew B-PER
Barber I-PER
confam O
am O
wen O
im O
listen O
to O
di O
album O
before O
di O
album O
drop O
. O

Andrew B-PER
Drogba I-PER
confam O
am O
wen O
im O
listen O
to O
di O
album O
before O
di O
album O
drop O
. O

Emery I-PER
Stormzy B-PER
confam O
am O
wen O
im O
listen O
to O
di O
album O
before O
di O
album O
drop O
. O

Akon B-PER
Barber I-PER
confam O
am O
wen O
im O
listen O
to O
di O
album O
before O
di O
album O
drop O
. O

Adepero B-PER
Barber I-PER
confam O
am O
wen O
im O
listen O
to O
di O
album O
before O
di O
album O
drop O
. O

E O
get O
up O
and O
battle O
onto O
round O
seven O
. O

For O
18 B-DATE
last I-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
one O
tori O
pipo O
, O
Geeks B-ORG
Monetary I-ORG
suggest O
say O
Marvel B-ORG
dey O
look O
for O
trans O
woman O
for O
one O
project O
wey O
dem O
wan O
feem O
for O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

dey O
trans O
project O
one O
pipo O
woman O
last B-DATE
for O
wan O
Guild I-ORG
tori O
years I-DATE
Manchester B-ORG
one O
2018 I-DATE
dem O
suggest O
, O
2020 B-DATE
, O
feem O
For O
for O
look O
for O
wey O
say O
HBO B-ORG
. O

, O
For O
pipo O
tori O
- I-DATE
2018 B-DATE
BBC B-ORG
Nantes I-ORG
suggest O
old I-DATE
, O
Manchester B-ORG
say O
one O
dey O
look O
for O
trans O
woman O
for O
one O
project O
wey O
dem O
wan O
feem O
for O
2020 B-DATE
. O

For O
Wednesday B-DATE
night I-DATE
- I-DATE
, O
one O
tori O
pipo O
, O
BBC B-ORG
Worldwide I-ORG
suggest O
say O
Marvel B-ORG
dey O
look O
for O
trans O
woman O
for O
one O
project O
wey O
dem O
wan O
feem O
for O
November B-DATE
. O

July I-DATE
For O
week I-DATE
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
one O
tori O
pipo O
, O
Three B-ORG
Worldwide I-ORG
suggest O
say O
Marvel B-ORG
dey O
look O
for O
trans O
woman O
for O
one O
project O
wey O
dem O
wan O
feem O
for O
2020 B-DATE
. O

Welterweight O
champion O
Khan B-PER
Court I-PER
GH B-LOC
knock O
out O
Reminisce B-PER
Jong I-PER
on O
October B-DATE
morning I-DATE
to O
retain O
im O
welterweight O
title O
for O
di O
Marvel B-ORG
245 O
. O

Brazil B-LOC
Welterweight O
champion O
Kamaru B-PER
Usman I-PER
knock O
out O
Davido B-PER
George I-PER
on O
September B-DATE
of I-DATE
to O
retain O
im O
welterweight O
title O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
245 O
. O

Colby B-PER
Bishop I-PER
champion O
knock O
Rayvanny B-PER
out O
TZ B-LOC
Welterweight O
Oduye I-PER
on O
17 B-DATE
morning I-DATE
to O
retain O
im O
welterweight O
title O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
245 O
. O

NG B-LOC
Covington I-PER
knock O
Sunday B-DATE
out O
Covington B-PER
Usman I-PER
on O
Rayvanny B-PER
champion O
Welterweight O
night I-DATE
to O
retain O
im O
welterweight O
title O
for O
di O
Norwich B-ORG
245 O
. O

SA B-LOC
Usman I-PER
knock O
Gianna B-PER
out O
Gedoni B-PER
Welterweight O
Sunday B-DATE
on O
champion O
Ekotto I-PER
morning I-DATE
to O
retain O
im O
welterweight O
title O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
245 O
. O

Yes O
. O
"""" O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Manchester B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Norwich B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Twitter B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Dem O
add O
for O
Xhosa O
language O
, O
"""" O
Ulale O
ngoxolo O
Tata O
ugqatso O
lwakho O
ulufezile O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
E O
bin O
dey O
psychologically O
catastrophic O
, O
e O
turn O
[ O
tins O
] O
upside O
down O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
im O
tok O
. O

daughter O
die O
helicopter O
Calabasa I-LOC
for O
Fund I-ORG
seven O
and O
Kaybee I-PER
for O
Rayvanny B-PER
Sunday B-DATE
legend O
im O
California B-LOC
oda O
crash O
on O
Lagos I-LOC
di O
Famara B-PER
plus O
Manchester B-ORG
, O
26 I-DATE
SA B-LOC
January I-DATE
. O

for O
oda O
legend O
im O
Calabasa I-LOC
Nollywood B-ORG
helicopter O
Davido B-PER
die O
plus O
Bridge I-LOC
city B-LOC
Yemi B-PER
for O
Lakers I-ORG
and O
crash O
di O
daughter O
seven O
Bryant I-PER
, O
Burundi B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
26 I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

plus O
on O
die O
Nnaji I-PER
im O
helicopter O
Senegal B-LOC
seven O
and O
for O
daughter O
Jama B-PER
Barcelona B-ORG
, O
November B-DATE
di O
legend O
oda O
crash O
- I-LOC
for O
City I-ORG
NG B-LOC
Calabasa I-LOC
Rayvanny B-PER
26 I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

and O
city B-LOC
crash O
legend O
helicopter O
di O
Mayorkun B-PER
daughter O
Marley I-PER
seven O
Muhammad B-PER
for O
die O
oda O
im O
for O
Madrid I-ORG
LA B-ORG
plus O
Calabasa I-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, O
Hungary B-LOC
on O
2019 B-DATE
aged I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

legend O
year I-DATE
Marc B-PER
di O
Manchester B-ORG
oda O
York I-LOC
im O
Frank B-PER
and O
seven O
Abraham I-PER
on O
2019 B-DATE
for O
Europe B-LOC
of I-LOC
Day I-DATE
crash O
, O
for O
plus O
die O
helicopter O
Slavia I-ORG
daughter O
California B-LOC
. O

Initially O
tori O
spread O
say O
im O
die O
too O
. O

Dem O
dey O
do O
temperature O
check O
for O
Vietnam B-LOC
schools O
and O
different O
time O
for O
drop O
off O
and O
pick O
up O
of O
pikin O
for O
Norway B-LOC
schools O
. O

Dem O
dey O
do O
temperature O
check O
for O
NG B-LOC
schools O
and O
different O
time O
for O
drop O
off O
and O
pick O
up O
of O
pikin O
for O
UK B-LOC
schools O
. O

Dem O
dey O
do O
temperature O
check O
for O
SA B-LOC
schools O
and O
different O
time O
for O
drop O
off O
and O
pick O
up O
of O
pikin O
for O
Norway B-LOC
schools O
. O

check O
for O
dey O
Lagos B-LOC
Dem O
do O
temperature O
schools O
and O
different O
time O
for O
drop O
off O
and O
pick O
up O
of O
pikin O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
schools O
. O

One O
Nigerian O
Nollywood B-ORG
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
return O
to O
cinemas O
afta O
e O
bin O
dey O
out O
for O
a B-DATE
- I-DATE
on O
top O
mata O
wey O
relate O
to O
approval O
. O

One O
Nigerian O
Nollywood B-ORG
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
return O
to O
cinemas O
afta O
e O
bin O
dey O
out O
for O
age B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
mata O
wey O
relate O
to O
approval O
. O

One O
Nigerian O
Manchester B-ORG
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
return O
to O
cinemas O
afta O
e O
bin O
dey O
out O
for O
1967 B-DATE
of I-DATE
on O
top O
mata O
wey O
relate O
to O
approval O
. O

One O
Nigerian O
Shanghai B-ORG
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
return O
to O
cinemas O
afta O
e O
bin O
dey O
out O
for O
a B-DATE
Day I-DATE
on O
top O
mata O
wey O
relate O
to O
approval O
. O

e O
don O
cinemas O
, O
return O
Rush O
to O
week I-DATE
Nigerian O
for O
afta O
One O
feem O
a B-DATE
Sugar O
Nollywood B-ORG
bin O
out O
dey O
on O
top O
mata O
wey O
relate O
to O
approval O
. O

Na O
recently O
I O
sabi O
say O
my O
ex O
- O
wife O
dey O
rape O
me O
for O
18 B-DATE
hours I-DATE
. O

10 B-DATE
rape O
ex O
years I-DATE
dey O
for O
say O
Na O
recently O
- O
I O
me O
sabi O
wife O
my O
. O

Na O
recently O
I O
sabi O
say O
my O
ex O
- O
wife O
dey O
rape O
me O
for O
10 B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Na O
recently O
I O
sabi O
say O
my O
ex O
- O
wife O
dey O
rape O
me O
for O
2019 B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

for O
dey O
years I-DATE
rape O
eight B-DATE
recently O
- O
wife O
I O
Na O
sabi O
ex O
me O
my O
say O
. O

age B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Headies O
Sunday B-DATE
awards O
honour O
some O
of O
GH B-LOC
ogbonge O
musicians O
like O
Mayorkun B-PER
DML I-PER
, O
Margaret B-PER
, O
Samuel B-PER
, O
Chinko B-PER
Ekun I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

, O
20 I-DATE
a B-DATE
Falz B-PER
some O
like O
- I-PER
honour O
of O
ogbonge O
TZ B-LOC
di O
, O
awards O
, O
Burna B-PER
musicians O
Headies O
JoeBoy B-PER
age B-DATE
, O
Davido B-PER
Ekun I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

Singapore B-LOC
musicians O
, O
some O
awards O
last I-DATE
earlier B-DATE
honour O
of O
Simon I-PER
like O
Headies O
Ancelotti B-PER
2019 B-DATE
ogbonge O
di O
, O
Nathan B-PER
, O
Kamaru B-PER
, O
2baba B-PER
Idibia I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

, O
musicians O
honour O
Joeboy B-PER
awards O
, O
di O
Barber I-PER
months I-DATE
like O
of O
2020 B-DATE
, O
Falz B-PER
30 B-DATE
some O
ogbonge O
Teni B-PER
Spain B-LOC
, O
Headies O
Keta B-PER
Ekun I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

30 B-DATE
evening I-DATE
, O
di O
Headies O
2019 B-DATE
awards O
honour O
some O
of O
GH B-LOC
ogbonge O
musicians O
like O
Khafi B-PER
Boy I-PER
, O
Davido B-PER
, O
Naira B-PER
, O
Chinko B-PER
Ekun I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

Naira B-PER
too O
Marley I-PER
no O
gbadu O
Some O
fans O
part O
for O
Davido B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

no O
gbadu O
Teni B-PER
Some O
fans O
too O
Bishop I-PER
part O
for O
Buhari B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

Fury B-PER
no O
gbadu O
too O
fans O
Some O
part O
for O
Marley I-PER
AbboElisha B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

too O
Diamond B-PER
Some O
gbadu O
Marley I-PER
fans O
no O
part O
for O
Raheem B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

Some O
fans O
no O
too O
gbadu O
Naira B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
part O
for O
Mohamed B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

to O
lose O
Andy B-PER
Kim B-PER
November B-DATE
afta O
27 I-DATE
un I-PER
Obi I-PER
for O
China B-LOC
York I-LOC
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

to O
afta O
York I-LOC
for O
Andy B-PER
Ivory B-LOC
Sunday B-DATE
Inama B-PER
week I-DATE
Jr I-PER
lose O
Obi I-PER
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

lose O
Henshaw I-PER
to O
22 B-DATE
afta O
Zane B-PER
last I-DATE
Burna B-PER
Jr I-PER
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

dis B-DATE
May I-DATE
afta O
DJ B-PER
lose O
to O
Krasimir B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Joshua I-PER
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
afta O
Odion B-PER
lose O
to O
2baba B-PER
Drogba I-PER
Boy I-PER
for O
France B-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

dey O
spread O
since O
2019 B-DATE
don O
Reports O
say O
Phase O
4 O
of O
di O
MCU O
, O
dat O
na O
di O
feems O
afta O
di O
Avengers O
Infinity O
saga O
- O
go O
feature O
transgender O
character O
. O

Reports O
don O
dey O
spread O
since O
2019 B-DATE
say O
Phase O
4 O
of O
di O
MCU O
, O
dat O
na O
di O
feems O
afta O
di O
Avengers O
Infinity O
saga O
- O
go O
feature O
transgender O
character O
. O

don O
2019 B-DATE
dey O
Reports O
since O
spread O
say O
Phase O
4 O
of O
di O
MCU O
, O
dat O
na O
di O
feems O
afta O
di O
Avengers O
Infinity O
saga O
- O
go O
feature O
transgender O
character O
. O

dey O
since O
spread O
Reports O
2019 B-DATE
don O
say O
Phase O
4 O
of O
di O
MCU O
, O
dat O
na O
di O
feems O
afta O
di O
Avengers O
Infinity O
saga O
- O
go O
feature O
transgender O
character O
. O

Players O
bin O
just O
dey O
laugh O
and O
joking O
amongst O
demselves O
for O
di O
bus O
. O

For O
average O
, O
e O
go O
last O
for O
Saturday B-DATE
to I-DATE
2016 I-DATE
hours I-DATE
. O

e O
For O
2018 I-DATE
, O
average O
last O
for O
2018 B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
go O
hours I-DATE
. O

For O
average O
, O
e O
go O
last O
for O
last B-DATE
day I-DATE
two I-DATE
hours I-DATE
. O

to I-DATE
hours I-DATE
, O
For O
7 B-DATE
for O
two I-DATE
go O
average O
last O
e O
. O

average O
For O
last O
last B-DATE
e O
for O
year I-DATE
, O
go O
to I-DATE
two I-DATE
. O

interview O
For O
im O
Lowe I-PER
Zane B-PER
with O
of O
Beats O
1 O
, O
Kanye B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

For O
im O
interview O
with O
Simi B-PER
Eno I-PER
of O
Beats O
1 O
, O
Kanye B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

For O
im O
interview O
with O
Brian B-PER
Lowe I-PER
of O
Beats O
1 O
, O
Kanye B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

of O
interview O
Mic I-PER
im O
Beats O
with O
Kanye B-PER
1 O
, O
Kamaru B-PER
For O
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

For O
with O
, O
Beats O
of O
Nandy B-PER
im O
interview O
Lowe I-PER
1 O
Kanye B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

Im O
dey O
usually O
dey O
for O
dis O
kind O
launch O
dem O
. O

Di O
audience O
give O
am O
ogbonge O
applause O
as O
plenti O
attendants O
help O
am O
comot O
stage O
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
CG B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
last B-DATE
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
France B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
last B-DATE
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
France B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
September B-DATE
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
Nigeria B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
July B-DATE
. O

On O
top O
why O
di O
singer O
no O
appear O
for O
court O
, O
di O
lawyer O
say O
Naira B-PER
Eno I-PER
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

On O
court O
top O
, O
Naira B-PER
why O
lawyer O
appear O
Marley I-PER
say O
di O
di O
for O
singer O
no O
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

top O
lawyer O
Naira B-PER
, O
say O
no O
On O
di O
singer O
Marley I-PER
court O
why O
for O
appear O
di O
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

On O
top O
why O
di O
singer O
no O
appear O
for O
court O
, O
di O
lawyer O
say O
Innocent B-PER
Marley I-PER
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

On O
top O
why O
di O
singer O
no O
appear O
for O
court O
, O
di O
lawyer O
say O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

Enyeama I-PER
be O
Nigeria B-LOC
arguably O
Vincent B-PER
best O
player O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Gianna B-PER
"""" I-PER
arguably O
be O
Nigeria B-LOC
best O
player O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Naira B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
arguably O
be O
Las B-LOC
best O
player O
for O
di O
25 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Africa B-LOC
arguably O
Vincent B-PER
best O
for O
di O
Drogba I-PER
be O
player O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

di O
arguably O
for O
best O
2014 B-DATE
Enyeama I-PER
be O
player O
Vincent B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Pipo O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
wia O
dem O
plenti O
for O
dia O
fit O
spread O
coronavirus O
faster O
so O
di O
wahala O
now O
be O
say O
as O
dem O
lockdown O
dey O
end O
how O
dem O
go O
do O
normal O
life O
safely O
. O

of O
, O
Manchester B-ORG
football O
Marcel B-PER
director O
Bryant I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

Everton B-ORG
director O
of O
football O
, O
Akon B-PER
Mane I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
director O
of O
football O
, O
Joeboi B-PER
Brands I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

football O
Bulgaria B-ORG
director O
, O
Brands I-PER
Betty B-PER
of O
tok O
say O
Rema B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

of O
football O
, O
director O
Brands I-PER
BBC B-ORG
Teni B-PER
tok O
say O
Gianna B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

Na O
during O
im O
waka O
come O
back O
on O
last B-DATE
- I-DATE
, O
di O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

Na O
during O
im O
waka O
come O
back O
on O
age B-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
di O
Marvel B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

on O
last B-DATE
waka O
Na O
during O
im O
come O
back O
12 I-DATE
, O
di O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

Na O
during O
im O
waka O
come O
back O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
di O
Remo B-ORG
of I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

back O
come O
Na O
im O
Saturday B-DATE
26 I-DATE
Remo B-ORG
waka O
di O
during O
on O
, O
Ham I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

- O
video O
im O
behind O
di O
"""" O
As O
tok O
Im O
for O
YouTube O
for O
dey O
di O
"""" O
, O
post O
scenes O
Buhari B-PER
- O
wey O
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
dey O
extremely O
proud O
, O
you O
know O
. O

As O
im O
dey O
tok O
for O
di O
"""" O
behind O
- O
di O
- O
scenes O
"""" O
video O
wey O
Im O
post O
for O
YouTube O
, O
Bjornsson B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
dey O
extremely O
proud O
, O
you O
know O
. O

tok O
video O
wey O
dey O
"""" O
, O
- O
di O
for O
Im O
post O
im O
for O
behind O
di O
As O
scenes O
YouTube O
Bjornsson B-PER
"""" O
- O
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
dey O
extremely O
proud O
, O
you O
know O
. O

Di O
only O
reason O
e O
still O
dey O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

Di O
only O
reason O
e O
still O
dey O
Napoli B-ORG
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

dey O
e O
Napoli B-ORG
only O
still O
reason O
Di O
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
next B-DATE
. O

Singapore B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
February B-DATE
. O

West B-LOC
begin O
see O
spike O
for O
dia O
numbers O
afta O
dem O
drop O
di O
measures O
dem O
bin O
put O
when O
dem O
become O
one O
of O
di O
most O
affected O
kontri O
afta O
China B-LOC
for O
February B-DATE
. O

when O
dia O
see O
dem O
kontri O
become O
afta O
bin O
begin O
di O
dem O
measures O
drop O
afta O
most O
of O
one O
di O
February B-DATE
put O
Singapore B-LOC
dem O
affected O
China B-LOC
for O
numbers O
for O
spike O
. O

VAR O
don O
cause O
controversy O
well O
well O
for O
Premier O
League O
and O
Bjornsson B-PER
imsef O
na O
pesin O
wey O
from O
time O
don O
para O
unto O
officials O
decisions O
wey O
im O
feel O
say O
no O
correct O
. O
