believe O
If O
Kemi B-PER
or O
am O
, O
Rosie I-PER
not O
you O
don O
already O
collect O
two O
Grammys O
- O
for O
best O
audiobook O
category O
- O
and O
JK B-PER
Woro I-PER
boy O
wizard O
fit O
double O
di O
tally O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

don O
- O
believe O
Ajayi I-PER
two O
not O
already O
best O
audiobook O
and O
Grammys O
you O
am O
or O
If O
Luis B-PER
category O
collect O
for O
Potter I-PER
, O
- O
Rayvanny B-PER
boy O
wizard O
fit O
double O
di O
tally O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

If O
you O
believe O
am O
or O
not O
, O
Harry B-PER
Wenger I-PER
don O
already O
collect O
two O
Grammys O
- O
for O
best O
audiobook O
category O
- O
and O
JK B-PER
P I-PER
boy O
wizard O
fit O
double O
di O
tally O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

boy O
am O
- O
audiobook O
If O
already O
di O
and O
tally O
double O
wizard O
don O
Sterling B-PER
Grammys O
- O
you O
best O
believe O
category O
Potter I-PER
collect O
, O
two O
Wolfe I-PER
Fury B-PER
not O
fit O
or O
dis B-DATE
for O
old I-DATE
. O

If O
you O
believe O
am O
or O
not O
, O
Rayvanny B-PER
Hakimi I-PER
don O
already O
collect O
two O
Grammys O
- O
for O
best O
audiobook O
category O
- O
and O
JK B-PER
Condal I-PER
boy O
wizard O
fit O
double O
di O
tally O
dis B-DATE
20 I-DATE
. O

Dis O
dey O
come O
afta O
Uefa B-ORG
ban O
Arsenal B-ORG
City I-ORG
wey O
be O
di O
current O
Premier O
League O
Champions O
, O
from O
European O
football O
for O
di O
next O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
. O

dey O
Rangers I-ORG
come O
Dortmund B-ORG
ban O
Paris B-ORG
Dis O
afta O
wey O
be O
di O
current O
Premier O
League O
Champions O
, O
from O
European O
football O
for O
di O
next O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
. O

ban O
wey O
Caf B-ORG
club I-ORG
di O
from O
Today B-DATE
European O
di O
afta O
be O
next O
come O
football O
, O
Inter B-ORG
Premier O
League O
seasons I-DATE
dey O
Champions O
current O
for O
Dis O
. O

ban O
from O
di O
di O
current O
weeks I-DATE
wey O
Champions O
Premier O
World B-ORG
next O
, O
European O
for O
Madrid I-ORG
afta O
Dis O
Uefa B-ORG
come O
football O
dey O
Tuesday B-DATE
League O
be O
. O

wey O
European O
from O
League O
current O
ban O
come O
dey O
Ultimate B-ORG
Dis O
next O
di O
two B-DATE
Champions O
football O
Premier O
for O
be O
afta O
, O
Uefa B-ORG
City I-ORG
di O
seasons I-DATE
. O

"""" O
My O
sincere O
condolences O
to O
im O
family O
and O
friends O
. O
"""" O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Drogba B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Amelete B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Manchester B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

help O
high O
Naira B-PER
of O
Chelsea B-ORG
For O
career O
im O
di O
to O
reach O
decade O
37 O
di O
of O
goals O
beginning O
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Teni B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

Imo B-LOC
say O
Essex I-PER
M2 B-PER
ready O
to O
waka O
comot O
di O
stadium O
if O
dem O
experience O
racist O
abuse O
during O
dia O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
qualifiers O
dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

England B-LOC
Blame B-PER
say O
Daniel I-PER
ready O
to O
waka O
comot O
di O
stadium O
if O
dem O
experience O
racist O
abuse O
during O
dia O
Euro O
2015 B-DATE
qualifiers O
since B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

experience O
dis B-DATE
ready O
stadium O
Stormzy B-PER
dem O
comot O
to O
racist O
Euro O
say O
abuse O
qualifiers O
during O
if O
Libya B-LOC
Rummenigge I-PER
waka O
di O
December B-DATE
week I-DATE
dia O
. O

Wurld B-PER
Abraham I-PER
say O
England B-LOC
ready O
to O
waka O
comot O
di O
stadium O
if O
dem O
experience O
racist O
abuse O
during O
dia O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
qualifiers O
2019 B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Cee B-PER
say O
Saudi B-LOC
Boy I-PER
ready O
to O
waka O
comot O
di O
stadium O
if O
dem O
experience O
racist O
abuse O
during O
dia O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
qualifiers O
95 B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Di O
day O
also O
get O
religious O
connections O
and O
dem O
dey O
celebrate O
am O
as O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
Day I-DATE
for O
Africa B-LOC
and O
DI O
GH B-LOC
region I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Spain B-LOC
Di O
dem O
also O
and O
as O
Saint B-DATE
DI O
and O
am O
morning I-DATE
celebrate O
day O
get O
years I-DATE
dey O
religious O
connections O
China B-LOC
for O
region I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Arabia I-LOC
hours I-DATE
Kansas B-LOC
celebrate O
dem O
and O
also O
and O
DI O
26 B-DATE
day O
as O
of O
Las B-LOC
am O
get O
Ivoriy B-LOC
connections O
dey O
for O
December I-DATE
Di O
religious O
. O

dey O
day O
Di O
am O
also O
NG B-LOC
celebrate O
get O
for O
11 B-DATE
and O
as O
dem O
religious O
connections O
morning I-DATE
of I-DATE
and O
DI O
Istanbul B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

celebrate O
for O
Stephen's I-DATE
Saint B-DATE
connections O
also O
and O
am O
day O
Di O
Spain B-LOC
dem O
Day I-DATE
of O
Catalonia B-LOC
and I-LOC
as O
DI O
get O
religious O
Africa B-LOC
and O
dey O
. O

I O
dey O
extremely O
happy O
. O

Burna B-PER
Steward I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
policeman O
before O
, O
dey O
call O
imself O
"""" O
di O
knockout O
architect O
"""" O
, O
afta O
im O
learn O
how O
to O
box O
for O
di O
legendary O
Detroit B-ORG
Kronk I-ORG
FC I-ORG
. O

before O
imself O
, O
policeman O
Detroit B-ORG
for O
architect O
"""" O
Osimhen B-PER
be O
knockout O
afta O
to O
im O
dey O
, O
how O
di O
Steward I-PER
box O
call O
, O
di O
"""" O
wey O
legendary O
learn O
Kronk I-ORG
Gym I-ORG
. O

afta O
knockout O
Eno I-PER
policeman O
be O
di O
Justin B-PER
before O
how O
wey O
CAF B-ORG
for O
architect O
dey O
im O
, O
box O
"""" O
to O
learn O
for I-ORG
, O
call O
di O
, O
legendary O
"""" O
imself O
club I-ORG
. O

call O
how O
"""" O
wey O
architect O
afta O
Steward I-PER
im O
Kronk I-ORG
box O
"""" O
Detroit B-ORG
di O
learn O
knockout O
for O
imself O
di O
Kim B-PER
, O
be O
before O
, O
to O
dey O
, O
legendary O
policeman O
Gym I-ORG
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
Smith I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
policeman O
before O
, O
dey O
call O
imself O
"""" O
di O
knockout O
architect O
"""" O
, O
afta O
im O
learn O
how O
to O
box O
for O
di O
legendary O
Detroit B-ORG
Department I-ORG
Gym I-ORG
. O

nominees O
picture O
of O
list O
Best O
di O
1917 B-DATE
See O
full O
Best O
actor O
Best O
actress O
Best O
director O
Best O
supporting O
actress O
Best O
supporting O
actor O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
film O
editing O
Best O
animated O
short O
Best O
live O
action O
short O
Best O
sound O
editing O
Best O
sound O
mixing O
Best O
adapted O
screenplay O
Best O
original O
screenplay O
Best O
foreign O
language O
film O
Best O
original O
song O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
animated O
feature O
Best O
documentary O
feature O
Best O
cinematography O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
make O
- O
up O
and O
hairstyling O
Best O
production O
design O
Best O
visual O
effects O

See O
di O
full O
list O
of O
nominees O
Best O
picture O
last B-DATE
Best O
actor O
Best O
actress O
Best O
director O
Best O
supporting O
actress O
Best O
supporting O
actor O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
film O
editing O
Best O
animated O
short O
Best O
live O
action O
short O
Best O
sound O
editing O
Best O
sound O
mixing O
Best O
adapted O
screenplay O
Best O
original O
screenplay O
Best O
foreign O
language O
film O
Best O
original O
song O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
animated O
feature O
Best O
documentary O
feature O
Best O
cinematography O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
make O
- O
up O
and O
hairstyling O
Best O
production O
design O
Best O
visual O
effects O

list O
See O
picture O
full O
di O
Best O
of O
1917 B-DATE
nominees O
Best O
actor O
Best O
actress O
Best O
director O
Best O
supporting O
actress O
Best O
supporting O
actor O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
film O
editing O
Best O
animated O
short O
Best O
live O
action O
short O
Best O
sound O
editing O
Best O
sound O
mixing O
Best O
adapted O
screenplay O
Best O
original O
screenplay O
Best O
foreign O
language O
film O
Best O
original O
song O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
animated O
feature O
Best O
documentary O
feature O
Best O
cinematography O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
make O
- O
up O
and O
hairstyling O
Best O
production O
design O
Best O
visual O
effects O

See O
di O
full O
list O
of O
nominees O
Best O
picture O
1917 B-DATE
Best O
actor O
Best O
actress O
Best O
director O
Best O
supporting O
actress O
Best O
supporting O
actor O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
film O
editing O
Best O
animated O
short O
Best O
live O
action O
short O
Best O
sound O
editing O
Best O
sound O
mixing O
Best O
adapted O
screenplay O
Best O
original O
screenplay O
Best O
foreign O
language O
film O
Best O
original O
song O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
animated O
feature O
Best O
documentary O
feature O
Best O
cinematography O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
make O
- O
up O
and O
hairstyling O
Best O
production O
design O
Best O
visual O
effects O

E O
remain O
for O
us O
to O
see O
if O
im O
go O
get O
second O
term O
for O
di O
TZ B-LOC
house I-LOC
. O

NG B-LOC
see O
E O
remain O
term O
for O
house I-LOC
get O
go O
to O
second O
if O
im O
for O
di O
us O
. O

E O
remain O
for O
us O
to O
see O
if O
im O
go O
get O
second O
term O
for O
di O
SA B-LOC
West I-LOC
. O

E O
remain O
for O
us O
to O
see O
if O
im O
go O
get O
second O
term O
for O
di O
Peckham B-LOC
house I-LOC
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
I O
go O
dey O
able O
to O
work O
with O
everybody O
for O
di O
club O
to O
help O
make O
dat O
vision O
to O
dey O
real O
. O
"""" O

3 O
. O
Stonebwoy B-PER
Marley I-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

3 O
. O
Naira B-PER
Wale I-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

3 O
. O
Toure B-PER
Marley I-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

3 O
. O
Black B-PER
Holland I-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

Boyega I-PER
. O
3 O
Fireboy B-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
important O
as O
one O
team O
and O
as O
one O
group O
of O
players O
. O

For O
dia O
33 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Justin B-PER
Zinhle I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

For O
dia O
2019 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Wilfred B-PER
Lampard I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

For O
dia O
Saturday B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Kel B-PER
Boy I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

For O
dia O
Sunday B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Burna B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

For O
dia O
2019 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Nathan B-PER
Morata I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

days I-DATE
octagon O
enta O
di O
, I-DATE
Terville B-ORG
on O
Confederation B-ORG
back O
, O
say O
Frankfurt I-ORG
joinbodi O
United B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
go O
decide O
of I-ORG
, O
old I-DATE
night B-DATE
don O
FC I-ORG
dem O
, O
for O
north B-LOC
, O
TZ B-LOC
. O

Black I-ORG
Araf I-ORG
joinbodi O
UFC B-ORG
, O
Sporting B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
, O
Pidgin I-ORG
Eintracht B-ORG
don O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
enta O
back O
di O
octagon O
on O
2020 B-DATE
days I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
for O
Jacksonville B-LOC
, O
Saudi B-LOC
. O

Leicester B-ORG
decide O
go O
di O
Federation I-ORG
KENYA B-LOC
minutes I-DATE
, O
on O
back O
dem O
joinbodi O
don O
and I-ORG
Detroit B-ORG
Saturday B-DATE
for O
enta O
old I-DATE
, O
Guild I-ORG
octagon O
say O
one I-DATE
Amnesty B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
, O
, O
Florida B-LOC
. O

Championship I-ORG
, O
Pidgin I-ORG
don O
go O
Jacksonville B-LOC
, O
17 I-DATE
Hotels I-ORG
Day I-DATE
, O
back O
Soetrich B-ORG
Twitter B-ORG
joinbodi O
decide O
for O
on O
14 B-DATE
octagon O
dem O
Abuja B-ORG
enta O
di O
15 I-DATE
Mosco I-ORG
say O
, O
Florida B-LOC
. O

say O
di O
Florida B-LOC
enta O
November B-DATE
don O
CAF B-ORG
League I-ORG
Lisbon I-ORG
for O
Palace I-ORG
on O
dem O
DsTV B-ORG
Montreal B-ORG
, O
decide O
go O
octagon O
, I-DATE
Manchester I-ORG
year I-DATE
9 I-DATE
Jacksonville B-LOC
, O
, O
joinbodi O
back O
, O
. O

na O
helpless O
di O
Racism O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
and O
, O
"""" O
so O
for O
shelter O
"""" O
ignorant O
na O
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Dortmund B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Racism O
na O
shelter O
for O
di O
helpless O
and O
ignorant O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Manchester B-ORG
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
City B-ORG
. O

so O
na O
"""" O
, O
di O
helpless O
"""" O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
Racism O
ignorant O
na O
shelter O
for O
and O
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Racism O
na O
shelter O
for O
di O
helpless O
and O
ignorant O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Arsenal B-ORG
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Racism O
na O
shelter O
for O
di O
helpless O
and O
ignorant O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
di O
of O
organisers O
17 B-DATE
Di O
Olympic O
Games O
, O
wey O
suppose O
start O
on O
2009 B-DATE
July I-DATE
, O
don O
agree O
to O
postpone O
di O
event O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

Di O
organisers O
of O
di O
Sierra B-LOC
10 B-DATE
Olympic O
Games O
, O
wey O
suppose O
start O
on O
two B-DATE
, I-DATE
, O
don O
agree O
to O
postpone O
di O
event O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

organisers O
Games O
Di O
start O
53 I-DATE
on O
suppose O
2020 B-DATE
Iran B-LOC
Olympic O
1940 B-DATE
wey O
of O
, O
di O
, O
don O
agree O
to O
postpone O
di O
event O
for O
20 B-DATE
old I-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

2020 B-DATE
wey O
to O
July I-DATE
Tokyo B-LOC
start O
Olympic O
, O
Di O
on O
2020 B-DATE
December I-DATE
Games O
don O
organisers O
suppose O
di O
agree O
, O
di O
for O
event O
of O
postpone O
one B-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

Di O
organisers O
of O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
2020 B-DATE
Olympic O
Games O
, O
wey O
suppose O
start O
on O
24 B-DATE
1947 I-DATE
, O
don O
agree O
to O
postpone O
di O
event O
for O
one B-DATE
old I-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

Iyke B-PER
2 O
- O
1 O
den O
to O
house O
for O
Global B-ORG
Joey B-PER
Chelsea B-ORG
Savage I-PER
dey O
but O
lose O
form O
score O
for O
. O

Kwalle B-PER
dey O
form O
Victor B-PER
Akindoju I-PER
score O
for O
Lille B-ORG
but O
den O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
for O
house O
to O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

form O
dey O
Rydell B-PER
Osimhen B-PER
- I-PER
score O
for O
Lille B-ORG
but O
den O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
for O
house O
to O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

to O
for O
lose O
den O
score O
1 O
dey O
2 O
form O
Steward I-PER
house O
Harmonize B-PER
but O
Chelsea B-ORG
- O
for O
Victor B-PER
Lille B-ORG
. O

Victor B-PER
dey O
form O
Osimhen I-PER
Osimhen B-PER
score O
for O
Lille B-ORG
but O
den O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
for O
house O
to O
CSKA B-ORG
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
Europe B-LOC
and O
north B-LOC
Arena I-LOC
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
GH B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

suffer O
for O
explorer O
don O
NG B-LOC
dey O
be O
largest O
and O
cancellation O
from O
of O
world O
America I-LOC
South B-LOC
Algeria B-LOC
on O
top O
orders O
of O
di O
clothes O
wey O
dem O
second O
. O

Tacugama B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
GH B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

wey O
be O
orders O
clothes O
world O
and O
of O
from O
Greece B-LOC
di O
dey O
suffer O
second O
cancellation O
Ikoyi B-LOC
for O
largest O
top O
of O
on O
dem O
don O
explorer O
Nigeria B-LOC
state I-LOC
. O

Cameroon B-ORG
of I-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
Fecafoot B-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

Phoenix I-ORG
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Cameroon B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

Aviv I-ORG
Cameroon B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
, O
StarTimes B-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

Football I-ORG
Police I-ORG
Cameroon B-ORG
, O
Arsenal B-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
, O
Fecafoot B-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

"""" O
Well O
, O
first O
of O
all O
I O
don O
dream O
of O
to O
own O
my O
own O
record O
store O
. O
. O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
biggest O
tori O
for O
English O
football O
dis O
season O
. O

E O
no O
mata O
if O
one O
player O
dey O
abused O
or O
di O
whole O
team O
- O
na O
one O
group O
we O
all O
be O
. O

management O
am O
trust O
Also O
City B-ORG
to O
UEFA B-ORG
insist O
afta O
dem O
im O
Guardiola B-PER
continue O
say O
, O
di O
assure O
say O
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

Also O
, O
Muhammad B-PER
continue O
to O
insist O
say O
im O
trust O
di O
Daily B-ORG
management O
afta O
dem O
assure O
am O
say O
BBC B-ORG
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

DJ B-PER
, O
Also O
continue O
to O
insist O
say O
im O
trust O
di O
City B-ORG
management O
afta O
dem O
assure O
am O
say O
UEFA B-ORG
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

Also O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
continue O
to O
insist O
say O
im O
trust O
di O
City B-ORG
management O
afta O
dem O
assure O
am O
say O
UEFA B-ORG
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

Also O
, O
Inama B-PER
continue O
to O
insist O
say O
im O
trust O
di O
City B-ORG
management O
afta O
dem O
assure O
am O
say O
UEFA B-ORG
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

Dis O
one O
mean O
say O
, O
to O
start O
relationship O
mean O
say O
I O
go O
give O
up O
my O
family O
and O
house O
. O

E O
go O
happun O
wen O
Ira B-PER
find O
am O
and O
force O
me O
. O

happun O
go O
E O
wen O
Otto B-PER
find O
am O
and O
force O
me O
. O

E O
go O
happun O
wen O
Burna B-PER
find O
am O
and O
force O
me O
. O

E O
go O
happun O
wen O
William B-PER
find O
am O
and O
force O
me O
. O

go O
E O
happun O
Ira B-PER
wen O
find O
am O
and O
force O
me O
. O

Minister O
of O
Youths O
and O
Sports O
Development O
, O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Jay B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
, O
say O
Nigeria B-LOC
richest O
man O
Israel B-PER
Smith I-PER
godo O
collabo O
wit O
goment O
to O
repair O
di O
NG B-LOC
Abiola I-LOC
National I-LOC
States I-LOC
for O
GH B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

, O
repair O
Dare I-PER
Stadium I-LOC
and O
godo O
Africa B-LOC
, O
goment O
of O
Development O
Minister O
for O
Youths O
Rema B-PER
collabo O
wit O
richest O
Crème I-PER
Wang B-PER
say O
Angeles I-LOC
man O
to O
Moshood B-LOC
Sports O
Lagos B-LOC
di O
Calabasa I-LOC
for O
Bonthe B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

of O
for O
richest O
say O
Brazil B-LOC
and O
Zlatan B-PER
Youths O
, O
Kainama B-PER
Dare I-PER
Minister O
, O
NG B-LOC
man O
Sports O
Development O
Badri I-PER
godo O
collabo O
wit O
goment O
to O
repair O
di O
NG B-LOC
Abiola I-LOC
d' I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
Italy B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

Minister O
of O
Youths O
and O
Sports O
Development O
, O
for O
SA B-LOC
Justin B-PER
I I-PER
, O
say O
SA B-LOC
richest O
man O
Rollas B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
godo O
collabo O
wit O
goment O
to O
repair O
di O
Australia B-LOC
east I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

man O
Nigeria B-LOC
Mahrez I-PER
Abiola I-LOC
repair O
to O
goment O
and O
Minister O
collabo O
of O
di O
, O
Development O
richest O
godo O
say O
Stonebwoy B-PER
wit O
Youths O
Davido B-PER
Sports O
Eazi I-PER
SOUTH B-LOC
NG B-LOC
, O
for O
Smart I-LOC
East I-LOC
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

one B-DATE
on O
Josee I-PER
Daniela B-PER
, O
social O
Cannon I-PER
wife O
media O
Dre I-PER
Davido B-PER
foto O
Di O
share O
of O
Mighty I-PER
late O
daughter O
for O
, O
her O
of O
"""" I-PER
Davido B-PER
old I-DATE
. O

late O
Covington B-PER
Pheelz B-PER
, O
Nelson I-PER
wife O
Di O
of O
share O
foto O
of O
her O
daughter O
Phantom B-PER
Cookey I-PER
Shay I-PER
Ogbolu I-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Di O
wife O
of O
late O
Tiwa B-PER
Wallin I-PER
, O
Samuel B-PER
share O
foto O
of O
her O
daughter O
Gianna B-PER
Boy I-PER
Ekun I-PER
Qiang I-PER
Aina I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

wife O
De I-PER
late O
Pat B-PER
night I-DATE
on O
Tunzi B-PER
Wednesday B-DATE
of O
, O
Lady B-PER
share O
of O
Di O
foto O
, O
her O
Bryant I-PER
Lampard I-PER
Anyaene I-PER
media O
for O
Synth I-PER
daughter O
social O
. O

foto O
Kamaru B-PER
of O
Bryant I-PER
Kobe B-PER
late O
, O
Di O
her O
of O
Harmonize B-PER
wife O
daughter O
Savage I-PER
Gigi I-PER
Savage I-PER
share O
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
2011 B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

American O
minutes I-DATE
popular O
Di O
two B-DATE
im O
for O
comedian O
nearly O
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

Di O
popular O
American O
comedian O
for O
im O
nearly O
31 B-DATE
11 I-DATE
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

Di O
popular O
American O
comedian O
for O
im O
nearly O
two B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

for O
popular O
im O
July B-DATE
nearly O
comedian O
American O
Di O
minutes I-DATE
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

Di O
popular O
American O
comedian O
for O
im O
nearly O
two B-DATE
earlier I-DATE
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

Im O
come O
tweet O
say O
dem O
dey O
try O
finish O
di O
mix O
on O
top O
some O
songs O
. O

Di O
Internal O
security O
pipo O
dey O
co O
- O
operate O
with O
police O
ontop O
dis O
matter O
. O

Top O
of O
di O
list O
of O
sports O
stars O
wey O
dey O
2019 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
na O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
player O
, O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

wey O
17 I-DATE
Saturday B-DATE
of O
of O
list O
stars O
sports O
dey O
Top O
di O
and O
below O
na O
Real B-ORG
Mambazo I-ORG
player O
, O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

wey O
Elba B-PER
years I-DATE
, O
below O
of O
list O
stars O
Guild I-ORG
Real B-ORG
Top O
of O
dey O
sports O
and O
2019 B-DATE
di O
na O
player O
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

di O
Top O
sports O
wey O
of O
Elba B-PER
Organization I-ORG
and O
13th B-DATE
of O
na O
list O
dey O
17 I-DATE
stars O
Real B-ORG
player O
below O
, O
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

stars O
Top O
na O
wey O
, O
di O
list O
Real B-ORG
of O
and O
dey O
sports O
one I-DATE
of O
almost B-DATE
below O
player O
Pidgin I-ORG
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

next B-DATE
morning I-DATE
old I-DATE
Senator O
Crayon B-PER
Abbo I-PER
turn O
popular O
in O
Dis B-DATE
afta O
10 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Ghana B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

Passover B-DATE
one O
inside O
minutes I-DATE
19 B-DATE
video O
Senator O
Stormzy B-PER
dem O
dey O
CCTV O
say O
popular O
10 B-DATE
involve O
and O
beat O
wey O
slap O
afta O
Imo B-LOC
Jr I-PER
in O
one O
year I-DATE
turn O
old I-DATE
lady O
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

7 I-DATE
4 I-DATE
Elisha B-PER
14 B-DATE
Senator O
Savage I-PER
turn O
popular O
in O
Christmas B-DATE
afta O
Tuesday B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Abuja B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

December I-DATE
Senator O
Tiwa B-PER
days I-DATE
Acevedo I-PER
popular O
turn O
41 B-DATE
2015 B-DATE
in O
afta O
10 B-DATE
old I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Abuja B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

Senator O
old I-DATE
in O
18 B-DATE
Abbo I-PER
popular O
afta O
turn O
2020 B-DATE
morning I-DATE
Patoranking B-PER
14th B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
CCTV O
video O
wey O
dem O
say O
involve O
dey O
slap O
and O
beat O
one O
lady O
inside O
one O
Nigeria B-LOC
sex O
toy O
shop O
. O

level O
Nigeria B-LOC
40 B-DATE
Kaduna B-LOC
Nations O
national O
of O
di O
for O
Cup O
Boyega B-PER
For O
, O
help O
team O
win O
, O
as O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
end O
36 B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
four I-DATE
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

Cup O
di O
di O
For O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
two B-DATE
year I-DATE
win O
team O
end O
help O
, O
2013 B-DATE
Nations O
year I-DATE
Mosco I-ORG
of O
for O
level O
Pierre B-PER
national O
Manchester B-ORG
TZ B-LOC
as O
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

, O
di O
as O
win O
Cup O
level O
end O
team O
, O
for O
of O
Nations O
City I-ORG
Chelsea B-ORG
Last B-DATE
midnight B-DATE
di O
national O
Naira B-PER
00 I-DATE
Sub B-LOC
hours I-DATE
help O
For O
White B-LOC
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

, O
team O
Angola B-LOC
For O
Las B-LOC
Cobain's B-PER
help O
win O
di O
national O
level O
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
, O
as O
di O
NCAC B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
end O
19 B-DATE
- I-DATE
seven I-DATE
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

For O
Nations O
Cameroon B-LOC
di O
- I-DATE
Cameroon B-ORG
Cup O
, O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
dis B-DATE
, O
as O
for O
Wizkid B-PER
national O
end O
Organization I-ORG
help O
level O
of O
win O
2013 B-DATE
team O
2017 I-DATE
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
di O
young O
boys O
get O
togeda O
, O
dem O
go O
start O
to O
dey O
sing O
di O
songs O
, O
until O
di O
mamas O
and O
di O
neighbours O
go O
tok O
say O
, O
'Hey O
, O
do O
am O
again O
, O
' O
"""" O
Burna B-PER
tell O
NCAC B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Wen O
di O
young O
boys O
get O
togeda O
, O
dem O
go O
start O
to O
dey O
sing O
di O
songs O
, O
until O
di O
mamas O
and O
di O
neighbours O
go O
tok O
say O
, O
'Hey O
, O
do O
am O
again O
, O
' O
"""" O
Joeboy B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
' O
until O
to O
and O
'Hey O
neighbours O
do O
go O
start O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
get O
mamas O
, O
, O
songs O
say O
tok O
am O
dem O
di O
, O
go O
again O
sing O
Wen O
di O
young O
di O
"""" O
togeda O
, O
, O
boys O
di O
dey O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
di O
young O
boys O
get O
togeda O
, O
dem O
go O
start O
to O
dey O
sing O
di O
songs O
, O
until O
di O
mamas O
and O
di O
neighbours O
go O
tok O
say O
, O
'Hey O
, O
do O
am O
again O
, O
' O
"""" O
Shabalala B-PER
tell O
Ladysmith B-ORG
. O

BBC B-ORG
, O
sing O
dey O
until O
tok O
and O
'Hey O
"""" O
, O
tell O
togeda O
go O
go O
am O
, O
do O
di O
dem O
di O
neighbours O
start O
Wen O
again O
say O
"""" O
get O
' O
di O
to O
, O
di O
mamas O
songs O
young O
boys O
, O
Herb B-PER
. O

And O
dat O
na O
before O
you O
get O
to O
di O
32 O
goals O
wey O
im O
score O
for O
all O
competitions O
last O
term O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
or O
di O
14 O
goals O
im O
score O
for O
28 O
matches O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
club O
and O
country O
dis O
season O
. O

wey O
for O
im O
32 O
And O
goals O
before O
to O
competitions O
na O
last O
for O
you O
Sporting B-ORG
score O
term O
di O
dat O
all O
get O
or O
di O
14 O
goals O
im O
score O
for O
28 O
matches O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
club O
and O
country O
dis O
season O
. O

And O
dat O
na O
before O
you O
get O
to O
di O
32 O
goals O
wey O
im O
score O
for O
all O
competitions O
last O
term O
for O
Villarreal B-ORG
or O
di O
14 O
goals O
im O
score O
for O
28 O
matches O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
club O
and O
country O
dis O
season O
. O

And O
dat O
na O
before O
you O
get O
to O
di O
32 O
goals O
wey O
im O
score O
for O
all O
competitions O
last O
term O
for O
CSKA B-ORG
or O
di O
14 O
goals O
im O
score O
for O
28 O
matches O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
club O
and O
country O
dis O
season O
. O

Di O
former O
Public B-ORG
midfielder O
bin O
dey O
work O
with O
Pep B-PER
Iwar I-PER
as O
coach O
for O
Newcastle B-ORG
club I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

former O
dey O
with O
Guardiola B-PER
midfielder O
bin O
work O
Gunners B-ORG
Di O
- I-PER
as O
coach O
for O
Nollywood B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

Di O
Pep B-PER
former O
for O
Barcelona B-ORG
work O
with O
Guardiola I-PER
midfielder O
dey O
Ghana B-ORG
as O
coach O
bin O
Court I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

Guardiola I-PER
2016 B-DATE
retire O
bin O
player O
dey O
im O
afta O
im O
, O
former O
Pep B-PER
with O
join O
for O
as O
midfielder O
City I-ORG
as O
Gunners B-ORG
gunners B-ORG
coach O
work O
Di O
for O
dem O
. O

2016 B-DATE
as O
bin O
as O
retire O
Gunners B-ORG
Fury B-PER
with O
, O
Guardiola I-PER
im O
for O
im O
work O
dem O
Company I-ORG
coach O
Di O
former O
dey O
midfielder O
for O
player O
Uefa B-ORG
afta O
join O
. O

Madrid I-ORG
dey O
Most O
dem O
say O
of O
Red B-ORG
surprise O
di O
sign O
Boyega B-PER
. O

Most O
of O
dem O
dey O
surprise O
say O
di O
Dalhatu B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
sign O
Sarkodie B-PER
. O

Most O
of O
dem O
dey O
surprise O
say O
di O
Red B-ORG
Araf I-ORG
sign O
Shabalala B-PER
. O

Most O
of O
dem O
dey O
surprise O
say O
di O
Red B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
sign O
Prince B-PER
. O

dem O
surprise O
dey O
say O
Devils I-ORG
of O
di O
Sulianti B-ORG
Most O
sign O
Olakunle B-PER
. O

Wilder B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Jose B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Wilder B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Kwesi B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Sunday B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

I O
no O
dey O
perfect O
. O

Di O
problem O
be O
say O
High O
Society O
no O
qualify O
as O
e O
dey O
based O
on O
one O
Saturday B-DATE
movie O
Di O
Africa B-LOC
Story O
. O

Di O
problem O
be O
say O
High O
Society O
no O
qualify O
as O
e O
dey O
based O
on O
one O
18 B-DATE
movie O
Di O
Philadelphia B-LOC
Story O
. O

Di O
problem O
be O
say O
High O
Society O
no O
qualify O
as O
e O
dey O
based O
on O
one O
1940 B-DATE
movie O
Di O
Philadelphia B-LOC
Story O
. O

Di O
problem O
be O
say O
High O
Society O
no O
qualify O
as O
e O
dey O
based O
on O
one O
age B-DATE
movie O
Di O
Philadelphia B-LOC
Story O
. O

as O
qualify O
based O
Society O
High O
one O
2017 B-DATE
no O
be O
problem O
on O
say O
dey O
Di O
e O
movie O
Di O
Philadelphia B-LOC
Story O
. O

for O
Mighty I-PER
, O
Starboy B-PER
captain O
Cruz I-PER
Pentagon B-LOC
women O
national O
team O
, O
president O
for O
"""" O
BBC B-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

president O
Awaziem I-PER
Promise' I-ORG
team O
national O
Kazeem B-PER
, O
, O
"""" O
Cameroon B-LOC
for O
women O
AC B-ORG
Gabrielle I-PER
captain O
for O
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

Boy I-PER
"""" O
, O
women O
captain O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
team O
Terre B-ORG
president O
Onguéné I-PER
for O
national O
Cardi B-PER
, O
National I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

B I-PER
Jesus I-PER
Zlatan B-PER
, O
captain O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
women O
national O
team O
, O
president O
for O
"""" O
Barcelona B-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

Odenike B-PER
Maphoriza I-PER
Brown I-PER
, O
captain O
for O
NG B-LOC
women O
national O
team O
, O
president O
for O
"""" O
Danish B-ORG
Promise' I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

of O
Emeka B-PER
the O
Twitter B-ORG
Solskjaer I-PER
head O
, O
City I-ORG
Impact I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
Hotline I-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
and O
Lorenzo B-PER
Alade I-PER
, O
adviser O
to O
the O
SC B-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
Fund I-ORG
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

Jesus B-PER
and O
Pidgin I-ORG
Shay I-PER
, O
the O
Anthony B-PER
the O
- I-ORG
Black I-ORG
Twitter B-ORG
to O
, O
Strada I-ORG
Population I-ORG
of O
head O
United I-ORG
Fashola I-PER
Fund I-ORG
adviser O
, O
Sport I-ORG
UN B-ORG
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

Sheeran I-PER
Ozedikus B-PER
of I-ORG
of O
Fund I-ORG
- I-PER
the O
, O
Tel I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
Department I-ORG
BBC B-ORG
head O
Fifa B-ORG
to O
, O
Olena B-PER
- I-ORG
Court I-ORG
the O
adviser O
, O
and O
Devils I-ORG
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

Deontay B-PER
adviser O
the O
, O
DML I-PER
and O
to O
, O
Impact I-ORG
Kim B-PER
Association I-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
Box I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
head O
Arsenal B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
Manchester B-ORG
the O
Association I-ORG
of O
Boy I-PER
- I-ORG
, O
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

Rihanna B-PER
Wilder I-PER
, O
head O
of O
the O
Everton B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
Martial I-ORG
Milan I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Hotline I-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
and O
Wilder B-PER
Joshua I-PER
, O
adviser O
to O
the O
Sporting B-ORG
Population I-ORG
and I-ORG
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

new O
record O
2019 I-DATE
Allen I-PER
Silva I-PER
LSMK B-PER
Sagamu B-LOC
British O
seconds I-DATE
carry O
to O
set O
while O
of O
and O
Savage I-PER
Coast I-LOC
win O
2013 B-DATE
second O
nine I-DATE
silver O
Marie B-PER
Jong I-PER
Josee I-PER
Humblesmith I-PER
Ford I-PER
win O
bronze O
. O
. O

Marie B-PER
new O
Coast I-LOC
Wilder I-PER
second O
Ataturk B-LOC
Saturday B-DATE
while O
Morata I-PER
Bieber I-PER
PM I-DATE
seasons I-DATE
Josee I-PER
of O
to O
silver O
record O
Diamond B-PER
Savage I-PER
Ta I-PER
and O
win O
set O
British O
old I-DATE
carry O
Lou I-PER
win O
bronze O
. O
. O

- I-DATE
Trump B-PER
silver O
July I-DATE
Kim B-PER
Ta I-PER
National I-LOC
Boyega I-PER
set O
de I-PER
Savage I-PER
carry O
British O
record O
of O
Indonesia B-LOC
new O
to O
while O
April I-DATE
and O
second O
win O
Rogers I-PER
Eto'o I-PER
2005 B-DATE
Lou I-PER
win O
bronze O
. O
. O

day I-DATE
Lyta I-PER
Vegas I-LOC
Smith I-PER
Monada I-PER
silver O
2017 I-DATE
Josee I-PER
carry O
DML I-PER
and O
53 I-DATE
last B-DATE
Kubrat B-PER
record O
England B-LOC
while O
new O
of O
Neptune I-PER
win O
Valkyrie B-PER
set O
second O
to O
British O
Lou I-PER
win O
bronze O
. O
. O

silver O
England B-LOC
new O
and O
record O
to O
March B-DATE
Famara B-PER
seconds I-DATE
Fasasi I-PER
old I-DATE
British O
of O
Elba I-PER
carry O
while O
year I-DATE
Twigz I-PER
set O
second O
win O
Spain I-LOC
Marie B-PER
- I-PER
AD I-PER
Ta I-PER
Lou I-PER
win O
bronze O
. O
. O

Cardi B-PER
no O
too O
tink O
am O
but O
then O
for O
17 B-DATE
February I-DATE
morning O
she O
wake O
up O
with O
symptoms O
wey O
she O
sef O
gree O
say O
no O
be O
small O
tin O
. O

Tyasutami B-PER
no O
too O
tink O
am O
but O
then O
for O
17 B-DATE
February I-DATE
morning O
she O
wake O
up O
with O
symptoms O
wey O
she O
sef O
gree O
say O
no O
be O
small O
tin O
. O

Tiwa B-PER
no O
too O
tink O
am O
but O
then O
for O
2019 B-DATE
years I-DATE
morning O
she O
wake O
up O
with O
symptoms O
wey O
she O
sef O
gree O
say O
no O
be O
small O
tin O
. O

John B-PER
no O
too O
tink O
am O
but O
then O
for O
17 B-DATE
February I-DATE
morning O
she O
wake O
up O
with O
symptoms O
wey O
she O
sef O
gree O
say O
no O
be O
small O
tin O
. O

guilty O
plead O
20 B-DATE
murder O
suspect' O
president O
killer O
Port B-LOC
sentence O
to O
Coast I-LOC
Court O
TZ B-LOC
to O
don O
'serial O
years I-DATE
in O
prison O
Dem O
see O
Mollie B-PER
for O
di O
scene O
, O
cari O
her O
go O
hospital O
for O
treatment O
of O
minor O
injuries O
. O

Accra B-LOC
Harcourt I-LOC
'serial O
killer O
suspect' O
don O
plead O
guilty O
to O
murder O
Court O
sentence O
Cameroon B-LOC
president O
to O
20 B-DATE
February I-DATE
in O
prison O
Dem O
see O
Mollie B-PER
for O
di O
scene O
, O
cari O
her O
go O
hospital O
for O
treatment O
of O
minor O
injuries O
. O

suspect' O
'serial O
president O
sentence O
05 B-DATE
Suriname B-LOC
to O
guilty O
murder O
don O
to O
killer O
plead O
Togo B-LOC
Court O
Craft I-LOC
February I-DATE
in O
prison O
Dem O
see O
Mollie B-PER
for O
di O
scene O
, O
cari O
her O
go O
hospital O
for O
treatment O
of O
minor O
injuries O
. O

Port B-LOC
AFRICA I-LOC
'serial O
killer O
suspect' O
don O
plead O
guilty O
to O
murder O
Court O
sentence O
Europe B-LOC
president O
to O
20 B-DATE
years I-DATE
in O
prison O
Dem O
see O
Mollie B-PER
for O
di O
scene O
, O
cari O
her O
go O
hospital O
for O
treatment O
of O
minor O
injuries O
. O

America I-LOC
prison O
suspect' O
president O
murder O
plead O
to O
Court O
in O
20 B-DATE
don O
killer O
Dem O
'serial O
to O
Mollie B-PER
Port B-LOC
guilty O
Suriname B-LOC
see O
sentence O
years I-DATE
for O
di O
scene O
, O
cari O
her O
go O
hospital O
for O
treatment O
of O
minor O
injuries O
. O

club I-ORG
Stars I-ORG
na O
rising O
Dortmund B-ORG
Joko B-PER
with O
footballer O
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Boko B-ORG
of I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Idris B-PER
footballer O
rising O
Stars I-ORG
Remo B-ORG
with O
na O
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

marley I-PER
, O
to O
Burna B-PER
Lawyer O
Ayodeji B-PER
Mighty I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

marley I-PER
, O
Ayodeji B-PER
Lawyer O
MOG B-PER
to O
Savage I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

to O
Lawyer O
Kamaru B-PER
Fireboy I-PER
, O
Ayodeji B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

Lawyer O
to O
Naira B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
, O
Khafi B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

Lawyer O
to O
LSMK B-PER
Senaya I-PER
, O
Robbie B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

go O
organisers O
2008 B-DATE
Seoul B-LOC
7 I-DATE
NG B-LOC
performance O
Saturday B-DATE
World B-ORG
KE B-LOC
for O
De O
for O
say O
go O
visit O
den O
year I-DATE
come O
Nigeria I-LOC
on O
first O
which O
en O
happen O
Eazi I-PER
Starboy B-PER
Stadium I-LOC
. O

Glasgow B-ORG
Ghana B-LOC
last B-DATE
Wilder B-PER
year I-DATE
den O
California B-LOC
organisers O
go O
on O
Boy I-PER
come O
De O
say O
40 B-DATE
first O
visit O
: I-DATE
for O
en O
performance O
which O
go O
happen O
for O
TZ B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
York I-LOC
. O

Las B-LOC
performance O
visit O
28 B-DATE
den O
happen O
first O
Erivo I-PER
year I-DATE
come O
say O
which O
Busisiwa B-PER
on O
for O
Stadium I-LOC
for O
en O
US B-LOC
Livespot360 B-ORG
7 I-DATE
go O
Passover B-DATE
De O
organisers O
Sports I-LOC
go O
Spain B-LOC
. O

organisers O
on O
4 B-DATE
den O
first O
De O
Bayelsa B-LOC
come O
B I-PER
Ghana B-LOC
say O
UN B-ORG
Duncan B-PER
visit O
7 I-DATE
go O
October B-DATE
8 I-DATE
for O
en O
performance O
which O
go O
happen O
for O
Accra B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

year I-DATE
Saudi B-LOC
New B-LOC
68 B-DATE
den O
Cardi B-PER
go O
first O
Cannon I-PER
organisers O
De O
say O
June B-DATE
visit O
come O
Liverpool B-ORG
on O
year I-DATE
for O
en O
performance O
which O
go O
happen O
for O
Lafia B-LOC
Calabasa I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
. O

, O
di O
kontri O
all O
CAF B-ORG
Angola B-LOC
In O
while O
for O
activities O
for O
Super I-ORG
two B-DATE
addition O
Impact I-ORG
di O
don O
morning I-DATE
cancel O
football O
Eredivisie O
don O
dey O
suspended O
until O
31 B-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

two B-DATE
cancel O
di O
di O
while O
don O
weeks I-DATE
kontri O
In O
for O
for O
NCAC B-ORG
, O
addition O
Worldwide I-ORG
activities O
all O
football O
Phoenix I-ORG
Spain B-LOC
Eredivisie O
don O
dey O
suspended O
until O
dis B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

In O
addition O
, O
BBC B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Population I-ORG
don O
cancel O
all O
football O
activities O
for O
di O
kontri O
for O
dis B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
while O
di O
Western B-LOC
Eredivisie O
don O
dey O
suspended O
until O
December B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

November B-DATE
37 B-DATE
kontri O
Nigeria B-LOC
dey O
suspended O
until O
Eredivisie O
Eagles I-ORG
di O
for O
di O
, O
for O
addition O
cancel O
Association I-ORG
football O
weeks I-DATE
Danish B-ORG
all O
activities O
while O
don O
March I-DATE
In O
don O
. O

In O
addition O
, O
Nepa B-ORG
Jazzhole I-ORG
Unite I-ORG
don O
cancel O
all O
football O
activities O
for O
di O
kontri O
for O
2018 B-DATE
evening I-DATE
while O
di O
NG B-LOC
Eredivisie O
don O
dey O
suspended O
until O
July B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

The B-ORG
Tori O
United I-ORG
pipo O
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Tori O
pipo O
UFC B-ORG
Wrap I-ORG
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Tori O
pipo O
Caf B-ORG
Wrap I-ORG
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Tori O
pipo O
Actors B-ORG
Yatai I-ORG
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Abuja B-ORG
Tori O
Wrap I-ORG
pipo O
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Additional O
reporting O
by O
Wendy B-PER
Lyta I-PER
Yuniar I-PER
of O
Bournemouth B-ORG
Indonesia I-ORG

Additional O
reporting O
by O
Zlatan B-PER
Tip I-PER
Yuniar I-PER
of O
BBC B-ORG
Indonesia I-ORG

Khafi B-PER
reporting O
Merkel I-PER
Additional O
Silva I-PER
by O
of O
BBC B-ORG
Arts I-ORG

Additional O
reporting O
by O
Resty B-PER
Micsmith I-PER
Yuniar I-PER
of O
Soetrich B-ORG
Milan I-ORG

Additional O
reporting O
by O
Sontje B-PER
Daniel I-PER
Lowe I-PER
of O
BBC B-ORG
Indonesia I-ORG

DML I-PER
wey O
im O
Di O
of O
album O
African O
Kevin B-PER
na O
name O
Burna B-PER
real O
Giant O
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

Di O
African O
Giant O
album O
of O
Alex B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Max B-PER
Ebunoluwa I-PER
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

Di O
African O
Giant O
album O
of O
Burna B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Kazeem B-PER
- I-PER
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

album O
Burna B-PER
Di O
African O
of O
Giant O
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Damini B-PER
Qiang I-PER
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

Di O
African O
Giant O
album O
of O
Asisat B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Eminem B-PER
Ebunoluwa I-PER
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

Na O
because O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
rules O
wey O
relate O
to O
how O
much O
money O
dem O
dey O
allowed O
to O
spend O
. O

Dr O
Newson B-PER
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

Dr O
Harry B-PER
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

Dr O
Snoop B-PER
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

Newson B-PER
Dr O
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

While O
Nkurunziza I-PER
Victoire B-PER
win O
di O
Best O
Female O
Artiste O
for O
Western B-LOC
Paektu I-LOC
with O
her O
song O
"""" O
One O
"""" O
. O

While O
Kenneth B-PER
Savage I-PER
win O
di O
Best O
Female O
Artiste O
for O
Catalonia B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
with O
her O
song O
"""" O
One O
"""" O
. O

While O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
win O
di O
Best O
Female O
Artiste O
for O
Western B-LOC
Craft I-LOC
with O
her O
song O
"""" O
One O
"""" O
. O

Vyrusky I-PER
Gabriel B-PER
While O
win O
di O
Best O
Female O
Artiste O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
with O
her O
song O
"""" O
One O
"""" O
. O

While O
Jesus B-PER
Savage I-PER
win O
di O
Best O
Female O
Artiste O
for O
Western B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
with O
her O
song O
"""" O
One O
"""" O
. O

Smith I-PER
like O
AQ B-PER
Lily B-PER
E O
Dre I-PER
with O
, O
work O
Dungan B-PER
don O
and O
artists O
. O

E O
don O
work O
with O
artists O
like O
John B-PER
, O
Jorja B-PER
Smith I-PER
and O
Prince B-PER
Rummenigge I-PER
. O

work O
Shehu I-PER
E O
like O
, O
artists O
Burna B-PER
Celie B-PER
with O
don O
and O
Lily B-PER
Pearl I-PER
. O

Maphoriza I-PER
Beyonce B-PER
E O
work O
don O
Jorja B-PER
artists O
like O
with O
, O
and O
Lily B-PER
Allen I-PER
. O

E O
don O
work O
with O
artists O
like O
Luis B-PER
, O
Naira B-PER
Braithwaite I-PER
and O
Davido B-PER
Allen I-PER
. O

"""" O
So O
di O
only O
tin O
wey O
I O
fit O
do O
na O
to O
just O
beg O
dis O
guys O
to O
free O
my O
mama O
. O

E O
dey O
easy O
: O
some O
pipo O
dey O
drink O
- O
oda O
pipo O
dey O
choose O
to O
work O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
for O
France B-LOC
for O
two B-DATE
17 I-DATE
for O
di O
second O
division O
match O
between O
Terville B-ORG
and O
Soetrich B-ORG
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
for O
2018 B-DATE
17 I-DATE
for O
di O
second O
division O
match O
between O
Inter B-ORG
and O
Soetrich B-ORG
. O

France B-LOC
Di O
Saturday B-DATE
for O
incident O
happun O
17 I-DATE
for O
for O
di O
second O
division O
match O
between O
Blues B-ORG
and O
Soetrich B-ORG
. O

Europe B-LOC
for O
second O
for O
year I-DATE
happun O
Flamengo B-ORG
Saturday B-DATE
between O
match O
incident O
Di O
di O
for O
division O
and O
FA B-ORG
. O

for O
incident O
for O
17 I-DATE
Di O
France B-LOC
happun O
tonight B-DATE
for O
di O
second O
division O
match O
between O
Terville B-ORG
and O
HBO B-ORG
. O

Wetin O
surprise O
me O
be O
say O
nobody O
really O
look O
im O
side O
until O
Jorge B-PER
Awaziem I-PER
, O
di O
current O
Newcastle B-ORG
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
Balakov I-PER
. O

Walker I-PER
di O
surprise O
current O
Wetin O
until O
be O
nobody O
Super B-ORG
side O
im O
, O
really O
Jorge B-PER
say O
look O
me O
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
Jong I-PER
. O

football O
wetin O
surprise O
im O
, O
am O
Flamengo B-ORG
until O
current O
"""" O
say O
me O
, O
di O
nobody O
look O
sign O
Vanessa B-PER
Portuguese O
Mane I-PER
boss O
side O
Jose B-PER
na O
Wetin O
to O
be O
- I-PER
really O
decided O
writer O
. O

Wetin O
really O
surprise O
nobody O
until O
side O
me O
Joeboi B-PER
look O
im O
be O
say O
Diamond I-PER
, O
di O
current O
Flamengo B-ORG
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
- I-PER
. O

Wetin O
surprise O
me O
be O
say O
nobody O
really O
look O
im O
side O
until O
Busisiwa B-PER
Jesus I-PER
, O
di O
current O
Maccabi B-ORG
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
Delgado I-PER
. O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Jr I-PER
tell O
HBO B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

Di O
Ozedikus B-PER
feem O
director O
di O
, O
Kasum I-PER
of O
tell O
Atletico B-ORG
Police I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

di O
tell O
Obilale I-PER
, O
feem O
of O
director O
Yemi B-PER
Di O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

di O
Kayode B-PER
director O
, O
of O
Di O
feem O
Boy I-PER
tell O
Liverpool B-ORG
FC I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Azeez I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

di O
of O
year I-DATE
2018 B-DATE
for O
of I-DATE
di O
One O
- I-DATE
house O
youngest O
, O
, I-DATE
Iyke B-PER
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

October I-DATE
house O
for O
One O
, O
27 B-DATE
di O
Diamond B-PER
youngest O
old I-DATE
old I-DATE
27 I-DATE
of O
di O
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

dis I-DATE
of O
di O
youngest O
24 B-DATE
year I-DATE
One O
di O
for O
house O
December I-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Otile B-PER
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

for O
2002 B-DATE
di O
year I-DATE
of O
One O
di O
- I-DATE
house O
youngest O
, O
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
Iyke B-PER
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

One O
youngest O
, O
Monday I-DATE
house O
di O
of O
di O
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
24 B-DATE
May I-DATE
Iyke B-PER
for O
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
full O
draw O
for O
di O
Champions O
League O
last O
- O
16 O
stage O
. O

Dem O
don O
already O
film O
di O
pilot O
episode O
wey O
go O
star O
Oscar O
nominee O
Naomi B-PER
Watts I-PER
. O

Dem O
don O
already O
film O
di O
pilot O
episode O
wey O
go O
star O
Oscar O
nominee O
Naomi B-PER
- I-PER
. O

Dem O
don O
already O
film O
di O
pilot O
episode O
wey O
go O
star O
Oscar O
nominee O
David B-PER
Adjoua I-PER
. O

episode O
already O
pilot O
wey O
go O
Oscar O
Naomi B-PER
nominee O
don O
film O
star O
di O
Watts I-PER
Dem O
. O

Met O
police O
say O
dem O
call O
officers O
make O
dem O
come O
dia O
house O
for O
Singapore B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
, O
Egypt B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
40 B-DATE
: I-DATE
of I-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

officers O
come O
, O
make O
house O
shortly O
Brazil B-LOC
dem O
for O
: I-DATE
after O
police O
call O
say O
dem O
UK B-LOC
dia O
, O
Arena I-LOC
23 B-DATE
Met O
00 I-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

after O
make O
, O
say O
shortly O
dia O
- I-LOC
dem O
call O
, O
California B-LOC
police O
house O
Met O
officers O
for O
come O
23 B-DATE
Imo B-LOC
dem O
1997 I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
. O

make O
come O
house O
call O
SA B-LOC
police O
dem O
dem O
Green I-LOC
say O
officers O
Met O
, O
Las B-LOC
dia O
for O
, O
shortly O
after O
2002 B-DATE
Friday I-DATE
Day I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
. O

dia O
after O
dem O
police O
say O
, O
call O
years I-DATE
for O
shortly O
, O
dem O
: I-DATE
Kensington B-LOC
Angola B-LOC
Met O
come O
Tuesday B-DATE
Nigeria I-LOC
officers O
house O
make O
00 I-DATE
. O

Anytin O
wey O
dey O
happun O
- O
she O
go O
blame O
me O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
1950s B-DATE
, O
tins O
begin O
change O
and O
to O
dey O
play O
sport O
on O
1987 B-DATE
, I-DATE
change O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
2002 B-DATE
, O
tins O
begin O
change O
and O
to O
dey O
play O
sport O
on O
Christmas B-DATE
Day I-DATE
change O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
72 B-DATE
, O
tins O
begin O
change O
and O
to O
dey O
play O
sport O
on O
next B-DATE
Day I-DATE
change O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
26 B-DATE
, O
tins O
begin O
change O
and O
to O
dey O
play O
sport O
on O
Christmas B-DATE
Day I-DATE
change O
. O

di O
for O
Na O
1950s B-DATE
, O
tins O
begin O
change O
and O
to O
dey O
play O
sport O
on O
Christmas B-DATE
Day I-DATE
change O
. O

Bieber I-PER
Gain' O
Neptune I-PER
Diamond B-PER
Boyega I-PER
Pearl I-PER
· O
Evaristo I-PER
Black B-PER
Xolani B-PER
'Case' O
· O
Williams I-PER
Jack B-PER
Kel B-PER
- O
- O
- O
Kenny B-PER
'Ye' O
di O
· O
'Ye' O
Michael B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
, O
Shatta B-PER
- O
Wilder B-PER
'Wetin O
- O
· O
D O
- O
Next O
Chinko B-PER
Love' O
Pop O
by O
Recording O
DML I-PER
Brown I-PER
Best O
· O
We O
Fireboy I-PER
Ye O
- O
· O
'Baby' O
Boy I-PER
- O
'Fake O
Year O
· O
Producer O
Year O
Best O
King B-PER
Ire O
Single O
Pellegrini B-PER
Watts I-PER
Heal O
· O
Mikel B-PER
Herd I-PER
Vanessa B-PER
Leon B-PER
Rated O
· O
- O
'Jealous' O
UyoMeyo O
- O
ft O
- O
· O
· O
di O
- O
Gabriel B-PER
of O
of O
World O
· O
Michael B-PER
Boy I-PER
· O
Wang B-PER
- O
'Dumebi' O
by O
Rema B-PER
· O

- O
Love' O
· O
Kamaru B-PER
- O
· O
Pop O
· O
- O
- O
di O
Next O
Achraf B-PER
Gain' O
'Dumebi' O
Wurld I-PER
Ire O
· O
· O
Joko B-PER
World O
Q B-PER
Jenny I-PER
Jamilu B-PER
Rema B-PER
We O
· O
'Baby' O
ft O
· O
'Case' O
Bishop I-PER
Ye O
Single O
by O
Nyovest I-PER
Abalo I-PER
'Jealous' O
- O
'Fake O
UyoMeyo O
of O
- O
- O
FireBoy B-PER
Rema B-PER
Ozedikus B-PER
di O
Zlatan B-PER
- O
Year O
of O
· O
by O
Silva I-PER
Rogers I-PER
- O
'Ye' O
Heinz I-PER
Boy I-PER
- O
Otto B-PER
- O
Best O
Siasia I-PER
BigTril B-PER
· O
Producer O
DJ B-PER
Rated O
· O
Heal O
De I-PER
Recording O
Teni B-PER
Year O
Costello I-PER
Wilder B-PER
'Ye' O
, O
Best O
· O
- O
Burna B-PER
D O
- O
Xolani B-PER
· O
Lampard I-PER
Ighalo B-PER
Phantom B-PER
P I-PER
'Wetin O
· O
· O

, O
Ire O
Bruyne I-PER
- O
· O
Galaxy I-PER
- O
· O
'Baby' O
Best O
Year O
di O
Ye O
Kazeem B-PER
'Fake O
· O
- O
Best O
Ali B-PER
by O
Producer O
Rita B-PER
D O
· O
Eazi I-PER
Etienne B-PER
· O
of O
Heal O
ft O
· O
UyoMeyo O
- O
- O
Year O
'Ye' O
- O
- O
'Ye' O
Thembi B-PER
Arteta B-PER
'Jealous' O
Kgatlana I-PER
· O
Gunna B-PER
bond I-PER
· O
Kaybee I-PER
World O
· O
· O
Twigz I-PER
· O
Ecclestone B-PER
Single O
Pop O
Next O
di O
I I-PER
- O
Recording O
'Wetin O
Ekong I-PER
Prince B-PER
· O
Ayodele I-PER
Gedoni B-PER
Anthony B-PER
DJ B-PER
'Case' O
- O
Adebayor I-PER
We O
Iwar I-PER
- O
Rivaldo B-PER
of O
Oshoala B-PER
Zlatan B-PER
Pepe B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
- O
- O
Yemi B-PER
Gain' O
· O
Rated O
Love' O
Ozedikus B-PER
Twigz I-PER
- O
'Dumebi' O
by O
Joeboy B-PER
· O

Cobain's B-PER
Rema B-PER
'Wetin O
Jong I-PER
Enyeama B-PER
· O
- O
World O
SugarHill B-PER
Love' O
Recording O
'Jealous' O
'Jenny B-PER
Year O
· O
· O
- O
We O
- O
of O
Asinim I-PER
Phiona B-PER
Kodak B-PER
Gain' O
· O
· O
Pop O
- O
- O
- O
'Ye' O
Teni B-PER
Woro I-PER
UyoMeyo O
Ire O
Famara B-PER
Raheem B-PER
Zlatan B-PER
'Ye' O
John B-PER
· O
of O
Anice B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
- O
D O
Ye O
Best O
Best O
di O
- O
Zinhle I-PER
, O
di O
- O
· O
Heal O
- O
Sol I-PER
Boy I-PER
Producer O
· O
'Case' O
· O
Aina I-PER
Matthews I-PER
Yoel B-PER
· O
- O
YCEE B-PER
Year O
Jack B-PER
'Baby' O
Boy I-PER
Ekun I-PER
by O
Next O
· O
Victor I-PER
'Fake O
Marie B-PER
- O
· O
Rated O
ft O
Jhay I-PER
Single O
Eazi I-PER
· O
Ozedikus B-PER
- O
'Dumebi' O
by O
Nathan B-PER
· O

Domenico B-PER
UyoMeyo O
World O
· O
Riyad B-PER
M2 B-PER
, O
'Baby' O
· O
- O
- O
We O
· O
Heal O
'Fake O
Ivy I-PER
Nchout I-PER
· O
Alex B-PER
Chineme B-PER
· O
Year O
Evaristo I-PER
· O
Single O
Ighalo B-PER
West I-PER
- O
- O
Fireboy B-PER
Allen I-PER
Gain' O
- O
· O
· O
Tarek B-PER
· O
Tedela I-PER
Firmino I-PER
Rated O
'Wetin O
Samuel B-PER
- O
Ortiz B-PER
David B-PER
Amelete B-PER
'Jealous' O
Best O
- O
- O
'Ye' O
Recording O
Ilkay B-PER
· O
· O
- O
Khafi B-PER
ft O
Ire O
of O
- O
Bieber I-PER
Pop O
'Case' O
di O
Boy I-PER
Mighty I-PER
Kim B-PER
D O
Love' O
- O
Ye O
Next O
Best O
Majozi I-PER
Erivo I-PER
Boy I-PER
Producer O
of O
di O
Year O
· O
Phantom B-PER
- O
'Ye' O
by O
Joshua B-PER
Ferguson I-PER
· O
Ozedikus B-PER
- O
'Dumebi' O
by O
Rema B-PER
· O

to O
e O
between O
Ghedoni B-PER
watch O
for O
Kareem I-PER
for O
na O
Nigerian O
wedding O
anoda O
# O
Khadoni O
and O
out O
Menakaya I-PER
celeb O
wedding O
Luis B-PER
Make O
di O
nor O
loss O
, O
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Khafi B-PER
Kareem I-PER
and O
Joshua B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Khafi B-PER
Kareem I-PER
and O
Ozedikus B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

wedding O
watch O
out O
wedding O
di O
, O
for O
Kareem I-PER
celeb O
# O
for O
between O
Khadoni O
nor O
na O
e O
Nigerian O
anoda O
loss O
Make O
Khafi B-PER
to O
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Khafi B-PER
Khadoni O
for O
Martin I-PER
# O
for O
watch O
e O
nor O
to O
out O
di O
between O
anoda O
wedding O
Joshua B-PER
Make O
Nigerian O
loss O
celeb O
wedding O
, O
na O
and O
Bieber I-PER
. O

Rumours O
suggest O
say O
split O
bin O
dey O
between O
those O
for O
camp O
wey O
want O
continue O
wit O
di O
tournament O
and O
those O
wey O
want O
go O
home O
. O

Dis O
also O
no O
go O
be O
di O
first O
time O
rumour O
about O
im O
health O
go O
bring O
up O
plenty O
tok O
tok O
- O
only O
for O
dem O
to O
dismiss O
am O
later O
. O

Johnson I-PER
as O
Naira B-PER
And O
and O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
perform O
wit O
am O
dia O
, O
dem O
too O
no O
show O
. O

as O
Naira B-PER
and O
Burna B-PER
Cisse I-PER
And O
Kasum I-PER
perform O
wit O
am O
dia O
, O
dem O
too O
no O
show O
. O

And O
as O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
and O
Herb B-PER
Boy I-PER
perform O
wit O
am O
dia O
, O
dem O
too O
no O
show O
. O

And O
as O
Chineze B-PER
Joshua I-PER
and O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
perform O
wit O
am O
dia O
, O
dem O
too O
no O
show O
. O

Emeka B-PER
And O
Mounguengui I-PER
and O
as O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
perform O
wit O
am O
dia O
, O
dem O
too O
no O
show O
. O

for O
year I-DATE
19 O
test O
find O
- O
for O
wia O
26 B-DATE
old I-DATE
na O
say O
her O
older O
Covid O
every O
house O
Dem O
out O
, O
her O
dem O
and O
sister O
pesin O
artist O
manager O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Anindyajati B-PER
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

Dem O
test O
every O
pesin O
for O
her O
house O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
and O
na O
wia O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
her O
older O
sister O
, O
10 B-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
artist O
manager O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Anindyajati B-PER
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

Anindyajati B-PER
NG B-LOC
out O
, O
say O
house O
find O
wia O
, O
early B-DATE
sister O
December I-DATE
her O
for O
artist O
dem O
manager O
- O
na O
for O
test O
morning I-DATE
and O
stay O
19 O
wey O
for O
her O
dey O
Dem O
Covid O
older O
pesin O
every O
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

Dem O
test O
every O
pesin O
for O
her O
house O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
and O
na O
wia O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
her O
older O
sister O
, O
Six B-DATE
old I-DATE
June I-DATE
artist O
manager O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
NG B-LOC
, O
Anindyajati B-PER
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

Dem O
test O
every O
pesin O
for O
her O
house O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
and O
na O
wia O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
her O
older O
sister O
, O
33 B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
old I-DATE
artist O
manager O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
Anindyajati B-PER
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

For O
di O
statement O
wen O
oga O
Orlando B-PER
carry O
come O
out O
, O
e O
say O
dem O
arrest O
Duncan B-PER
Alade I-PER
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
M2 B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

dem O
Justin B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
carry O
Alyona B-PER
statement O
For O
wen O
come O
e O
di O
out O
say O
, O
arrest O
oga O
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
Rowan B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

For O
di O
statement O
wen O
oga O
Jack B-PER
carry O
come O
out O
, O
e O
say O
dem O
arrest O
Duncan B-PER
Mighty I-PER
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
M2 B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

arrest O
come O
statement O
King B-PER
out O
wen O
Mighty I-PER
e O
carry O
di O
oga O
say O
Orlando B-PER
, O
For O
dem O
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
Burna B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

Medikal B-PER
come O
wen O
statement O
, O
arrest O
Joshua B-PER
dem O
e O
di O
out O
For O
carry O
say O
oga O
Pratt I-PER
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
Barry B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

pipo O
Tori O
Chelsea B-ORG
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

Tori O
pipo O
Di B-ORG
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

Tori O
pipo O
AFP B-ORG
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

AFP B-ORG
pipo O
Tori O
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

Tori O
pipo O
China B-ORG
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

correct O
Nigerian O
Di O
Odenike B-PER
by O
director O
play O
and O
directed O
dey O
, O
written O
. O

Odenike B-PER
, O
Nigerian O
directed O
director O
Di O
play O
written O
correct O
and O
dey O
by O
. O

Di O
play O
dey O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
correct O
Nigerian O
director O
, O
MC B-PER
. O

Di O
play O
dey O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
correct O
Nigerian O
director O
, O
Odenike B-PER
. O

, O
, O
1 O
10 O
Kovac's B-PER
- O
Valerenga B-ORG
Afta O
and O
Eintracht B-ORG
lost O
in O
games O
Sporting B-ORG
Bundesliga O
campaign O
of O
carri O
behind O
to O
leaders O
Hospital I-ORG
points O
di O
5 O
fourth O
four O
Madrid I-ORG
, O
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

leaders O
, O
fourth O
1 O
James B-PER
Afta O
points O
10 O
Bayern B-ORG
, O
5 O
to O
di O
, O
campaign O
behind O
and O
Monchengladbach I-ORG
lost O
four O
of O
games O
Bundesliga O
Borussia B-ORG
- O
Frankfurt I-ORG
in O
carri O
Chelsea B-ORG
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

Afta O
10 O
games O
of O
di O
Bundesliga O
campaign O
, O
Bayern B-ORG
carri O
fourth O
, O
four O
points O
behind O
leaders O
Barcelona B-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
, O
and O
lost O
5 O
- O
1 O
to O
Terre B-ORG
England I-ORG
in O
Jess B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

Afta O
10 O
games O
of O
di O
Bundesliga O
campaign O
, O
Bollywood B-ORG
carri O
fourth O
, O
four O
points O
behind O
leaders O
Borussia B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
, O
and O
lost O
5 O
- O
1 O
to O
Twitter B-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
in O
Kovac's B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

, O
carri O
Madrid I-ORG
- O
di O
campaign O
, O
Bayern B-ORG
Leicester B-ORG
games O
News I-ORG
1 O
and O
of O
to O
Afta O
behind O
points O
Bundesliga O
Napoli B-ORG
5 O
lost O
leaders O
, O
10 O
fourth O
four O
in O
Kovac's B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

Di O
Russian O
champion O
for O
2010 B-DATE
with O
Geeks B-ORG
Germain I-ORG
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2018 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

Di O
Russian O
champion O
for O
40 B-DATE
with O
RFEF B-ORG
Mosco I-ORG
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2022 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

Di O
Russian O
champion O
for O
31 B-DATE
with O
FA B-ORG
Mosco I-ORG
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2018 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

Russian O
champion O
deh O
'GO7 O
for O
de O
statement O
for O
2015 B-DATE
hard O
with O
e O
weh O
organise O
Awards' O
Pidgin I-ORG
UFC B-ORG
for O
pipo O
prize O
compensate O
de O
award O
work O
make O
2019 B-DATE
weh O
Di O
for O
football O
season O
. O

2019 B-DATE
Di O
for O
Russian O
CSKA B-ORG
Information I-ORG
champion O
with O
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2018 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
2018 B-DATE
of I-DATE
June I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

July I-DATE
forced O
But O
to O
for O
23 B-DATE
dey O
come O
di O
e O
leave O
school O
night I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
2018 B-DATE
of I-DATE
old I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

But O
e O
school O
dey O
to O
of I-DATE
forced O
leave O
di O
for O
same B-DATE
come O
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
2017 B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
March I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

See O
oda O
pictures O
of O
some O
of O
di O
artworks O
wey O
dey O
di O
fair O
. O

doctor O
or O
teacher O
, O
"""" O
pesin O
Wen O
maybe O
tell O
NHS B-ORG
dat O
boy O
Dr B-PER
something O
educated O
wey O
, O
pipo O
"""" O
I O
becoming O
tori O
of O
I O
dream O
, O
; O
Citizen I-ORG
like O
dey O
, O
be O
young O
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

"""" O
Wen O
I O
be O
young O
boy O
, O
I O
dream O
of O
becoming O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
educated O
; O
maybe O
teacher O
, O
doctor O
or O
something O
like O
dat O
, O
"""" O
Daniela B-PER
tell O
tori O
pipo O
, O
United B-ORG
Devils I-ORG
for O
2017 B-DATE
. O

, O
Boko B-ORG
becoming O
maybe O
teacher O
dat O
pesin O
, O
for O
tori O
Wen O
be O
or O
pipo O
Citizen I-ORG
"""" O
; O
I O
dream O
boy O
like O
, O
, O
I O
doctor O
of O
something O
tell O
young O
dey O
educated O
wey O
Alvaro B-PER
40 B-DATE
"""" O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
I O
be O
young O
boy O
, O
I O
dream O
of O
becoming O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
educated O
; O
maybe O
teacher O
, O
doctor O
or O
something O
like O
dat O
, O
"""" O
ShoMadjozi B-PER
tell O
tori O
pipo O
, O
Tottenham B-ORG
FC I-ORG
for O
dis B-DATE
. O

maybe O
doctor O
or O
pesin O
UFC B-ORG
pipo O
for O
like O
, O
I O
"""" O
; O
teacher O
something O
educated O
wey O
young O
, O
, O
tell O
I O
of O
tori O
Wen O
, O
be O
dey O
"""" O
Sport I-ORG
dat O
Domenico B-PER
becoming O
dream O
boy O
2014 B-DATE
. O

E O
also O
tok O
say O
di O
movie O
as O
e O
no O
dey O
cinema O
na O
"""" O
big O
blow O
because O
di O
movie O
bin O
dey O
climb O
for O
di O
money O
e O
dey O
make O
at O
very O
high O
rate O
. O
"""" O

Dem O
no O
know O
say O
very O
soon O
dem O
go O
begin O
fight O
for O
di O
lives O
of O
everyone O
inside O
di O
California B-LOC
team O
bus O
. O

di O
for O
inside O
of O
go O
fight O
everyone O
say O
no O
soon O
di O
begin O
TZ B-LOC
very O
lives O
Dem O
know O
dem O
team O
bus O
. O

Dem O
no O
know O
say O
very O
soon O
dem O
go O
begin O
fight O
for O
di O
lives O
of O
everyone O
inside O
di O
Togo B-LOC
team O
bus O
. O

On O
Monday B-DATE
, O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

, O
Monday B-DATE
di O
On O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

On O
18 B-DATE
, O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

On O
dis B-DATE
, O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

Monday B-DATE
di O
On O
NG B-LOC
, O
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

Her O
ultimate O
love O
na O
man O
wey O
fit O
understand O
her O
deeply O
and O
fit O
accept O
her O
as O
she O
dey O
, O
both O
good O
and O
bad O
. O

Wilder B-PER
so O
President O
Na O
see O
dem O
Lafia B-LOC
Widodo I-PER
dey O
follow O
tori O
pipo O
tok O
and O
say O
dem O
be O
di O
two O
first O
cases O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
e O
no O
tok O
dia O
name O
. O

Widodo I-PER
Na O
so O
Indonesia B-LOC
see O
Joko B-PER
dem O
President O
dey O
follow O
tori O
pipo O
tok O
and O
say O
dem O
be O
di O
two O
first O
cases O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
e O
no O
tok O
dia O
name O
. O

Na O
so O
dem O
see O
Indonesia B-LOC
President O
Joko B-PER
Widodo I-PER
dey O
follow O
tori O
pipo O
tok O
and O
say O
dem O
be O
di O
two O
first O
cases O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
e O
no O
tok O
dia O
name O
. O

Na O
so O
dem O
see O
NG B-LOC
President O
Joko B-PER
Da I-PER
dey O
follow O
tori O
pipo O
tok O
and O
say O
dem O
be O
di O
two O
first O
cases O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
e O
no O
tok O
dia O
name O
. O

Na O
so O
dem O
see O
Indonesia B-LOC
President O
Cardi B-PER
Widodo I-PER
dey O
follow O
tori O
pipo O
tok O
and O
say O
dem O
be O
di O
two O
first O
cases O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
e O
no O
tok O
dia O
name O
. O

Football O
fans O
dey O
use O
Ahli B-ORG
do O
yeye O
for O
social O
media O
with O
funny O
- O
funny O
comments O
and O
memes O
afta O
dem O
crash O
out O
for O
Champions O
League O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

with O
fans O
League O
for O
crash O
Football O
on O
afta O
funny O
out O
yeye O
Champions O
do O
- O
for O
and O
dem O
social O
Everton B-ORG
media O
use O
funny O
memes O
1950s B-DATE
dey O
comments O
. O

Football O
fans O
dey O
use O
Liverpool B-ORG
do O
yeye O
for O
social O
media O
with O
funny O
- O
funny O
comments O
and O
memes O
afta O
dem O
crash O
out O
for O
Champions O
League O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Football O
fans O
dey O
use O
Lyon B-ORG
do O
yeye O
for O
social O
media O
with O
funny O
- O
funny O
comments O
and O
memes O
afta O
dem O
crash O
out O
for O
Champions O
League O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Deontay B-PER
For O
Shay I-PER
, O
2010 B-DATE
donate O
N300 O
, O
000 O
to O
help O
fans O
of O
2018 B-DATE
contestant O
, O
Ozedikus B-PER
Bruyne I-PER
vote O
for O
the O
competition O
. O

fans O
000 O
of O
- I-PER
donate O
, O
2018 B-DATE
N300 O
help O
2002 B-DATE
to O
, O
For O
Teni B-PER
contestant O
, O
Nina B-PER
Ivy I-PER
vote O
for O
the O
competition O
. O

N300 O
fans O
, O
, O
000 O
Nina B-PER
of O
26 B-DATE
For O
contestant O
donate O
Galaxy I-PER
to O
help O
Ivy I-PER
MC B-PER
, O
Thursday B-DATE
vote O
for O
the O
competition O
. O

of O
For O
N300 O
help O
donate O
to O
Saturday B-DATE
Galaxy I-PER
000 O
fans O
3 B-DATE
Elton B-PER
, O
, O
contestant O
, O
Nina B-PER
Dogg I-PER
vote O
for O
the O
competition O
. O

1960 B-DATE
donate O
Joey B-PER
, O
help O
, O
to O
contestant O
N300 O
Nina B-PER
000 O
Joshua I-PER
, O
PlatNumz I-PER
of O
34 B-DATE
fans O
For O
vote O
for O
the O
competition O
. O

Im O
be O
di O
reigning O
Caf B-ORG
footballer O
of O
di O
year O
afta O
im O
retain O
di O
crown O
for O
Friday B-DATE
. O

Im O
be O
di O
reigning O
Caf B-ORG
footballer O
of O
di O
year O
afta O
im O
retain O
di O
crown O
for O
2019 B-DATE
. O

for O
year O
crown O
of O
di O
Im O
be O
im O
di O
di O
reigning O
footballer O
Wednesday B-DATE
Caf B-ORG
retain O
afta O
. O

Im O
be O
di O
reigning O
Inter B-ORG
footballer O
of O
di O
year O
afta O
im O
retain O
di O
crown O
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

be O
di O
for O
reigning O
retain O
Im O
of O
2019 B-DATE
im O
footballer O
Sampdoria B-ORG
di O
crown O
afta O
year O
di O
. O

Nigerian O
veteran O
actress O
and O
celebrity O
, O
Colby B-PER
Henshaw I-PER
tok O
say O
oga O
Phiona B-PER
must O
give O
dem O
di O
criteria O
wey O
di O
excos O
take O
select O
di O
new O
patron O
wey O
dey O
cause O
katakata O
for O
di O
group O
. O

celebrity O
and O
Henshaw I-PER
, O
Kate B-PER
Nigerian O
actress O
veteran O
tok O
say O
oga O
Banomoya B-PER
must O
give O
dem O
di O
criteria O
wey O
di O
excos O
take O
select O
di O
new O
patron O
wey O
dey O
cause O
katakata O
for O
di O
group O
. O

Kate B-PER
and O
Nigerian O
celebrity O
tok O
Henshaw I-PER
say O
actress O
oga O
veteran O
Rollas B-PER
, O
must O
give O
dem O
di O
criteria O
wey O
di O
excos O
take O
select O
di O
new O
patron O
wey O
dey O
cause O
katakata O
for O
di O
group O
. O

Nigerian O
veteran O
actress O
and O
celebrity O
, O
'Toni B-PER
Henshaw I-PER
tok O
say O
oga O
Ederson B-PER
must O
give O
dem O
di O
criteria O
wey O
di O
excos O
take O
select O
di O
new O
patron O
wey O
dey O
cause O
katakata O
for O
di O
group O
. O

un I-PER
Nigerian O
, O
Kate B-PER
veteran O
and O
actress O
celebrity O
tok O
say O
oga O
Rollas B-PER
must O
give O
dem O
di O
criteria O
wey O
di O
excos O
take O
select O
di O
new O
patron O
wey O
dey O
cause O
katakata O
for O
di O
group O
. O

Wen O
you O
dey O
inside O
a O
situation O
like O
dat O
, O
you O
no O
go O
realize O
wetin O
dey O
happun O
to O
you O
. O

I O
feel O
say O
e O
dey O
important O
to O
protect O
my O
personal O
truth O
and O
to O
live O
my O
truth O
reach O
di O
fullest O
just O
like O
I O
don O
dey O
do O
before O
and O
I O
go O
continue O
to O
dey O
do O
. O

contest O
land O
say O
Herb B-PER
and O
step O
afta O
Hoodie I-PER
ontop O
blow O
end O
di O
But O
afta O
referee O
blow O
don O
Henshaw B-PER
contest O
inside O
wave O
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

But O
referee O
Wurld B-PER
la I-PER
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
Darmaningsih B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

But O
referee O
Herb B-PER
Fowler I-PER
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
Joshua B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
June B-DATE
. O

But O
Banksy B-PER
Potter I-PER
referee O
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
Tay B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

But O
referee O
Herb B-PER
Bieber I-PER
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
Ryan B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

Di O
World B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

WHO B-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
FC I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
Di O
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

Di O
Burnley B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

Di O
United' B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Department I-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

Di O
Daily B-ORG
Jazzhole I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

You O
go O
dey O
sweat O
. O

Di O
tok O
be O
say O
no O
be O
her O
scene O
and O
she O
no O
even O
dey O
di O
industry O
so O
why O
she O
go O
dey O
present O
for O
di O
Headies O
. O

winner O
di O
Maryam B-PER
im O
don O
actor O
im O
test O
for O
Australia B-LOC
Hanks I-PER
positive O
and O
- O
wife O
Ighalo B-PER
Ogbonge O
Wilson I-PER
tell O
world O
Oscar O
say O
coronavirus O
pipo O
for O
. O

world O
don O
Ogbonge O
for O
im O
pipo O
tell O
and O
actor O
Kamaru B-PER
Kansas B-LOC
test O
im O
Rita B-PER
winner O
Wilson I-PER
wife O
coronavirus O
positive O
for O
Oscar O
di O
say O
P I-PER
- O
. O

wife O
im O
Ogbonge O
say O
pipo O
Fiege I-PER
im O
- O
winner O
Tiwa B-PER
Pellegrini B-PER
tell O
and O
Oscar O
actor O
world O
Nchout I-PER
don O
test O
positive O
for O
di O
coronavirus O
for O
Australia B-LOC
. O

Ogbonge O
Oscar O
- O
winner O
actor O
Kazeem B-PER
Hanks I-PER
tell O
world O
pipo O
say O
im O
and O
im O
wife O
Rita B-PER
Wilson I-PER
don O
test O
positive O
for O
di O
coronavirus O
for O
Australia B-LOC
. O

Ogbonge O
Oscar O
- O
winner O
actor O
Victor B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
tell O
world O
pipo O
say O
im O
and O
im O
wife O
Rita B-PER
Wilson I-PER
don O
test O
positive O
for O
di O
coronavirus O
for O
France B-LOC
. O

of O
value O
gree O
me O
Argentina B-LOC
wey O
Rohr I-PER
from O
, O
remove O
Soundcity B-ORG
( O
Craft I-LOC
I O
put O
dey O
behind O
billion O
opposite O
The B-ORG
General O
for O
, O
dem O
and O
- O
for O
make O
wetin O
me O
I O
di O
8 O
Dollars O
Africa I-LOC
N9 O
( O
BBC B-ORG
wey O
KENYA B-LOC
"""" O
because O
wey O
Na O
di O
"""" O
with O
parastatal O
AFRICA I-LOC
some O
pipo O
no O
27 O
03 O
me O
be O
do O
Gym I-ORG
na O
Studio I-ORG
of O
. O
of I-ORG
vex O
- O
Di O
, O
so O
why O
reason O
want O
Film I-ORG
dey O
want O
) O
office O
of O
Otunba O
Rosie B-PER
dem O
) O
prison O
Health I-ORG
Director O
and I-ORG
Ministry I-ORG
, O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

some O
because O
"""" O
Madrid I-ORG
want O
( O
Director O
vex O
dey O
. O
opposite O
billion O
from O
behind O
Otunba O
dem O
, O
office O
do O
Di O
( O
dem O
be O
"""" O
pipo O
Times I-ORG
di O
- O
America I-LOC
and O
with O
) O
of I-ORG
, O
me O
I O
Mario B-PER
Dollars O
gree O
Sierra B-LOC
reason O
put O
Hakimi I-PER
why O
no O
wey O
Twitter B-ORG
Na O
) O
wey O
N9 O
for O
Schalke B-ORG
South I-LOC
of O
for O
so O
8 O
for O
parastatal O
and I-ORG
remove O
General O
make O
, O
27 O
LA B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
tori O
TZ B-LOC
City I-ORG
me O
want O
, O
na O
wetin O
dey O
me O
wey O
- O
UK B-LOC
tell O
I O
of O
and I-LOC
value O
of O
prison O
Super I-ORG
03 O
di O
pipo O
. O

Stadium I-LOC
US B-LOC
, O
) O
. O
value O
N9 O
of O
"""" O
Di O
parastatal O
wey O
office O
want O
put O
Platnumz I-PER
wey O
me O
( O
Manchester B-ORG
- O
no O
- I-LOC
vex O
"""" O
dey O
me O
wetin O
remove O
of O
, O
opposite O
27 O
di O
gree O
so O
for O
Pidgin I-ORG
03 O
di O
some O
with O
Director O
I O
why O
) O
di I-ORG
prison O
na O
wey O
dey O
dem O
pipo O
because O
make O
, O
for O
reason O
of O
Na O
want O
billion O
( O
Rihanna B-PER
Fifa B-ORG
dem O
I O
NG B-LOC
Dollars O
Department I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
hotel I-LOC
do O
8 O
Otunba O
me O
be O
behind O
from O
- O
General O
and O
Udinese B-ORG
Ministry I-ORG
and I-ORG
federation I-ORG
, O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

be O
wey O
South B-LOC
Madrid I-ORG
Otunba O
pipo O
Blues B-ORG
wey O
want O
want O
I O
, O
Senegal B-LOC
West B-ORG
dem O
Director O
Wilder B-PER
dem O
( O
reason O
03 O
no O
Pidgin I-ORG
, O
) O
some O
na O
with O
dey O
of O
Information I-ORG
wey O
Leone I-LOC
me O
and O
office O
vex O
gree O
Craft I-LOC
prison O
"""" O
for O
- O
billion O
wetin O
Na O
Wrap I-ORG
Dollars O
dey O
of O
because O
value O
Manchester B-ORG
remove O
for O
Indonesia I-ORG
Calabasa I-LOC
"""" O
put O
Runsewe I-PER
( O
of O
so O
N9 O
do O
I O
me O
opposite O
di O
me O
8 O
behind O
from O
parastatal O
General O
make O
Union I-ORG
, O
Box I-ORG
- O
) O
why O
. O
di O
27 O
Di O
, O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

Director O
27 O
with O
David B-PER
, O
of O
United I-ORG
and O
me O
Island I-LOC
for O
wey O
parastatal O
Na O
General O
remove O
make O
Lagos B-LOC
reason O
I O
di O
Federal B-ORG
of I-ORG
03 O
dey O
) O
dey O
some O
wey O
. O
value O
from O
want O
of O
of O
Di O
so O
) O
for O
billion O
Monada I-PER
be O
na O
why O
no O
, O
dem O
Championship I-ORG
"""" O
gree O
me O
wey O
NG B-LOC
Black I-ORG
office O
- O
( O
put O
"""" O
want O
Manchester B-ORG
- O
8 O
because O
Sports I-LOC
( O
Africa I-LOC
dem O
wetin O
N9 O
opposite O
me O
Otunba O
do O
I O
, O
prison O
pipo O
behind O
South B-ORG
di O
Dollars O
vex O
FC I-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
, O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

Deontay B-PER
, O
Cardi B-PER
from O
Johnny B-PER
Boy I-PER
guest O
, O
Boogie I-PER
Mane I-PER
, O
and O
artist O
, O
, O
Shatta B-PER
Kryvuliak I-PER
, O
Wale I-PER
Kazeem B-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
Silva I-PER
Teni B-PER
, O
Nandy B-PER
Yonda B-PER
Fireboy B-PER
Summer B-PER
many O
Hoodie I-PER
Kubrat B-PER
, O
feature O
, O
. O

, O
, O
Zlatan B-PER
Wallin I-PER
Chaplin B-PER
, O
, O
Justin B-PER
many O
Brown I-PER
, O
Rayvanny B-PER
, O
Savage I-PER
artist O
TNS B-PER
feature O
Kuami B-PER
Abraham I-PER
Shatta B-PER
from O
guest O
Afeez B-PER
Ekun I-PER
, O
Prince B-PER
Guardiola B-PER
, O
, O
Leon B-PER
Spinall I-PER
Salah I-PER
and O
Jess B-PER
. O

feature O
guest O
many O
Tom B-PER
artist O
Ortiz B-PER
from O
, O
Anderson B-PER
, O
Buhari B-PER
, O
Patoranking B-PER
Nkurunziza I-PER
, O
Barry B-PER
, O
Tiwa B-PER
RR I-PER
, O
Burna B-PER
Tejuoso I-PER
, O
Burna B-PER
, O
Dremo B-PER
, O
Joe B-PER
Boogie I-PER
Jr I-PER
Marley I-PER
Hoodie I-PER
and O
Yonda B-PER
. O

, O
Adjoua I-PER
, O
Tyasutami B-PER
, O
Wizkid B-PER
A B-PER
Jenny B-PER
Maphoriza I-PER
from O
Prince B-PER
feature O
, O
artist O
MC B-PER
, O
M B-PER
Wurld I-PER
Thembi B-PER
Duncan B-PER
, O
, O
Oluwasemilogo B-PER
, O
Osimhen B-PER
guest O
Cookey I-PER
, O
many O
Boy I-PER
McGregor I-PER
Fashola I-PER
and O
Yonda B-PER
. O

Aboudi B-PER
JoeBoy B-PER
, O
, O
GoodGirl B-PER
, O
Max B-PER
, O
Ogbolu I-PER
Biya B-PER
, O
Boogey B-PER
Mikel B-PER
Tiwa B-PER
Nkurunziza I-PER
Kamaru B-PER
, O
, O
many O
Tiwa B-PER
Salah I-PER
artist O
from O
Platnumz I-PER
guest O
feature O
and O
Qiang I-PER
Brothers I-PER
Qiang I-PER
, O
Rahman B-PER
, O
Holyfield B-PER
. O

one O
im O
national O
go O
wey O
di O
am O
animal O
from O
go O
say O
about O
Leone I-LOC
chimpanzees O
movie O
im O
and O
premiere O
visit O
di O
chimpanzee O
of O
wey O
di O
come O
sanctuary O
mama O
Abuja B-LOC
be O
attend O
actor O
be O
foolow O
Dariya B-LOC
later O
Tori O
of O
, O
, O
Tacugama B-LOC
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
actor O
wey O
im O
mama O
come O
from O
Sagamu B-LOC
go O
foolow O
am O
attend O
di O
premiere O
of O
one O
movie O
about O
chimpanzees O
, O
wey O
be O
GH B-LOC
Leone I-LOC
national O
animal O
, O
and O
im O
go O
later O
visit O
di O
chimpanzee O
sanctuary O
of O
Tacugama B-LOC
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
actor O
wey O
im O
mama O
come O
from O
Ghana B-LOC
go O
foolow O
am O
attend O
di O
premiere O
of O
one O
movie O
about O
chimpanzees O
, O
wey O
be O
US B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
national O
animal O
, O
and O
im O
go O
later O
visit O
di O
chimpanzee O
sanctuary O
of O
Africa B-LOC
. O

foolow O
visit O
one O
, O
am O
Tori O
and O
come O
Tacugama B-LOC
national O
of O
premiere O
be O
chimpanzee O
mama O
go O
wey O
di O
later O
of O
say O
sanctuary O
attend O
be O
di O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
from O
Leone I-LOC
animal O
im O
actor O
about O
Ghana B-LOC
movie O
wey O
im O
go O
chimpanzees O
, O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
actor O
wey O
im O
mama O
come O
from O
Senegal B-LOC
go O
foolow O
am O
attend O
di O
premiere O
of O
one O
movie O
about O
chimpanzees O
, O
wey O
be O
Sierra B-LOC
Leone I-LOC
national O
animal O
, O
and O
im O
go O
later O
visit O
di O
chimpanzee O
sanctuary O
of O
Ivoriy B-LOC
. O

Di O
former O
midfielder O
sabi O
speak O
plenty O
language O
dem O
, O
im O
dey O
speak O
Spanish O
, O
Basque O
, O
Catalan O
and O
English O
well O
- O
well O
. O

equalise O
Moorer I-PER
Tessa B-PER
wey O
to O
convert O
Italy B-LOC
come O
striker O
later O
Diedhiou I-PER
Famara B-PER
Senegal B-LOC
for O
win O
penarity O
. O

penarity O
Mane I-PER
striker O
wey O
Frank B-PER
come O
later O
NG B-LOC
Skibii B-PER
win O
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Peckham B-LOC
. O

later O
striker O
penarity O
wey O
Aboudi B-PER
Nonso I-PER
NG B-LOC
win O
Famara B-PER
come O
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Cassper B-PER
Mane I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Andy B-PER
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
. O

Kansas B-LOC
Ighalo B-PER
Platinumz I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Anthony B-PER
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
. O

Di O
experience O
don O
change O
dia O
life O
forever O
. O

tell O
team O
immediately O
known O
best O
- O
tok O
player O
say O
me O
dia O
- O
pesin O
wey O
someone O
to O
Manchester B-ORG
ask O
di O
to O
- O
na O
, O
speak O
I O
tok O
dem O
be O
City I-ORG
star O
Emmanuel B-PER
Wallin I-PER
. O

star O
ask O
best O
tell O
known O
be O
immediately O
- O
team O
pesin O
say O
- O
dem O
dia O
Jr I-PER
Emmanuel B-PER
me O
someone O
speak O
na O
I O
player O
tok O
to O
wey O
, O
to O
Arsenal B-ORG
tok O
United I-ORG
- O
di O
. O

Lakers I-ORG
wey O
tok O
immediately O
ask O
to O
dem O
speak O
player O
say O
na O
me O
pesin O
tok O
star O
team O
dia O
- O
Ighalo B-PER
known O
di O
tell O
best O
Lowe I-PER
- O
someone O
to O
be O
, O
I O
- O
Manchester B-ORG
. O

I O
ask O
to O
speak O
to O
someone O
, O
dem O
immediately O
tell O
me O
say O
di O
team O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
na O
dia O
best O
- O
known O
player O
- O
wey O
be O
Manchester B-ORG
07 I-ORG
star O
Zlatan B-PER
Adebayor I-PER
. O

I O
ask O
to O
speak O
to O
someone O
, O
dem O
immediately O
tell O
me O
say O
di O
team O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
na O
dia O
best O
- O
known O
player O
- O
wey O
be O
AC B-ORG
Albion I-ORG
star O
Oluwasemilogo B-PER
Adebayor I-PER
. O

Police O
make O
sure O
say O
fans O
no O
gada O
outside O
. O

Kaffy B-PER
wey O
be O
dancer O
like O
her O
also O
comment O
. O

inside O
Las B-LOC
, O
Osimhen I-PER
Master B-PER
fight O
Cuba B-LOC
Unesco B-ORG
245 O
Andy B-PER
Welterweight O
octagon O
Eno I-PER
go O
for O
champion O
for O
Vegas I-LOC
, O
Jakarta's B-LOC
arena I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Welterweight O
champion O
Kelvynboy B-PER
bond I-PER
, O
go O
fight O
AQ B-PER
Boy I-PER
for O
Geeks B-ORG
245 O
inside O
octagon O
for O
Togo B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
, O
US B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

champion O
Fury B-PER
Welterweight O
US B-LOC
Ortiz I-PER
, O
go O
fight O
Khafi B-PER
un I-PER
for O
Fifa B-ORG
245 O
inside O
octagon O
for O
England B-LOC
Village I-LOC
, O
Catalonia B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
. O

on O
fight O
inside O
France B-LOC
for O
Bieber I-PER
245 O
Saturday B-DATE
for O
MMA B-ORG
Lagos B-LOC
champion O
Sadio B-PER
Welterweight O
octagon O
, O
go O
Anthony B-PER
Vegas I-LOC
United B-LOC
, O
Platnumz I-PER
Bridge I-LOC
old I-DATE
. O

Monada I-PER
Welterweight O
east I-LOC
for O
States I-LOC
Libya B-LOC
Stone I-PER
Terville B-ORG
inside O
Burna B-PER
octagon O
Diamond B-PER
go O
NG B-LOC
, O
fight O
, O
245 O
champion O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
on O
dis B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
great O
- O
nothing O
better O
pass O
make O
you O
prove O
pipo O
wrong O
. O

Oga O
Ancelotti B-PER
neva O
face O
Chelsea B-ORG
wey O
im O
manage O
between O
2009 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

wey O
neva O
Anthony B-PER
Oga O
Liverpool B-ORG
manage O
face O
im O
72 B-DATE
between O
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

Oga O
face O
between O
19 B-DATE
im O
manage O
neva O
wey O
Ancelotti B-PER
BBC B-ORG
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

neva O
Oga O
im O
manage O
Chelsea B-ORG
between O
wey O
2009 B-DATE
face O
Naira B-PER
and O
29 B-DATE
before O
. O

Oga O
Ancelotti B-PER
neva O
face O
Terre B-ORG
wey O
im O
manage O
between O
2009 B-DATE
and O
2020 B-DATE
before O
. O

for O
on O
tour O
NG B-LOC
group O
"""" O
Di O
dey O
, O
but O
dem O
don O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
e O
affect O
dia O
mood O
well O
- O
well O
becos O
di O
group O
na O
family O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Di O
group O
dey O
on O
tour O
for O
US B-LOC
, O
but O
dem O
don O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
e O
affect O
dia O
mood O
well O
- O
well O
becos O
di O
group O
na O
family O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Di O
group O
dey O
on O
tour O
for O
Italy B-LOC
, O
but O
dem O
don O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
e O
affect O
dia O
mood O
well O
- O
well O
becos O
di O
group O
na O
family O
. O
"""" O

tour O
on O
"""" O
US B-LOC
group O
Di O
for O
dey O
, O
but O
dem O
don O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
e O
affect O
dia O
mood O
well O
- O
well O
becos O
di O
group O
na O
family O
. O
"""" O

For O
2018 B-DATE
, O
di O
actor O
bin O
post O
for O
Bollywood B-ORG
say O
im O
get O
endocrine O
tumour O
, O
one O
sickness O
wey O
dey O
affect O
cells O
for O
pesin O
body O
wey O
dey O
release O
hormones O
inside O
di O
bloodstream O
. O

For O
2004 B-DATE
, O
di O
actor O
bin O
post O
for O
Everton B-ORG
say O
im O
get O
endocrine O
tumour O
, O
one O
sickness O
wey O
dey O
affect O
cells O
for O
pesin O
body O
wey O
dey O
release O
hormones O
inside O
di O
bloodstream O
. O

For O
2018 B-DATE
, O
di O
actor O
bin O
post O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
say O
im O
get O
endocrine O
tumour O
, O
one O
sickness O
wey O
dey O
affect O
cells O
for O
pesin O
body O
wey O
dey O
release O
hormones O
inside O
di O
bloodstream O
. O

For O
night B-DATE
, O
di O
actor O
bin O
post O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
say O
im O
get O
endocrine O
tumour O
, O
one O
sickness O
wey O
dey O
affect O
cells O
for O
pesin O
body O
wey O
dey O
release O
hormones O
inside O
di O
bloodstream O
. O

For O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
di O
actor O
bin O
post O
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
say O
im O
get O
endocrine O
tumour O
, O
one O
sickness O
wey O
dey O
affect O
cells O
for O
pesin O
body O
wey O
dey O
release O
hormones O
inside O
di O
bloodstream O
. O

Na O
once O
a O
day O
dis O
kind O
tin O
dey O
happun O
or O
even O
evri O
oda O
day O
. O

send O
3 O
go O
e O
But O
say O
go O
extra O
Vegas I-LOC
, O
000 O
, O
troops O
Middle B-LOC
US B-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Iran B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

But O
e O
say O
, O
US B-LOC
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
NG B-LOC
East I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Iran B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

Green I-LOC
US B-LOC
, O
in O
3 O
Middle B-LOC
, O
because O
But O
wan O
Sagamu B-LOC
extra O
case O
go O
000 O
anytin O
happun O
say O
send O
troops O
go O
e O
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

But O
e O
say O
, O
US B-LOC
go O
send O
3 O
, O
000 O
extra O
troops O
go O
Nigeria B-LOC
city I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Senegal B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

3 O
troops O
go O
send O
say O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
But O
000 O
US B-LOC
, O
extra O
e O
go O
Harcourt I-LOC
in O
case O
anytin O
wan O
happun O
because O
Iran B-LOC
don O
promise O
"""" O
severe O
revenge O
"""" O
for O
pipo O
wey O
get O
hand O
for O
di O
General O
death O
. O

Dat O
na O
why O
tori O
dey O
fly O
upandan O
weda O
di O
City B-ORG
top O
players O
go O
leave O
. O

upandan O
di O
Dat O
tori O
weda O
na O
fly O
Sporting B-ORG
dey O
why O
top O
players O
go O
leave O
. O

tori O
na O
upandan O
why O
weda O
Dat O
fly O
dey O
di O
City B-ORG
top O
players O
go O
leave O
. O

Tyasutami B-PER
tok O
say O
make O
tori O
pipo O
take O
responsibility O
for O
wetin O
dia O
tori O
of O
her O
coronavirus O
finding O
cause O
her O
family O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
4th O
edition O
of O
di O
show O
wey O
don O
feature O
Wilder B-PER
, O
Burna B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
, O
Teni B-PER
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

don O
, O
na O
Dis O
Davido B-PER
4th O
show O
di O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
, O
Fireboy B-PER
wey O
feature O
of O
di O
edition O
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

Boy I-PER
na O
don O
4th O
Dis O
di O
Duncan B-PER
show O
di O
of O
edition O
wey O
feature O
, O
Lil B-PER
, O
Teni B-PER
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

na O
Raheem B-PER
Dis O
, O
feature O
of O
wey O
edition O
di O
don O
show O
Burna B-PER
4th O
Teni B-PER
Boy I-PER
, O
di O
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

Dis O
Eazi I-PER
don O
Davido B-PER
di O
4th O
Burna B-PER
edition O
of O
show O
na O
di O
, O
wey O
feature O
, O
Teni B-PER
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

Di O
72 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
star O
wey O
still O
be O
one O
of O
di O
most O
in O
demand O
live O
musicians O
for O
world O
receive O
plenti O
sympathy O
for O
social O
media O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

January B-DATE
Di O
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
star O
wey O
still O
be O
one O
of O
di O
most O
in O
demand O
live O
musicians O
for O
world O
receive O
plenti O
sympathy O
for O
social O
media O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

Di O
2022 B-DATE
year I-DATE
hours I-DATE
star O
wey O
still O
be O
one O
of O
di O
most O
in O
demand O
live O
musicians O
for O
world O
receive O
plenti O
sympathy O
for O
social O
media O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

Di O
2009 B-DATE
year I-DATE
Monday I-DATE
star O
wey O
still O
be O
one O
of O
di O
most O
in O
demand O
live O
musicians O
for O
world O
receive O
plenti O
sympathy O
for O
social O
media O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

19 B-DATE
na O
of O
Dis O
di O
winners O
Africa B-LOC
di O
Movie O
Academy O
Awards O
( O
AMAA O
) O
wey O
shele O
on O
last B-DATE
October I-DATE
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

winners O
shele O
di O
2019 B-DATE
, O
( O
Academy O
for O
Dis O
years I-DATE
wey O
of O
Awards O
na O
AMAA O
today B-DATE
di O
) O
on O
Movie O
Philadelphia B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
Africa B-LOC
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
winners O
of O
di O
2005 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Movie O
Academy O
Awards O
( O
AMAA O
) O
wey O
shele O
on O
27 B-DATE
October I-DATE
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Diriyah B-LOC
. O

Movie O
di O
83 I-DATE
wey O
AMAA O
shele O
, O
( O
) O
winners O
Awards O
on O
Dis O
Africa B-LOC
na O
Lagos B-LOC
2022 B-DATE
Academy O
7 B-DATE
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
of O
di O
. O

winners O
di O
2014 B-DATE
na O
of O
di O
Dis O
Africa B-LOC
Movie O
Academy O
Awards O
( O
AMAA O
) O
wey O
shele O
on O
Friday B-DATE
October I-DATE
for O
Lorraine B-LOC
, O
Netherlands' B-LOC
. O

dem O
Na O
dem O
go O
test O
transfer O
Covid O
Alan B-PER
dem O
IMF B-ORG
insist O
and O
come O
make O
19 O
her O
do O
say O
- O
when O
Organization I-ORG
, O
Angola B-LOC
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

Na O
when O
Tyasutami B-PER
insist O
say O
make O
dem O
do O
her O
Covid O
- O
19 O
test O
and O
dem O
come O
transfer O
dem O
go O
Sulianti B-ORG
Saroso I-ORG
, O
Jakarta's B-LOC
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

Na O
when O
Casey B-PER
insist O
say O
make O
dem O
do O
her O
Covid O
- O
19 O
test O
and O
dem O
come O
transfer O
dem O
go O
Sulianti B-ORG
Saroso I-ORG
, O
Jakarta's B-LOC
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

dem O
Duncan B-PER
- O
Covid O
do O
dem O
Sulianti B-ORG
say O
make O
her O
19 O
and O
go O
insist O
come O
test O
transfer O
when O
Na O
dem O
Saroso I-ORG
, O
Jakarta's B-LOC
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

dem O
Sulianti B-ORG
Joshua B-PER
Covid O
go O
do O
when O
and O
Jakarta's B-LOC
19 O
say O
dem O
Saroso I-ORG
test O
dem O
come O
transfer O
Na O
, O
her O
- O
make O
insist O
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
for O
di O
stadium O
car O
park O
. O
