"""" O
E O
no O
go O
dey O
possible O
, O
whether O
to O
practice O
sport O
for O
covered O
places O
, O
nor O
team O
or O
contact O
sports O
. O
"""" O

Initially O
tori O
spread O
say O
im O
die O
too O
. O

oga O
Wen O
ask O
one O
fan O
Runsewe B-PER
weda O
dem O
get O
any O
plan O
for O
more O
LGBT O
characters O
inside O
World B-ORG
feems O
, O
especially O
di O
T O
, O
trans O
characters O
, O
e O
reply O
say O
"""" O
Yes O
, O
absolutely O
. O

ask O
one O
Wen O
oga O
fan O
Fiege B-PER
weda O
dem O
get O
any O
plan O
for O
more O
LGBT O
characters O
inside O
Marvel B-ORG
feems O
, O
especially O
di O
T O
, O
trans O
characters O
, O
e O
reply O
say O
"""" O
Yes O
, O
absolutely O
. O

Wen O
one O
fan O
ask O
oga O
Kenny B-PER
weda O
dem O
get O
any O
plan O
for O
more O
LGBT O
characters O
inside O
Spanish B-ORG
feems O
, O
especially O
di O
T O
, O
trans O
characters O
, O
e O
reply O
say O
"""" O
Yes O
, O
absolutely O
. O

Wen O
one O
fan O
ask O
oga O
Fiege B-PER
weda O
dem O
get O
any O
plan O
for O
more O
LGBT O
characters O
inside O
Marvel B-ORG
feems O
, O
especially O
di O
T O
, O
trans O
characters O
, O
e O
reply O
say O
"""" O
Yes O
, O
absolutely O
. O

Wen O
one O
fan O
ask O
oga O
M2 B-PER
weda O
dem O
get O
any O
plan O
for O
more O
LGBT O
characters O
inside O
Marvel B-ORG
feems O
, O
especially O
di O
T O
, O
trans O
characters O
, O
e O
reply O
say O
"""" O
Yes O
, O
absolutely O
. O

Dem O
say O
Twitter B-ORG
bin O
claim O
Kazeem B-PER
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

Dem O
say O
BBC B-ORG
bin O
claim O
Kazeem B-PER
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

Dem O
say O
Real B-ORG
bin O
claim O
Kazeem B-PER
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

Rollas B-PER
claim O
bin O
say O
Dem O
SARS B-ORG
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

bin O
Ighalo B-PER
say O
BBC B-ORG
Dem O
claim O
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

For O
next B-DATE
and I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Mel B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

Soetrich B-ORG
For O
, O
age B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
AQ B-PER
Neptune I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

coach O
and O
former O
, O
midfielder O
: I-DATE
Frank B-PER
For O
, O
Lampard I-PER
one B-DATE
Chelsea B-ORG
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

For O
2019 B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Justin B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

2020 B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
For O
, O
LFP B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

Authorities O
don O
say O
now O
dem O
go O
look O
di O
mata O
and O
investigate O
. O

Snoop B-PER
Salah I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

Salah I-PER
Mohamed B-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

Warryn B-PER
Salah I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Neptune I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

Yemi B-PER
Adegoke I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

, O
na O
wey O
be O
NG B-LOC
from O
wey O
boxing O
years I-DATE
be O
and O
IBF O
Joshua B-PER
come O
him O
- O
, O
join O
38 B-DATE
say O
S2Kizzy B-PER
body O
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

Joshua B-PER
from O
, O
Bulgaria B-LOC
come O
years I-DATE
since B-DATE
be O
wey O
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

from O
come O
be O
Duncan B-PER
, O
four B-DATE
wey O
South B-LOC
weeks I-DATE
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

be O
wey O
38 B-DATE
Daniela B-PER
October I-DATE
, O
come O
from O
India B-LOC
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

Henry B-PER
wey O
be O
dis B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
come O
from O
Bulgaria B-LOC
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

forced O
But O
come O
, I-DATE
leave O
to O
school O
30 B-DATE
di O
dey O
e O
for O
30 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

Yesterday B-DATE
leave O
dey O
for O
forced O
But O
come O
of I-DATE
school O
di O
to O
e O
months I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

forced O
to O
e O
come O
for O
school O
leave O
But O
eight B-DATE
dey O
di O
30 I-DATE
20 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

1967 I-DATE
Dis B-DATE
, O
every O
suppose O
click O
especially O
after O
Prime O
Minister O
Anthony B-PER
Johnson I-PER
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

click O
every O
Prime O
year I-DATE
Minister O
after O
Boris B-PER
suppose O
Dis B-DATE
Johnson I-PER
especially O
, O
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

especially O
old I-DATE
, O
Dis B-DATE
every O
Minister O
after O
DJ B-PER
suppose O
click O
Prime O
Johnson I-PER
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

Johnson I-PER
especially O
November B-DATE
Prime O
December I-DATE
after O
Minister O
every O
, O
Yemi B-PER
suppose O
click O
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

2015 B-DATE
21 I-DATE
, O
every O
suppose O
click O
especially O
after O
Prime O
Minister O
Boris B-PER
Savage I-PER
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

But O
di O
last O
time O
wey O
Cobain's B-PER
coach O
for O
Premier O
League O
nothing O
like O
VAR O
bin O
dey O
for O
England B-LOC
. O

League O
Premier O
nothing O
But O
time O
dey O
for O
wey O
last O
England B-LOC
Khafi B-PER
coach O
for O
di O
VAR O
like O
bin O
. O

But O
di O
last O
time O
wey O
Mourinho B-PER
coach O
for O
Premier O
League O
nothing O
like O
VAR O
bin O
dey O
for O
England B-LOC
. O

di O
But O
wey O
time O
Mourinho B-PER
last O
coach O
for O
Premier O
League O
nothing O
like O
VAR O
bin O
dey O
for O
England B-LOC
. O

But O
di O
last O
time O
wey O
Mourinho B-PER
coach O
for O
Premier O
League O
nothing O
like O
VAR O
bin O
dey O
for O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Actors B-ORG
of O
im O
Rollas B-PER
Gedoni I-PER
Before O
im O
part O
as O
dia O
new O
join O
bin O
dey O
manager O
coaching O
staff O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

join O
im O
Arsenal B-ORG
Before O
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
im O
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
Nkechi B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
coaching O
staff O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
football I-ORG
. O

dey O
Guardiola I-PER
coaching O
im O
Dani B-PER
for O
new O
bin O
City I-ORG
of O
join O
Before O
staff O
part O
twitter B-ORG
im O
manager O
as O
dia O
Manchester B-ORG
. O

Before O
im O
join O
Uefa B-ORG
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
im O
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
Patricia B-PER
Hill I-PER
coaching O
staff O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Before O
im O
join O
Uefa B-ORG
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
im O
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
Joseph B-PER
Kochemyrovska I-PER
coaching O
staff O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

golden O
Dis O
2020 I-DATE
di O
Yesterday B-DATE
na O
wey O
pipo O
( O
well O
some O
pipo O
) O
don O
dey O
shout O
, O
dey O
expect O
in O
a O
very O
long O
time O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
golden O
one B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
wey O
pipo O
( O
well O
some O
pipo O
) O
don O
dey O
shout O
, O
dey O
expect O
in O
a O
very O
long O
time O
. O

38 B-DATE
Dis O
di O
golden O
2020 I-DATE
na O
wey O
pipo O
( O
well O
some O
pipo O
) O
don O
dey O
shout O
, O
dey O
expect O
in O
a O
very O
long O
time O
. O

Dis O
di O
November B-DATE
golden O
na O
2020 I-DATE
wey O
pipo O
( O
well O
some O
pipo O
) O
don O
dey O
shout O
, O
dey O
expect O
in O
a O
very O
long O
time O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
golden O
year B-DATE
of I-DATE
wey O
pipo O
( O
well O
some O
pipo O
) O
don O
dey O
shout O
, O
dey O
expect O
in O
a O
very O
long O
time O
. O

E O
English O
Christmas B-DATE
football O
to O
15 I-DATE
return O
year I-DATE
half I-DATE
year I-DATE
afta O
Chelsea B-ORG
sack O
am O
. O

December I-DATE
Chelsea B-ORG
E O
English O
return O
Friday I-DATE
11 B-DATE
to O
afta O
football O
March I-DATE
years I-DATE
sack O
am O
. O

return O
Day I-DATE
weeks I-DATE
football O
English O
years I-DATE
1990 B-DATE
December I-DATE
E O
to O
afta O
Brighton B-ORG
sack O
am O
. O

E O
return O
to O
English O
football O
Saturday B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
May I-DATE
year I-DATE
hours I-DATE
afta O
Chelsea B-ORG
sack O
am O
. O

football O
Chelsea B-ORG
eight B-DATE
March I-DATE
afta O
: I-DATE
E O
2019 I-DATE
English O
of I-DATE
return O
to O
sack O
am O
. O

Former O
research O
don O
show O
say O
heart O
attack O
among O
fans O
wen O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
important O
match O
dey O
increases O
weda O
dem O
dey O
support O
di O
club O
or O
dia O
kontri O
. O

for O
Former O
Ronaldinho B-PER
police O
forward O
custody O
dey O
Paraguay B-LOC
Senegal B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Mikel B-PER
Africa B-LOC
forward O
Former O
Paraguay B-LOC
for O
custody O
dey O
police O
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Former O
Africa B-LOC
forward O
Tay B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Former O
NG B-LOC
forward O
YCEE B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Former O
Europe B-LOC
forward O
Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

DJ B-PER
sister O
, O
Mourinho B-PER
Potter I-PER
- I-PER
jong I-PER
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

, O
Sarkodie B-PER
jong I-PER
Campbell I-PER
sister O
Kim B-PER
Yo I-PER
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
sister O
, O
Kim B-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
- I-PER
jong I-PER
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

, O
sister O
Henshaw B-PER
George I-PER
jong I-PER
Kim B-PER
- I-PER
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

jong I-PER
Kim B-PER
, O
Mary I-PER
Kim B-PER
Elba I-PER
sister O
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

- O
Piku B-PER
to O
victory O
first O
wit O
ring O
over O
Cerrone I-PER
di O
Firmino I-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
round O
fan O
retun O
octagon O
American O
Alade B-PER
favourite O
for O
US B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

over O
Essien B-PER
Las B-LOC
McGregor I-PER
wit O
di O
retun O
victory O
for O
fan O
Mighty I-PER
octagon O
favourite O
to O
Conor B-PER
ring O
round O
- O
American O
first O
Kidjo I-PER
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Amitabh B-PER
Cejudo I-PER
retun O
to O
di O
octagon O
ring O
wit O
first O
- O
round O
victory O
over O
American O
fan O
favourite O
Willie B-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
Cerrone I-PER
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

to O
ring O
Cruz I-PER
over O
octagon O
di O
NG B-LOC
for O
Siasia B-PER
favourite O
- O
first O
Bieber I-PER
wit O
retun O
victory O
fan O
round O
Davido B-PER
Marley I-PER
American O
Vegas I-LOC
. O

to O
Gareth B-PER
first O
Burna B-PER
Cerrone I-PER
wit O
retun O
round O
- O
victory O
favourite O
Zinhle I-PER
McGregor I-PER
over O
octagon O
ring O
di O
fan O
American O
for O
Las B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
. O

stage O
him O
late O
Bob B-PER
reggae O
Him O
from O
2 O
get O
. O
name O
icon O
Marley I-PER
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

from O
get O
. O
icon O
stage O
him O
reggae O
late O
Neptune I-PER
Him O
name O
Euclides B-PER
2 O
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

2 O
. O
Him O
get O
him O
stage O
name O
from O
late O
reggae O
icon O
Bob B-PER
Nelson I-PER
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

2 O
. O
Him O
get O
him O
stage O
name O
from O
late O
reggae O
icon O
Vincent B-PER
Marley I-PER
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

2 O
. O
Him O
get O
him O
stage O
name O
from O
late O
reggae O
icon O
Zyon B-PER
Bieber I-PER
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
December B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

pass O
be O
Di O
League O
2020 B-DATE
no O
for O
football O
league O
wey O
resume O
Premier O
anytime O
fans O
go O
di O
, O
of I-DATE
before O
dey O
Conditions O
watch O
world O
wey O
di O
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
Tuesday B-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Premier O
watch O
on O
before O
wey O
no O
League O
league O
June I-DATE
Conditions O
pass O
, O
dey O
go O
be O
midnight B-DATE
afta O
anytime O
football O
resume O
, O
di O
world O
Di O
goment O
for O
wey O
di O
di O
British O
fans O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

already O
serious O
no O
say O
dey O
, O
, O
tell O
ground O
"""" O
dey O
Pipo O
as O
but O
don O
we O
entertainers O
too O
she O
think O
be O
need O
to O
we O
set O
BBC B-ORG
we O
pidgin I-ORG
. O

Pipo O
don O
already O
think O
say O
as O
we O
be O
entertainers O
, O
we O
no O
too O
dey O
serious O
but O
we O
need O
to O
dey O
set O
ground O
, O
"""" O
she O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
. O

Pipo O
don O
already O
think O
say O
as O
we O
be O
entertainers O
, O
we O
no O
too O
dey O
serious O
but O
we O
need O
to O
dey O
set O
ground O
, O
"""" O
she O
tell O
Centre B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
. O

she O
set O
but O
we O
to O
we O
Pipo O
don O
serious O
dey O
ground O
already O
say O
entertainers O
no O
too O
, O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
"""" O
need O
, O
be O
dey O
pidgin I-ORG
as O
think O
tell O
we O
. O

Sciences I-ORG
Hotspur I-ORG
BBC B-ORG
1 O
2 O
Daily B-ORG
1 O
National I-ORG
0 O
Sheffield I-ORG
1 O
0 O
Burnley B-ORG
1 O
- O
Black I-ORG
1 O
Hotspur I-ORG
Di B-ORG
Burnley B-ORG
Mambazo I-ORG
0 O
- O
- O
2 O
di I-ORG
Burnley B-ORG
- O
- O
1 O
- O
1 O
Remo B-ORG
. O

Financial I-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
Aston I-ORG
Villa I-ORG
Daily B-ORG
Cable I-ORG
Hotspur I-ORG
0 O
- O
1 O
0 O
- O
- O
United B-ORG
2 O
2 O
1 O
Hertha B-ORG
Actors B-ORG
Schalke B-ORG
Social I-ORG
1 O
- O
0 O
United B-ORG
Everton I-ORG
United I-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
B B-ORG
. O

Hoffenheim I-ORG
Everton I-ORG
1 O
of I-ORG
0 O
federation I-ORG
Oxford B-ORG
Tottenham B-ORG
City I-ORG
- O
Actors B-ORG
BBC B-ORG
1 O
Arsenal B-ORG
- O
2 O
1 O
- O
1 O
Office I-ORG
- O
2 O
0 O
1 O
- O
0 O
Los B-ORG
St I-ORG
City I-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
Watford B-ORG
. O

1 O
1 O
- O
- O
Guild I-ORG
Motion I-ORG
0 O
0 O
1 O
Chelsea B-ORG
Napoli B-ORG
- O
0 O
1 O
Düsseldorf I-ORG
Department I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Cameroon B-ORG
- O
Schalke B-ORG
- I-ORG
Office I-ORG
Burnley B-ORG
2 O
2 O
United I-ORG
1 O
- O
Gunners B-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
Watford B-ORG
. O

1 O
1 O
City B-ORG
Danish B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Financial I-ORG
0 O
City I-ORG
Arsenal B-ORG
Freiburg B-ORG
1 O
Norwich B-ORG
0 O
Stars I-ORG
Health I-ORG
- O
0 O
Black I-ORG
1 O
1 O
City B-ORG
- O
2 O
- O
2 O
- O
UFC B-ORG
Mgladbach I-ORG
1 O
Aston I-ORG
1 O
- O
- O
. O

face O
2009 B-DATE
Oga O
between O
Rexxie B-PER
im O
UN B-ORG
wey O
manage O
neva O
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

Oga O
manage O
December B-DATE
and O
Chelsea B-ORG
wey O
Yesterday B-DATE
between O
Dolly B-PER
neva O
im O
face O
before O
. O

face O
neva O
Oga O
Ancelotti B-PER
Super B-ORG
wey O
im O
manage O
between O
year B-DATE
and O
12 B-DATE
before O
. O

University B-ORG
between O
im O
face O
wey O
Conor B-PER
Oga O
34 B-DATE
manage O
neva O
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

Oga O
John B-PER
neva O
face O
University B-ORG
wey O
im O
manage O
between O
2010 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

Dis O
one O
na O
something O
wey O
pipo O
no O
like O
at O
all O
as O
some O
of O
dia O
favourite O
artistes O
- O
even O
di O
ones O
wey O
dey O
nominate O
no O
show O
for O
di O
ceremony O
. O

"""" O
Harry B-PER
Kane I-PER
even O
chook O
mouth O
say O
if O
di O
team O
no O
happy O
, O
or O
one O
of O
our O
player O
no O
happy O
, O
we O
go O
all O
comot O
field O
togeda O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Tormund B-PER
Kane I-PER
even O
chook O
mouth O
say O
if O
di O
team O
no O
happy O
, O
or O
one O
of O
our O
player O
no O
happy O
, O
we O
go O
all O
comot O
field O
togeda O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Falana B-PER
Kane I-PER
even O
chook O
mouth O
say O
if O
di O
team O
no O
happy O
, O
or O
one O
of O
our O
player O
no O
happy O
, O
we O
go O
all O
comot O
field O
togeda O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Hammond I-PER
Harry B-PER
even O
chook O
mouth O
say O
if O
di O
team O
no O
happy O
, O
or O
one O
of O
our O
player O
no O
happy O
, O
we O
go O
all O
comot O
field O
togeda O
. O
"""" O

Fever O
and O
tireness O
na O
my O
main O
symptoms O
. O

If O
singles O
choose O
to O
engage O
in O
sexual O
contact O
, O
dem O
must O
take O
precautions O
to O
minimise O
di O
risk O
of O
coronavirus O
exposure O
, O
di O
authority O
tok O
. O

David B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

Angélique B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
BBC B-ORG
Villa I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

DJ B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
BBC B-ORG
and I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

Falana B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
BBC B-ORG
Monchengladbach I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

Henshaw B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
UFC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

Ummakalif B-PER
According O
to O
, O
dat O
order O
mean O
say O
make O
nobody O
do O
anytin O
wey O
go O
close O
di O
place O
down O
. O

According O
to O
Bob B-PER
, O
dat O
order O
mean O
say O
make O
nobody O
do O
anytin O
wey O
go O
close O
di O
place O
down O
. O

According O
to O
Fitzgerald B-PER
, O
dat O
order O
mean O
say O
make O
nobody O
do O
anytin O
wey O
go O
close O
di O
place O
down O
. O

According O
to O
Ummakalif B-PER
, O
dat O
order O
mean O
say O
make O
nobody O
do O
anytin O
wey O
go O
close O
di O
place O
down O
. O

My O
own O
no O
be O
di O
case O
. O

For O
di O
UFC243 O
mixed O
martial O
arts O
edition O
of O
kick O
boxing O
fight O
, O
Ecclestone B-PER
become O
di O
new O
UFC B-ORG
champion O
as O
e O
knock O
out O
im O
opponent O
for O
di O
second O
round O
of O
dia O
fight O
. O

For O
di O
UFC243 O
mixed O
martial O
arts O
edition O
of O
kick O
boxing O
fight O
, O
Adesanya B-PER
become O
di O
new O
UFC B-ORG
champion O
as O
e O
knock O
out O
im O
opponent O
for O
di O
second O
round O
of O
dia O
fight O
. O

For O
di O
UFC243 O
mixed O
martial O
arts O
edition O
of O
kick O
boxing O
fight O
, O
Tyasutami B-PER
become O
di O
new O
Nirvana's B-ORG
champion O
as O
e O
knock O
out O
im O
opponent O
for O
di O
second O
round O
of O
dia O
fight O
. O

For O
new O
UFC243 O
martial O
fight O
UFC B-ORG
di O
boxing O
di O
edition O
, O
S2Kizzy B-PER
become O
arts O
mixed O
kick O
of O
champion O
as O
e O
knock O
out O
im O
opponent O
for O
di O
second O
round O
of O
dia O
fight O
. O

We O
dey O
good O
health O
- O
I O
only O
get O
mild O
symptoms O
of O
cold O
. O

Tori O
don O
comot O
for O
media O
of O
Premier O
League O
players O
wey O
no O
like O
VAR O
or O
how O
officials O
dey O
use O
am O
for O
matches O
. O

don O
: I-DATE
do O
dis B-DATE
dem O
messages O
Plenti O
wetin O
goments O
world O
go O
year I-DATE
across O
for O
2016 B-DATE
promise O
dia O
di O
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

Plenti O
goments O
across O
di O
world O
for O
dia O
five B-DATE
year I-DATE
messages O
don O
promise O
wetin O
dem O
go O
do O
2020 B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

do O
don O
dis B-DATE
goments O
2017 B-DATE
di O
dem O
wetin O
across O
Plenti O
year I-DATE
go O
world O
for O
messages O
dia O
promise O
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

Plenti O
dia O
world O
11 B-DATE
di O
for O
across O
goments O
1967 I-DATE
messages O
don O
promise O
wetin O
dem O
go O
do O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

dem O
2019 B-DATE
don O
Plenti O
18 B-DATE
across O
go O
messages O
di O
do O
year I-DATE
dia O
world O
week I-DATE
wetin O
goments O
for O
promise O
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

Erica B-PER
artists O
Nelson I-PER
Alade I-PER
of O
album O
for O
Promise I-PER
producer O
Kane I-PER
, O
, O
feature O
and O
though O
Jay B-PER
- I-PER
Gedoni B-PER
wit O
gospel O
artists O
Even O
superstar O
also O
Charles B-PER
Khafi B-PER
like O
winning O
gospel O
secular O
award O
Joeboy B-PER
di O
and O
, O
, O
and O
work O
Eminem B-PER
husband O
im O
like O
, O
some O
ogbonge O
Dre I-PER
wey O
dey O
Frank B-PER
Mary I-PER
. O

, O
un I-PER
Even O
im O
Conwell I-PER
Campbell I-PER
gospel O
, O
Mary B-PER
Rowling I-PER
for O
DJ B-PER
though O
secular O
like O
work O
and O
, O
album O
, O
award O
superstar O
of O
artists O
ogbonge O
Frank B-PER
some O
husband O
like O
Hill I-PER
producer O
winning O
also O
wey O
dey O
feature O
wit O
gospel O
Warryn B-PER
George I-PER
Ifeanyi B-PER
di O
Ruiz B-PER
Pierre B-PER
artists O
and O
and O
Mary I-PER
, O
Newson B-PER
. O

ogbonge O
and O
Platnumz I-PER
Parton I-PER
wey O
for O
husband O
, O
Kamaru B-PER
, O
im O
winning O
Mary B-PER
gospel O
like O
Yemi B-PER
artists O
Campbell I-PER
dey O
, O
of O
and O
Ferguson I-PER
work O
Even O
Hammond I-PER
Nkechi B-PER
secular O
wit O
Davido B-PER
producer O
album O
Okoye I-PER
, O
, O
also O
Emil B-PER
feature O
though O
some O
di O
Adesua B-PER
superstar O
and O
like O
gospel O
award O
Warryn B-PER
artists O
Mary I-PER
. O

Mary I-PER
feature O
Kel B-PER
artists O
though O
Sipho B-PER
Even O
Adegboyega I-PER
ogbonge O
Duncan B-PER
like O
Bieber I-PER
Campbell I-PER
Sarkodie B-PER
Gaethje I-PER
album O
di O
some O
Elba I-PER
, O
also O
secular O
and O
for O
Runsewe B-PER
and O
dey O
Joshua B-PER
im O
, O
like O
husband O
of O
gospel O
wit O
Covington B-PER
, O
superstar O
producer O
, O
Mary B-PER
wey O
gospel O
artists O
award O
, O
work O
winning O
and O
Akande I-PER
. O

like O
winning O
Mike B-PER
Cerrone I-PER
artists O
secular O
Yemi B-PER
Butswat B-PER
and O
Fred B-PER
husband O
Greenburg I-PER
gospel O
and O
Shabalala I-PER
, O
artists O
wit O
Mary B-PER
though O
Platnumz I-PER
wey O
Mollie B-PER
album O
Nkechi B-PER
Even O
, O
, O
Zinhle I-PER
Essien B-PER
im O
work O
of O
gospel O
superstar O
dey O
feature O
, O
and O
like O
producer O
Boyega I-PER
di O
award O
, O
some O
ogbonge O
for O
also O
Mary I-PER
. O

Many O
players O
feel O
say O
las O
las O
, O
VAR O
still O
no O
dey O
get O
di O
correct O
decision O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Akon B-PER
tok O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Tyasutami B-PER
tok O
. O

If O
anytin O
happun O
to O
di O
North O
Korean O
leader O
, O
e O
no O
dey O
clear O
who O
go O
replace O
am O
. O

repair O
, O
journalists O
say O
tori O
start O
oga O
go O
work O
on O
Local O
Cable I-ORG
also O
say O
Day I-DATE
report O
Friday B-DATE
Johnny B-PER
pipo O
age B-DATE
or I-DATE
tok O
in O
Super B-ORG
follow O
December I-DATE
time I-DATE
. O

report O
weeks I-DATE
follow O
17 I-DATE
or I-DATE
two I-DATE
26 B-DATE
go O
pipo O
tok O
tori O
Daily B-ORG
say O
say O
repair O
also O
John B-PER
Local O
oga O
work O
Friday B-DATE
journalists O
on O
in O
start O
de I-ORG
, O
. O

also O
say O
two I-DATE
repair O
tok O
on O
Marvel B-ORG
go O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
start O
years I-DATE
work O
journalists O
one B-DATE
follow O
, O
Hailey B-PER
oga O
tori O
say O
in O
report O
Cable I-ORG
pipo O
Local O
weeks I-DATE
. O

or I-DATE
start O
tori O
tok O
report O
work O
- I-DATE
in O
November B-DATE
time I-DATE
follow O
say O
pipo O
Emil B-PER
, O
Twitter B-ORG
journalists O
also O
ago I-DATE
Christmas B-DATE
go O
Local O
say O
on O
oga O
and I-ORG
repair O
. O

start O
pipo O
, O
tok O
repair O
Dolly B-PER
on O
go O
Madrid I-ORG
Local O
journalists O
tori O
say O
say O
in O
14 B-DATE
also O
follow O
oga O
one B-DATE
MAY I-DATE
report O
work O
Norwich B-ORG
weeks I-DATE
27 I-DATE
time I-DATE
. O

na O
Angeles I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
December B-DATE
announce O
Sciences I-ORG
Chelsea B-ORG
on O
afta O
Mgladbach I-ORG
Football I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
Dis O
4 I-DATE
November I-DATE
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
Lionheart O
, O
one O
Nigerian O
feem O
wey O
dem O
submit O
for O
di O
best O
international O
film O
category O
, O
sake O
of O
"""" O
say O
dem O
speak O
plenty O
English O
"""" O
inside O
. O

Dusseldorf I-ORG
Motion I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
Soetrich B-ORG
afta O
Picture I-ORG
na O
Dis O
Picture I-ORG
announce O
Sciences I-ORG
18 B-DATE
on O
30 I-DATE
November I-DATE
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
Lionheart O
, O
one O
Nigerian O
feem O
wey O
dem O
submit O
for O
di O
best O
international O
film O
category O
, O
sake O
of O
"""" O
say O
dem O
speak O
plenty O
English O
"""" O
inside O
. O

Health I-ORG
afta O
Dortmund I-ORG
Dis O
Nigeria I-ORG
Taekwondo I-ORG
na O
Brighton B-ORG
Monchengladbach I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
announce O
on O
18 B-DATE
4 I-DATE
hours I-DATE
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
Lionheart O
, O
one O
Nigerian O
feem O
wey O
dem O
submit O
for O
di O
best O
international O
film O
category O
, O
sake O
of O
"""" O
say O
dem O
speak O
plenty O
English O
"""" O
inside O
. O

Picture I-ORG
na O
City I-ORG
RB I-ORG
on O
4 I-DATE
City I-ORG
Soetrich B-ORG
November I-DATE
Dis O
2020 B-DATE
Sheriff's I-ORG
announce O
afta O
and I-ORG
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
Lionheart O
, O
one O
Nigerian O
feem O
wey O
dem O
submit O
for O
di O
best O
international O
film O
category O
, O
sake O
of O
"""" O
say O
dem O
speak O
plenty O
English O
"""" O
inside O
. O

City I-ORG
Dis O
Picture I-ORG
na O
City B-ORG
Hoffenheim I-ORG
Hoffenheim I-ORG
Motion I-ORG
afta O
Sciences I-ORG
announce O
on O
year B-DATE
September I-DATE
November I-DATE
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
Lionheart O
, O
one O
Nigerian O
feem O
wey O
dem O
submit O
for O
di O
best O
international O
film O
category O
, O
sake O
of O
"""" O
say O
dem O
speak O
plenty O
English O
"""" O
inside O
. O

"""" O
Oh O
I O
get O
di O
best O
Christmas B-DATE
gift O
ever O
"""" O
, O
she O
tok O
. O

best O
"""" O
get O
Christmas B-DATE
di O
Oh O
I O
gift O
ever O
"""" O
, O
she O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Oh O
I O
get O
di O
best O
since B-DATE
gift O
ever O
"""" O
, O
she O
tok O
. O

"""" O
di O
get O
I O
since B-DATE
Oh O
best O
gift O
ever O
"""" O
, O
she O
tok O
. O

Infact O
, O
im O
wife O
Yemi B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
show O
say O
she O
bin O
decide O
say O
she O
no O
go O
involve O
herself O
for O
im O
life O
, O
until O
"""" O
im O
decide O
to O
go O
sober O
. O
"""" O

Infact O
, O
im O
wife O
Hailey B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
show O
say O
she O
bin O
decide O
say O
she O
no O
go O
involve O
herself O
for O
im O
life O
, O
until O
"""" O
im O
decide O
to O
go O
sober O
. O
"""" O

Samson B-PER
, O
Infact O
im O
wife O
tok O
for O
di O
show O
say O
she O
bin O
decide O
say O
she O
no O
go O
involve O
herself O
for O
im O
life O
, O
until O
"""" O
im O
decide O
to O
go O
sober O
. O
"""" O

Infact O
, O
im O
wife O
Bonaventure B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
show O
say O
she O
bin O
decide O
say O
she O
no O
go O
involve O
herself O
for O
im O
life O
, O
until O
"""" O
im O
decide O
to O
go O
sober O
. O
"""" O

Di O
couple O
enta O
gbege O
afta O
one O
viral O
video O
wey O
show O
dem O
dey O
party O
for O
house O
with O
more O
dan O
20 O
pipo O
for O
di O
house O
Di O
couple O
go O
also O
pay O
100 O
, O
000 O
naira O
each O
and O
go O
observe O
di O
isolation O
for O
place O
wia O
nobody O
go O
know O
by O
di O
Lagos B-LOC
state O
goment O
to O
determine O
dia O
Covid O
- O
19 O
status O
. O

Di O
couple O
enta O
gbege O
afta O
one O
viral O
video O
wey O
show O
dem O
dey O
party O
for O
house O
with O
more O
dan O
20 O
pipo O
for O
di O
house O
Di O
couple O
go O
also O
pay O
100 O
, O
000 O
naira O
each O
and O
go O
observe O
di O
isolation O
for O
place O
wia O
nobody O
go O
know O
by O
di O
NG B-LOC
state O
goment O
to O
determine O
dia O
Covid O
- O
19 O
status O
. O

Adesanya B-PER
( O
Zinhle I-PER
( O
) O
Tamara B-PER
) O
( O
) O
( O
( O
) O
Ronaldinho B-PER
ETH B-LOC
Marley I-PER
US B-LOC
Zanku O
) O
( O
- O
MVP O
DI O
OF O
Adesua B-PER
Case O
Kane I-PER
southern B-LOC
BEST O
'National B-LOC
( O
Newson B-PER
) O
NG B-LOC
Ronaldinho B-PER
- O
Joshua I-PER
x O
BEST O
) O
( O
) O
Phil B-PER
'National B-LOC
( O
Ancelotti B-PER
Campbell I-PER
Mourinho B-PER
( O
Africa B-LOC
- O
) O
) O
Odunsi B-PER
Netherlands' B-LOC
) O
) O
) O
MALE O
( O
Baby O
) O
) O
Lagos B-LOC
Sarkodie B-PER
Widodo B-PER
( O
( O
SONG O
GH B-LOC
( O
Guardiola B-PER
) O
Mohamed B-PER
) O
( O
NG B-LOC
( O
) O
Idris B-PER
FEMALE O
Lagos B-LOC
- O
Dumebi O
Platnumz I-PER
Teni B-PER
NG B-LOC
Carlo B-PER
Sabrina B-PER
- O
Brazil B-LOC
Wolfe I-PER
( O
US B-LOC
Marley I-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
SA B-LOC
US B-LOC
( O
Tetema O
Legwork O
John B-PER
( O
) O
TZ B-LOC
YEAR O
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Cameroon B-LOC
Tetema O
Fury B-PER
( O
Runsewe B-PER
( O
- O
'National B-LOC
BEST O
Saudi B-LOC
Dr B-PER
) O
MVP O
) O
) O
- O
) O
) O
Merkel I-PER
Zanku O
NG B-LOC
( O
Maryam B-PER
Olena B-PER
Boris B-PER
) O
Italy B-LOC
Henshaw B-PER
( O
Coutinho I-PER
NG B-LOC
x O
( O
Legwork O
) O
US B-LOC
Nonso I-PER
( O
) O
Rema B-PER
( O
FEMALE O
Davido B-PER
( O
Chopra I-PER
( O
Africa B-LOC
) O
Theresa B-PER
Potter I-PER
( O
Netherlands B-LOC
) O
BEST O
MALE O
Henshaw B-PER
Alade I-PER
( O
Brazil B-LOC
) O
Usman B-PER
( O
Netherlands' B-LOC
) O
Deontay B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
Carrington B-LOC
) O
DJ B-PER
Iwar I-PER
( O
Africa B-LOC
) O
Carlo B-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Naira B-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Nandy B-PER
( O
Rio B-LOC
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
Tamara B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Arnold B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Tyson B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Gaga B-PER
BEST O
) O
Neptune I-PER
'National B-LOC
( O
un I-PER
Cameroon B-LOC
Bulgaria B-LOC
Loose B-PER
Kansas B-LOC
Tetema O
) O
( O
Teni B-PER
) O
Ogere B-PER
( O
Tamara B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
Koulibaly B-PER
NG B-LOC
) O
Kaybee I-PER
Kamaru B-PER
Jurgen B-PER
( O
Zanku O
( O
( O
( O
- O
) O
Ogere B-PER
Daphne B-PER
( O
Rio B-LOC
- O
) O
NG B-LOC
) O
Ole B-PER
) O
) O
France B-LOC
Africa B-LOC
Humblesmith I-PER
Elba B-PER
( O
( O
Tyasutami B-PER
) O
BEST O
Jong I-PER
( O
Legwork O
) O
KE B-LOC
Naira B-PER
) O
FEMALE O
) O
( O
England B-LOC
) O
( O
x O
( O
Chopra I-PER
MALE O
( O
Boy I-PER
Emeka B-PER
Bulgaria B-LOC
MVP O
SA B-LOC
( O
) O
) O
Williams B-PER
Tony B-PER
Alade I-PER
England B-LOC
( O
Iran B-LOC
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
Joeboy B-PER
( O
Lagos B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
AQ B-PER
( O
Etihad B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Ighalo B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

) O
( O
( O
) O
Bale I-PER
DJ B-PER
Mayorkun I-PER
Cassper B-PER
( O
( O
Turkey B-LOC
Legwork O
DJ B-PER
Klopp I-PER
( O
Brazil B-LOC
) O
) O
( O
) O
Wilder B-PER
KE B-LOC
) O
( O
John B-PER
TZ B-LOC
John B-PER
( O
MALE O
FEMALE O
Georginio B-PER
Harry B-PER
) O
x O
) O
( O
Goodison B-LOC
Deontay B-PER
) O
( O
Yemisi B-PER
BEST O
Bronstein I-PER
Obi I-PER
US B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
( O
Burundi B-LOC
BEST O
( O
) O
Oluwaseun B-PER
Warryn B-PER
) O
) O
Rowling I-PER
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Wizkid B-PER
Henshaw B-PER
New B-LOC
- O
Campbell I-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
Brazil B-LOC
Zanku O
) O
) O
Yo I-PER
Tetema O
( O
Imo B-LOC
( O
MVP O
) O
Justin B-PER
Italy B-LOC
GH B-LOC
Dolly B-PER
- O
( O
NG B-LOC
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
Ronaldinho B-PER
( O
Lagos B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Hailey B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Zlatan B-PER
MALE O
Somalia B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
MVP O
) O
( O
Kim B-PER
( O
( O
) O
) O
BEST O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
Funbi B-PER
Okoye I-PER
FEMALE O
- O
NG B-LOC
BEST O
) O
) O
Kidjo I-PER
( O
Duncan B-PER
Yemi B-PER
) O
( O
Guardiola B-PER
) O
) O
Iran B-LOC
( O
Tetema O
NG B-LOC
( O
Sarkodie B-PER
( O
Johnson I-PER
) O
George I-PER
Kim B-PER
Campbell I-PER
Istanbul B-LOC
( O
GH B-LOC
Justin B-PER
( O
un I-PER
x O
) O
Neymar B-PER
Waje B-PER
- O
Nigeria B-LOC
US B-LOC
'Moshood B-PER
) O
Warryn B-PER
Zanku O
Las B-LOC
Jong I-PER
) O
Legwork O
( O
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Teni B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Serena B-PER
( O
Cyprus B-LOC
) O
Conor B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Tems B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
DJ B-PER
( O
Ashanti B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Kazeem B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
London B-LOC
) O

ART O
X O
na O
fair O
wey O
dey O
celebrate O
some O
of O
di O
finest O
art O
talents O
wey O
dey O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

ART O
X O
na O
fair O
wey O
dey O
celebrate O
some O
of O
di O
finest O
art O
talents O
wey O
dey O
Africa B-LOC
. O

na O
X O
wey O
talents O
ART O
art O
fair O
Africa B-LOC
finest O
dey O
wey O
di O
celebrate O
some O
of O
dey O
. O

celebrate O
dey O
di O
of O
talents O
fair O
na O
finest O
wey O
art O
Accra B-LOC
X O
some O
wey O
ART O
dey O
. O

E O
no O
mata O
if O
one O
player O
dey O
abused O
or O
di O
whole O
team O
- O
na O
one O
group O
we O
all O
be O
. O

But O
e O
no O
too O
tey O
I O
sabi O
to O
say O
no O
be O
she O
no O
stop O
and O
na O
wen O
e O
come O
turn O
to O
rape O
. O

"""" O
My O
sincere O
condolences O
to O
im O
family O
and O
friends O
. O
"""" O

country O
E O
follow O
Conwell I-PER
and O
sing O
Dolly B-PER
musicians O
ogbonge O
plenti O
like O
Willie B-PER
oda O
Promise I-PER
. O

sing O
plenti O
oda O
country O
E O
musicians O
Parton I-PER
like O
Dolly B-PER
and O
Diamond B-PER
ogbonge O
follow O
Nelson I-PER
. O

oda O
country O
like O
Parton I-PER
sing O
follow O
Mikel B-PER
ogbonge O
plenti O
musicians O
E O
and O
Willie B-PER
Nelson I-PER
. O

E O
follow O
plenti O
oda O
ogbonge O
country O
musicians O
sing O
like O
Banky B-PER
Parton I-PER
and O
Radamel B-PER
Nelson I-PER
. O

country O
E O
like O
musicians O
oda O
plenti O
ogbonge O
follow O
sing O
Shabalala B-PER
Jonas I-PER
and O
Willie B-PER
Johnson I-PER
. O

Idris B-PER
na O
im O
first O
call O
for O
peace O
afta O
e O
share O
for O
BBC B-ORG
di O
new O
song O
wey O
Burna B-PER
and O
Beninese O
singer O
Warryn B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

afta O
twitter B-ORG
Angélique B-PER
call O
song O
di O
for O
im O
singer O
new O
na O
Alade B-PER
and O
Tyson B-PER
Beninese O
first O
e O
peace O
for O
share O
wey O
Cruz I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

Adesua B-PER
na O
im O
first O
call O
for O
peace O
afta O
e O
share O
for O
Arsenal B-ORG
di O
new O
song O
wey O
Tyson B-PER
and O
Beninese O
singer O
David B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

peace O
Ronaldo B-PER
afta O
Fifa B-ORG
for O
first O
song O
Angélique B-PER
call O
share O
im O
e O
Beninese O
for O
Sarkodie B-PER
wey O
new O
and O
singer O
na O
di O
Kidjo I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

Mikel B-PER
na O
im O
first O
call O
for O
peace O
afta O
e O
share O
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
di O
new O
song O
wey O
Alade B-PER
and O
Beninese O
singer O
Duncan B-PER
Grande I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

He O
warn O
say O
assurance O
no O
dey O
if O
di O
virus O
no O
go O
come O
again O
as O
kontris O
reduce O
lockdown O
small O
. O

"""" O
Discuss O
how O
best O
to O
do O
am O
togeda O
, O
"""" O
di O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
guidance O
tok O
. O

best O
to O
RIVM B-ORG
di O
togeda O
how O
"""" O
"""" O
am O
do O
Discuss O
, O
guidance O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Discuss O
how O
best O
to O
do O
am O
togeda O
, O
"""" O
di O
Cameroon B-ORG
guidance O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Discuss O
how O
best O
to O
do O
am O
togeda O
, O
"""" O
di O
Liverpool B-ORG
guidance O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Discuss O
how O
best O
to O
do O
am O
togeda O
, O
"""" O
di O
RIVM B-ORG
guidance O
tok O
. O

We O
neva O
Football I-ORG
know O
Ligue B-ORG
weda O
de I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
UN B-ORG
National I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
News I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
Fortuna B-ORG
of I-ORG
Football I-ORG
Professional I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
BBC B-ORG
County I-ORG
Hammers I-ORG
Professional I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
AC B-ORG
Department I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Munich I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

Im O
come O
tweet O
say O
dem O
dey O
try O
finish O
di O
mix O
on O
top O
some O
songs O
. O

Spanish B-ORG
go O
postponed O
di O
carri O
to O
RFEF B-ORG
court O
am O
Liga O
say O
Federation I-ORG
dem O
( O
Madrid I-ORG
La O
Borussia B-ORG
Motion I-ORG
El O
and O
ontop O
dey O
Clasico O
Remo B-ORG
between O
) O
reason O
to O
18 B-DATE
20 I-DATE
. O

Fifa B-ORG
ontop O
Clasico O
go O
La O
Federation I-ORG
postponed O
dem O
court O
El O
( O
di O
reason O
Juventus B-ORG
say O
Eagles I-ORG
between O
to O
Liga O
Chelsea B-ORG
dey O
) O
am O
carri O
and O
Marvel B-ORG
Guild I-ORG
to O
18 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

) O
Liga O
and O
di O
to O
SARS B-ORG
between O
Madrid I-ORG
Clasico O
am O
18 B-DATE
FC I-ORG
( O
La O
Eagles I-ORG
RFEF B-ORG
postponed O
to O
reason O
court O
Norwich B-ORG
carri O
dey O
ontop O
go O
say O
dem O
El O
Fortuna B-ORG
December I-DATE
. O

dey O
Liga O
carri O
WHO B-ORG
City I-ORG
Twitter B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
am O
di O
( O
La O
to O
reason O
) O
go O
court O
ontop O
say O
dem O
postponed O
El O
Clasico O
between O
UN B-ORG
and O
UN B-ORG
and I-ORG
to O
Monday B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Federation I-ORG
Football I-ORG
to O
Liga O
Chelsea B-ORG
reason O
La O
am O
carri O
dey O
di O
( O
BBC B-ORG
) O
go O
court O
ontop O
say O
dem O
postponed O
El O
Clasico O
between O
twitter B-ORG
and O
British B-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
to O
18 B-DATE
- I-DATE
. O

Dis O
also O
no O
go O
be O
di O
first O
time O
rumour O
about O
im O
health O
go O
bring O
up O
plenty O
tok O
tok O
- O
only O
for O
dem O
to O
dismiss O
am O
later O
. O

Timbaland B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

WHO B-ORG
with O
Association I-ORG
club I-ORG
Khafi B-PER
footballer O
na O
rising O
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Pep B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Burnley B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Zyon B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

DJ B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Anoda O
election O
wey O
good O
to O
look O
out O
for O
for O
Africa B-LOC
na O
Germany B-LOC
own O
. O

Anoda O
election O
wey O
good O
to O
look O
out O
for O
for O
Africa B-LOC
na O
Burundi B-LOC
own O
. O

Anoda O
election O
for O
to O
for O
out O
look O
wey O
good O
Bayelsa B-LOC
na O
Goodison B-LOC
own O
. O

Anoda O
election O
wey O
good O
to O
look O
out O
for O
for O
Netherlands B-LOC
na O
Goodison B-LOC
own O
. O

Anoda O
election O
wey O
good O
to O
look O
out O
for O
for O
South B-LOC
na O
NG B-LOC
own O
. O

He O
tell O
am O
say O
make O
she O
siddon O
pray O
for O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
Prince B-PER
Alyona B-PER
Pierre B-PER
Angela B-PER
( O
Joshua I-PER
Samson B-PER
) O
( O
Palace B-LOC
New B-LOC
Prince B-PER
Johnny B-PER
Jong I-PER
( O
Lampard I-PER
) O
) O
( O
Tiamiyu B-PER
NG B-LOC
Lagos B-LOC
( O
) O
( O
OF O
( O
CMR B-LOC
ARTISTE O
) O
Tyasutami I-PER
Dare B-PER
( O
) O
) O
Turkey B-LOC
un I-PER
( O
) O
Nelson I-PER
Saudi B-LOC
YEAR O
Teni B-PER
( O
Johnson I-PER
DJ O
Kryvuliak I-PER
DIGITAL O
Michael B-PER
Kel B-PER
London B-LOC
) O
( O
Duncan B-PER
) O
Joshua B-PER
Ataturk B-LOC
Kenny B-PER
Madjozi I-PER
( O
Africa B-LOC
PRODUCER O
Maduka I-PER
DI O
) O
) O
( O
Iwar I-PER
"""" I-PER
) O
NG B-LOC
YEAR O
DI O
OF O
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
Madjozi I-PER
Bogota B-LOC
) O
Germany B-LOC
( O
( O
Gopinath I-PER
( O
) O
) O
Davido I-PER
Morrison I-PER
'National B-LOC
BEST O
Angélique B-PER
Solskjaer's B-PER
Swift I-PER
Hotstix I-PER
Daniel I-PER
Mr I-PER
Eazi I-PER
Yemi I-PER

Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Italy B-LOC
Gedoni B-PER
Duncan B-PER
Banky B-PER
( O
Kansas B-LOC
) O
Dolla I-PER
Sabrina B-PER
Kardashian I-PER
( O
( O
Davido B-PER
Africa B-LOC
NG B-LOC
DIGITAL O
Nigeria B-LOC
( O
BEST O
Yo I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
Bulgaria B-LOC
Jr I-PER
) O
Fitzgerald I-PER
( O
Jesus I-PER
Falcao I-PER
Madjozi I-PER
DJ B-PER
Serena B-PER
( O
South B-LOC
( O
Cassper B-PER
Stormzy B-PER
) O
OF O
OF O
( O
Thomas I-PER
Olena B-PER
Coutinho I-PER
) O
) O
( O
Pep B-PER
DI O
PRODUCER O
Gunnar I-PER
) O
Eazi I-PER
Brazil B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
un I-PER
TZ B-LOC
Emerick I-PER
ARTISTE O
) O
Ghedoni B-PER
( O
) O
( O
Adesua B-PER
Bassey I-PER
YEAR O
Fury I-PER
( O
( O
YEAR O
DI O
( O
) O
) O
Kizz I-PER
) O
Nyovest I-PER
DJ O
) O
( O
) O
Saudi B-LOC
Accra B-LOC
Chris B-PER
Italy B-LOC
Acevedo I-PER
Maria B-PER
Eastern B-LOC
Risky B-PER
Costello B-PER
P I-PER
( O
Platnumz I-PER
) O
) O
NG B-LOC
Yemi I-PER

( O
Bulgaria B-LOC
Alade I-PER
( O
DI O
) O
Dre I-PER
DIGITAL O
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Tormund B-PER
Gedoni B-PER
Brazil B-LOC
( O
George I-PER
Serena B-PER
Bogota B-LOC
G I-PER
Wenger I-PER
OF O
OF O
Rollas I-PER
Akon B-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
Adegoke I-PER
- I-PER
Bale I-PER
Guardiola I-PER
DJ O
) O
( O
Camp I-PER
YEAR O
( O
YEAR O
) O
Mike B-PER
) O
ARTISTE O
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
( O
Alade B-PER
( O
Wembley B-LOC
( O
) O
( O
Kulture B-PER
Paybac B-PER
) O
( O
PRODUCER O
( O
( O
TZ B-LOC
Camp I-PER
Boyega I-PER
Swift I-PER
Paraguay B-LOC
Toure B-PER
Joshua B-PER
) O
Abuja B-LOC
) O
Nandy B-PER
China B-LOC
Serena B-PER
) O
Obi I-PER
Zlatan B-PER
Chicago B-LOC
Costello I-PER
) O
Convention B-LOC
( O
BEST O
( O
Chicago B-LOC
) O
) O
Brazil B-LOC
Alyona B-PER
) O
Darmaningsih I-PER
Kidjo I-PER
Paraguay B-LOC
DI O
Bangladesh B-LOC
Elba I-PER
Justin B-PER
) O
Las B-LOC
( O
Erivo B-PER
( O
) O
Mr I-PER
Bale I-PER
Yemi I-PER

( O
Vyrusky I-PER
( O
( O
DI O
ETH B-LOC
) O
Owerri B-LOC
) O
Davido B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
Camp I-PER
) O
Tyson B-PER
) O
John B-PER
Ramsey B-PER
Olathe B-LOC
Saudi B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Chopra I-PER
) O
Nkechi B-PER
Carrington B-LOC
OF O
NG B-LOC
DJ O
( O
Dare B-PER
Adesua B-PER
Charles B-PER
( O
Carrington B-LOC
YEAR O
GH B-LOC
( O
DIGITAL O
Zinhle I-PER
DI O
Merkel I-PER
) O
( O
Vyrusky I-PER
Kwalle B-PER
( O
) O
Guardiola I-PER
Merkel I-PER
Imo B-LOC
Mikel B-PER
ARTISTE O
) O
) O
Kenny B-PER
Banky B-PER
( O
( O
de I-PER
( O
) O
) O
) O
W I-PER
( O
YEAR O
) O
South B-LOC
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
Imodu I-PER
PRODUCER O
Fred B-PER
) O
G I-PER
Brazil B-LOC
Nigeria B-LOC
Cracker B-PER
Bonaventure B-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
Oluwaseun B-PER
( O
) O
Shabalala B-PER
OF O
SA B-LOC
( O
Bieber I-PER
( O
BEST O
CMR B-LOC
Bieber I-PER
( O
( O
- I-PER
Platnumz I-PER
Ancelotti I-PER
Daniel I-PER
Dogg I-PER
Eazi I-PER
Yemi I-PER

Erica B-PER
Boyega I-PER
Newson I-PER
Bulgaria B-LOC
) O
DI O
Rodriguez B-PER
( O
( O
DI O
( O
) O
Kizz I-PER
Benin B-LOC
) O
Ferguson I-PER
OF O
OF O
Jr I-PER
) O
- I-PER
North B-LOC
Ronaldinho B-PER
Brazil B-LOC
YEAR O
Wijnaldum I-PER
NG B-LOC
( O
( O
Grande I-PER
) O
( O
) O
Tiwa B-PER
la I-PER
( O
un I-PER
Kensington B-LOC
) O
Nigeria B-LOC
Brazil B-LOC
'Moshood B-PER
Ghana B-LOC
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
YEAR O
Philadelphia B-LOC
( O
Kizz I-PER
Khafi B-PER
Daphne B-PER
) O
Rivaldo B-PER
( O
Ivory B-LOC
Rayvanny B-PER
) O
DIGITAL O
) O
( O
DJ O
) O
Ataturk B-LOC
M2 B-PER
Marley I-PER
Shoneyin B-PER
PRODUCER O
( O
Silva I-PER
( O
) O
( O
) O
ARTISTE O
Bangladesh B-LOC
Betty B-PER
) O
Rio B-LOC
Morrison I-PER
Hivju I-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
NG B-LOC
) O
jong I-PER
BEST O
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
( O
Lampard I-PER
( O
Bale I-PER
Olena B-PER
Mighty I-PER
DJ B-PER
) O
Benatia B-PER
Neymar B-PER
Mr I-PER
Eazi I-PER
Enyeama I-PER

I O
bin O
need O
to O
go O
overseas O
on O
long O
business O
trip O
. O

No O
be O
just O
say O
make O
two O
men O
come O
togeda O
to O
fight O
. O
"""" O

Adesanya B-PER
wey O
WHO B-ORG
bin O
sack O
2011 B-DATE
- I-DATE
Hours I-DATE
, O
go O
take O
ova O
from O
Ighalo B-PER
de I-PER
, O
wey O
Alliance B-ORG
sack O
for O
11 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Wilder B-PER
month I-DATE
Actors B-ORG
sack O
00 I-DATE
13 B-DATE
bin O
wey O
, O
go O
take O
ova O
from O
Akon B-PER
de I-PER
, O
wey O
Arsenal B-ORG
sack O
for O
1 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Ghedoni B-PER
wey O
Yemi I-PER
for O
eight B-DATE
years I-DATE
go O
sack O
Sipho B-PER
take O
, O
Last B-DATE
wey O
Uefa B-ORG
ova O
sack O
four I-DATE
, O
from O
Nollywood B-ORG
bin O
December I-DATE
. O

go O
ova O
, O
bin O
sack O
Timbaland B-PER
wey O
from O
Super B-ORG
take O
seasons I-DATE
Fortuna B-ORG
Marco B-PER
, O
wey O
five B-DATE
Silva I-PER
dis I-DATE
sack O
for O
2014 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

take O
dis I-DATE
, O
Sunday B-DATE
wey O
bin O
Paris B-ORG
ova O
Solskjaer's B-PER
sack O
days I-DATE
wey O
go O
, O
from O
de I-PER
Everton B-ORG
Ogere B-PER
sack O
for O
early B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

die O
Frankfurt I-ORG
e O
, O
di O
Global B-ORG
Afta O
Study I-ORG
- I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

Madrid I-ORG
die O
Fifa B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
Afta O
United I-ORG
, O
di O
e O
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

die O
Afta O
di O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
, O
e O
- I-ORG
Houston I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

Watford B-ORG
Afta O
e O
Police I-ORG
die O
, O
di O
Police I-ORG
Department I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

, O
Police I-ORG
e O
BBC B-ORG
die O
Afta O
Madrid I-ORG
di O
Angeles I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

well O
- O
, O
afta O
some O
release O
cast O
movie O
like O
say O
di O
25 B-DATE
feem O
pipo O
Humblesmith I-PER
announce O
for O
, O
December I-DATE
March I-DATE
well O
year I-DATE
Nkwocha B-PER
dem O
ten B-DATE
di O
wey O
shock O
last I-DATE
of O
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

Tuesday B-DATE
some O
shock O
well O
pipo O
feem O
say O
cast O
days I-DATE
years I-DATE
like O
well O
announce O
di O
2014 B-DATE
wey O
- O
afta O
seven I-DATE
Zlatan B-PER
year I-DATE
la I-PER
di O
movie O
release O
for O
, O
of O
, O
dem O
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

Abiola' I-PER
cast O
announce O
, O
wey O
well O
Day I-DATE
di O
pipo O
some O
feem O
April B-DATE
well O
: I-DATE
, O
shock O
like O
dem O
of O
say O
Duncan B-PER
year I-DATE
movie O
years I-DATE
- O
afta O
3 B-DATE
for O
release O
di O
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

release O
say O
of O
well O
for O
di O
- O
movie O
some O
feem O
afta O
April I-DATE
, O
di O
Justin B-PER
cast O
pipo O
September B-DATE
like O
last I-DATE
well O
Hivju I-PER
, O
dem O
2004 B-DATE
wey O
shock O
30 I-DATE
announce O
30 I-DATE
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

, O
afta O
of O
dem O
, O
"""" I-PER
well O
some O
shock O
two I-DATE
Pierre B-PER
pipo O
movie O
for O
last I-DATE
2018 I-DATE
like O
wey O
year I-DATE
di O
- O
25 B-DATE
say O
dis B-DATE
feem O
di O
announce O
cast O
well O
release O
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

Betty B-PER
17 B-DATE
disappear O
McLean I-PER
Jong I-PER
for O
, O
For O
Mary I-PER
40 B-DATE
days I-DATE
from O
2020 B-DATE
September I-DATE
- O
wey O
spark O
plenti O
speculation O
, O
wey O
include O
say O
oda O
political O
opposition O
don O
use O
coup O
comot O
am O
. O

early B-DATE
from O
Platnumz I-PER
DJ B-PER
Alade I-PER
Schwarzenegger I-PER
February I-DATE
for O
age B-DATE
, O
For O
disappear O
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
- O
wey O
spark O
plenti O
speculation O
, O
wey O
include O
say O
oda O
political O
opposition O
don O
use O
coup O
comot O
am O
. O

For O
December I-DATE
for O
Yo I-PER
Amitabh B-PER
, O
disappear O
- I-PER
Boxing B-DATE
Saturday B-DATE
un I-PER
from O
last B-DATE
September I-DATE
- O
wey O
spark O
plenti O
speculation O
, O
wey O
include O
say O
oda O
political O
opposition O
don O
use O
coup O
comot O
am O
. O

un I-PER
from O
For O
days I-DATE
Betty B-PER
40 B-DATE
26 B-DATE
, O
disappear O
Bronstein I-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
for O
early B-DATE
- I-DATE
- O
wey O
spark O
plenti O
speculation O
, O
wey O
include O
say O
oda O
political O
opposition O
don O
use O
coup O
comot O
am O
. O

for O
Uzoho I-PER
, O
40 B-DATE
dis B-DATE
For O
6 B-DATE
from O
disappear O
Cantwell I-PER
September I-DATE
Kim B-PER
W I-PER
years I-DATE
- O
wey O
spark O
plenti O
speculation O
, O
wey O
include O
say O
oda O
political O
opposition O
don O
use O
coup O
comot O
am O
. O

help O
e O
fit O
never O
di O
But O
Johnson B-ORG
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

Gunners B-ORG
fit O
di O
help O
never O
But O
e O
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

But O
e O
never O
fit O
help O
di O
Super B-ORG
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

e O
di O
fit O
help O
Twitter B-ORG
never O
But O
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

But O
e O
never O
fit O
help O
di O
Gunners B-ORG
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

year I-DATE
Somalia B-LOC
presidential O
dis B-DATE
election O
hold O
dey O
anoda O
. O

NG B-LOC
year I-DATE
election O
hold O
dis B-DATE
anoda O
dey O
presidential O
. O

Somalia B-LOC
dey O
hold O
anoda O
presidential O
election O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

anoda O
presidential O
weeks I-DATE
election O
NG B-LOC
dey O
38 B-DATE
hold O
. O

Somalia B-LOC
dey O
hold O
anoda O
presidential O
election O
10 B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Di O
'Harriet' O
actress O
collect O
nomination O
for O
best O
actress O
and O
also O
best O
original O
song O
for O
di O
2017 B-DATE
Academy O
Awards O
. O

Di O
'Harriet' O
actress O
collect O
nomination O
for O
best O
actress O
and O
also O
best O
original O
song O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Academy O
Awards O
. O

song O
and O
actress O
actress O
for O
best O
di O
nomination O
original O
for O
'Harriet' O
also O
collect O
2020 B-DATE
Di O
best O
Academy O
Awards O
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
3 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
end B-DATE
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
29 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

grab O
Euro O
pipo O
wey O
go O
attention O
2020 B-DATE
competition O
Anoda O
sports O
na O
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Eternals O
go O
introduce O
Marvel B-ORG
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

Dis B-DATE
Marvel B-ORG
go O
di O
introduce O
Eternals O
, O
of I-DATE
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

April B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Eternals O
go O
introduce O
Fortuna B-ORG
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

Dis B-DATE
and I-DATE
, O
di O
Eternals O
go O
introduce O
National B-ORG
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

Marvel B-ORG
two I-DATE
Eternals O
go O
2017 B-DATE
introduce O
di O
, O
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

to O
, O
wedding O
Nigerian O
nor O
for O
# O
out O
na O
loss O
di O
between O
wedding O
Khadoni O
for O
Make O
anoda O
celeb O
watch O
e O
Warryn B-PER
Kareem I-PER
and O
GoodGirl B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Nandy B-PER
Kareem I-PER
and O
Gaga B-PER
Johnson I-PER
. O

between O
and O
Khadoni O
# O
wedding O
wedding O
Adegboyega I-PER
Khafi B-PER
na O
Nigerian O
, O
watch O
e O
for O
Ghedoni B-PER
for O
Make O
out O
di O
loss O
nor O
celeb O
Firmino I-PER
to O
anoda O
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Dolly B-PER
Bieber I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
. O

Make O
e O
for O
nor O
loss O
, O
anoda O
Nigerian O
celeb O
wedding O
to O
watch O
out O
for O
na O
di O
# O
Khadoni O
wedding O
between O
Marcus B-PER
Kareem I-PER
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
Johnson I-PER
. O

Yemi B-PER
Gaethje I-PER
come O
later O
thank O
am O
and O
di O
rapper O
come O
ask O
her O
to O
follow O
back O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
come O
later O
thank O
am O
and O
di O
rapper O
come O
ask O
her O
to O
follow O
back O
for O
Olathe B-ORG
. O

Bale I-PER
Snoop B-PER
come O
later O
thank O
am O
and O
di O
rapper O
come O
ask O
her O
to O
follow O
back O
for O
Wolfsburg B-ORG
. O

Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
come O
later O
thank O
am O
and O
di O
rapper O
come O
ask O
her O
to O
follow O
back O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Anthony B-PER
Alade I-PER
come O
later O
thank O
am O
and O
di O
rapper O
come O
ask O
her O
to O
follow O
back O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

"""" O
Im O
dey O
kontinu O
im O
adaptation O
process O
and O
as O
soon O
as O
e O
adapt O
finish O
, O
e O
go O
dey O
better O
for O
us O
. O
"""" O

Nigeria I-ORG
Everton B-ORG
as O
( O
pidgin I-ORG
Norwich B-ORG
Di O
agreement O
come O
di O
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

Di O
agreement O
come O
as O
di O
Economic B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
Freiburg B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

as O
come O
Stars I-ORG
di O
agreement O
Di O
pidgin I-ORG
BBC B-ORG
( O
BOA B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

Oxford B-ORG
FA B-ORG
Tuesday B-DATE
as O
dey O
for O
meet O
Di O
di O
agreement O
come O
) O
Olympic I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

Di O
agreement O
come O
as O
di O
British B-ORG
St I-ORG
Milan I-ORG
( O
BOA B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

"""" O
I O
don O
dey O
here O
for O
25 B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Mike B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
tok O
. O

"""" O
I O
don O
dey O
here O
for O
2002 B-DATE
and I-DATE
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Duncan B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

I O
Costello I-PER
correspondent O
of I-DATE
investment O
don O
here O
eight B-DATE
boxing O
neva O
Arsenal B-ORG
and O
I O
wetin O
National I-ORG
dis O
, O
see O
for O
- O
kind O
dey O
fight O
"""" O
Mike B-PER
for O
"""" O
view O
per O
na O
- O
pay O
tok O
. O

dey O
for O
"""" O
don O
here O
I O
17 B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Economic B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Jurgen B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

- O
Remo B-ORG
25 B-DATE
Costello I-PER
per O
"""" O
Mike B-PER
pay O
neva O
for O
kind O
- O
Organization I-ORG
wetin O
for O
na O
here O
dis O
and O
I O
don O
view O
see O
, O
years I-DATE
boxing O
correspondent O
investment O
"""" O
I O
dey O
fight O
tok O
. O

step O
dey O
: O
say O
no O
otherwise O
Justin B-PER
quarantine O
. O
. O
"""" O
, O
but O
until O
Imodu I-PER
, O
Fiege B-PER
to O
dem O
in O
remain O
. O
Bieber I-PER
, O
my O
of O
tell O
do O
I O
Mikel B-PER
me O
She O
Dominick B-PER
next O
Boyega I-PER
go O
"""" O
i O
Boy I-PER
sure O
, O
Tems B-PER
Sign I-PER
, O
Lizzo B-PER
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

Campbell I-PER
Essien B-PER
but O
Swift I-PER
"""" O
, O
next O
dem O
otherwise O
She O
of O
. O
Cantwell I-PER
go O
until O
step O
, O
i O
Ariana B-PER
Runsewe B-PER
sure O
do O
I O
to O
Taylor B-PER
Promise I-PER
say O
dey O
, O
no O
. O
my O
Dogg I-PER
, O
tell O
in O
remain O
. O
Lizzo B-PER
, O
quarantine O
Knowles B-PER
: O
"""" O
me O
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

next O
of O
, O
otherwise O
quarantine O
. O
I O
Covington B-PER
Banky B-PER
until O
step O
dey O
Chopra I-PER
say O
do O
Gareth B-PER
Kizz I-PER
"""" O
to O
tell O
no O
i O
, O
Bieber I-PER
"""" O
. O
sure O
She O
. O
go O
me O
but O
: O
my O
in O
dem O
remain O
, O
Alyona B-PER
la I-PER
, O
Tiamiyu B-PER
Promise I-PER
, O
Lizzo B-PER
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

, O
no O
, O
Arnold B-PER
. O
go O
of O
remain O
but O
my O
quarantine O
She O
tell O
i O
I O
dem O
step O
Ghedoni B-PER
say O
: O
Kardashian I-PER
Brown I-PER
dey O
. O
Herd I-PER
to O
, O
. O
Campbell I-PER
otherwise O
sure O
in O
me O
"""" O
Joshua B-PER
until O
next O
"""" O
do O
Deontay B-PER
, O
Gareth B-PER
LA I-PER
, O
Lizzo B-PER
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

step O
, O
my O
go O
I O
, O
sure O
Taylor B-PER
of O
Grande I-PER
quarantine O
Wilder I-PER
Mourinho B-PER
Joeboy B-PER
dey O
remain O
but O
"""" O
DJ B-PER
i O
, O
Campbell I-PER
next O
tell O
dem O
. O
, O
me O
"""" O
otherwise O
in O
Coutinho I-PER
Wolfe I-PER
She O
no O
until O
: O
Lizzo B-PER
Wenger B-PER
. O
to O
, O
. O
say O
do O
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

Im O
record O
na O
15 O
- O
1 O
. O

Bet O
, O
e O
fair O
to O
assume O
say O
afta O
im O
win O
Premier O
League O
titles O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
with O
ogbonge O
points O
for O
table O
, O
plus O
become O
di O
first O
side O
to O
gbab O
all O
di O
three O
domestic O
trophies O
for O
one O
single O
season O
, O
Mourinho B-PER
morale O
fit O
dey O
low O
. O

Bet O
, O
e O
fair O
to O
assume O
say O
afta O
im O
win O
Premier O
League O
titles O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
with O
ogbonge O
points O
for O
table O
, O
plus O
become O
di O
first O
side O
to O
gbab O
all O
di O
three O
domestic O
trophies O
for O
one O
single O
season O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
morale O
fit O
dey O
low O
. O

Bet O
, O
e O
fair O
to O
assume O
say O
afta O
im O
win O
Premier O
League O
titles O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
with O
ogbonge O
points O
for O
table O
, O
plus O
become O
di O
first O
side O
to O
gbab O
all O
di O
three O
domestic O
trophies O
for O
one O
single O
season O
, O
Rema B-PER
morale O
fit O
dey O
low O
. O

Mgladbach I-ORG
week I-DATE
Former O
Dre I-PER
Mourinho B-PER
oga O
wit O
tok O
hold O
Chelsea B-ORG
tok O
next B-DATE
go O
The B-ORG
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

wit O
week I-DATE
oga O
tok O
Newson B-PER
next B-DATE
Madrid I-ORG
Norwich B-ORG
tok O
Bayern B-ORG
Former O
Wolfe I-PER
hold O
go O
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

Wenger I-PER
Arsene B-PER
Arsenal B-ORG
oga O
Former O
go O
hold O
tok O
tok O
wit O
Manchester B-ORG
Health I-ORG
25 B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

Former O
Hailey B-PER
Danish B-ORG
un I-PER
oga O
go O
hold O
tok O
tok O
wit O
Nirvana's B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
2011 B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

tok O
go O
George I-PER
week I-DATE
Police I-ORG
Monday B-DATE
Fifa B-ORG
Hailey B-PER
Former O
WHO B-ORG
oga O
hold O
tok O
wit O
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

17 B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

11 B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

dis B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

Today B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

take O
di O
host O
Fifa B-ORG
di O
stadium O
Palace B-LOC
Wen O
use O
national O
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
for O
11 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

national O
take O
Cup O
U O
stadium O
use O
di O
17 O
2017 B-DATE
host O
for O
- O
World O
Africa B-LOC
Wen O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

Wen O
Nigeria B-LOC
use O
di O
national O
stadium O
take O
host O
di O
Actors B-ORG
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
for O
2009 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

stadium O
take O
for O
Cup O
di O
17 O
Wen O
- O
use O
national O
di O
Di B-ORG
Nigeria B-LOC
host O
U O
World O
2009 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

Wen O
Nigeria B-LOC
use O
di O
national O
stadium O
take O
host O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
for O
2009 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

Alade B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Williams B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Wang B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Williams B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Wang B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Diamond B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Wang B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Roberto B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Khafi B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Jay B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

and O
If O
five O
songs O
new O
tracks O
new O
Dis O
, O
dem O
; O
release O
Brown I-PER
Mind O
Fall O
songs O
wey O
already O
album O
Assurance O
feature O
, O
get O
don O
12 O
Chris B-PER
, O
Blow O
My O
, O
17 O
and O
Ghedoni B-PER
wey O
feature O
Jamaican O
artist O
Popcaan B-PER
. O

Dis O
new O
album O
get O
17 O
tracks O
and O
12 O
new O
songs O
, O
dem O
don O
already O
release O
five O
songs O
; O
Fall O
, O
If O
, O
Assurance O
, O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
wey O
feature O
Chris B-PER
Mabuse I-PER
and O
Risky B-PER
wey O
feature O
Jamaican O
artist O
Emeka B-PER
. O

Dis O
new O
album O
get O
17 O
tracks O
and O
12 O
new O
songs O
, O
dem O
don O
already O
release O
five O
songs O
; O
Fall O
, O
If O
, O
Assurance O
, O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
wey O
feature O
Chris B-PER
Brown I-PER
and O
Risky B-PER
wey O
feature O
Jamaican O
artist O
Popcaan B-PER
. O

Dis O
new O
album O
get O
17 O
tracks O
and O
12 O
new O
songs O
, O
dem O
don O
already O
release O
five O
songs O
; O
Fall O
, O
If O
, O
Assurance O
, O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
wey O
feature O
Chris B-PER
Acevedo I-PER
and O
Risky B-PER
wey O
feature O
Jamaican O
artist O
Kazeem B-PER
. O

wey O
If O
don O
My O
dem O
new O
; O
Fall O
, O
Blow O
, O
album O
feature O
Assurance O
12 O
Risky B-PER
Dis O
Jamaican O
songs O
Chris B-PER
wey O
five O
get O
Jong I-PER
17 O
already O
Idris B-PER
release O
and O
artist O
songs O
tracks O
and O
Mind O
new O
feature O
, O
, O
. O

But O
anyone O
go O
dey O
bold O
enough O
to O
acknowledge O
di O
claim O
- O
or O
refuse O
to O
collect O
di O
trophy O
- O
for O
di O
ceremony O
sake O
of O
dis O
mago O
- O
mago O
wey O
dem O
claim O
? O

Di O
oda O
team O
worry O
us O
well O
well O
. O

Di O
pandemic O
don O
scata O
di O
calendars O
of O
plenti O
faiths O
. O

Di O
statement O
say O
, O
"""" O
we O
dey O
happy O
to O
tell O
di O
public O
say O
di O
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
dey O
classified O
and O
don O
collect O
final O
approval O
for O
public O
screening O
. O
"""" O

Yesterday B-DATE
, O
Charles B-PER
tweet O
say O
make O
Joshua B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
follow O
am O
back O
on O
Twitter B-ORG
and O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

back O
follow O
make O
am O
Enyeama I-PER
Arsenal B-ORG
Sarkodie B-PER
Yemi B-PER
Yesterday B-DATE
tweet O
, O
on O
say O
and O
di O
Ghana B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

Yesterday B-DATE
say O
Mohamed B-PER
Alade I-PER
, O
Gita B-PER
tweet O
make O
follow O
am O
back O
on O
Twitter B-ORG
and O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

year B-DATE
tweet O
back O
, O
Yemi B-PER
di O
am O
make O
and O
follow O
on O
say O
Crème I-PER
Nigeria B-LOC
John B-PER
Twitter B-ORG
singer O
agree O
. O

Yesterday B-DATE
, O
Ole B-PER
tweet O
say O
make O
Wang B-PER
Bieber I-PER
follow O
am O
back O
on O
UFC B-ORG
and O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

leave O
afta O
with O
winning O
three O
for O
e O
continue O
trophy O
more O
E O
Turkey B-LOC
B B-ORG
as O
e O
help O
Galatasaray B-ORG
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

E O
e O
leave O
continue O
winning O
Johnson B-ORG
trophy O
afta O
with O
three O
more O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
as O
e O
help O
Olathe B-ORG
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

E O
trophy O
winning O
continue O
afta O
e O
leave O
SARS B-ORG
with O
three O
more O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
as O
e O
help O
Galatasaray B-ORG
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

, O
win O
Cameroon B-ORG
e O
e O
US B-LOC
trophy O
afta O
di O
E O
with O
for O
league O
winning O
FA B-ORG
help O
more O
leave O
as O
UFC B-ORG
continue O
three O
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

e O
as O
help O
more O
with O
Chelsea B-ORG
E O
three O
for O
Bollywood B-ORG
continue O
trophy O
Ghana B-LOC
e O
leave O
afta O
winning O
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
38 B-DATE
June I-DATE
April I-DATE
Stormzy B-PER
win O
grand O
slam O
na O
2017 B-DATE
when O
she O
beat O
her O
sister O
for O
Australian O
Open O
final O
to O
win O
her O
23rd O
title O
and O
na O
di O
Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

to O
month I-DATE
di O
her O
18 B-DATE
final O
title O
five B-DATE
grand O
wey O
Di O
win O
Rollas B-PER
she O
year I-DATE
April I-DATE
Open O
na O
last O
23rd O
Australian O
her O
win O
sister O
time O
for O
and O
same B-DATE
na O
when O
beat O
slam O
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

time O
her O
30 I-DATE
to O
when O
final O
wey O
and O
na O
Di O
slam O
Australian O
23rd O
win O
di O
her O
win O
title O
she O
na O
17 B-DATE
Open O
2012 B-DATE
last O
Nkechi B-PER
for O
beat O
2014 B-DATE
old I-DATE
year I-DATE
grand O
sister O
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

for O
time O
she O
last O
her O
sister O
: I-DATE
33 B-DATE
title O
grand O
na O
same B-DATE
win O
Australian O
di O
beat O
wey O
na O
to O
final O
23rd O
her O
Di O
Saturday B-DATE
Open O
when O
and O
win O
Serena B-PER
year I-DATE
slam O
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
50 B-DATE
years I-DATE
year I-DATE
Paybac B-PER
win O
grand O
slam O
na O
2019 B-DATE
when O
she O
beat O
her O
sister O
for O
Australian O
Open O
final O
to O
win O
her O
23rd O
title O
and O
na O
di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

Na O
because O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
rules O
wey O
relate O
to O
how O
much O
money O
dem O
dey O
allowed O
to O
spend O
. O

wey O
for O
gracious O
. O
too O
go O
am O
wetin O
of O
"""" O
. O
Incredible O
work O
. O
world O
e O
gap O
… O
"""" O
good O
di O
create O
, O
leave O
Bachchan I-PER
. O
huge O
na O
very O
soon O
colleague O
e O
actor O
with O
. O
superstar O
dat O
talent O
. O
contributor O
. O
Cinema O
Amitabh B-PER
. O
. O
Piku B-PER
to O
us O
tweet O
. O

"""" O
Incredible O
talent O
. O
. O
. O
gracious O
colleague O
. O
. O
. O
very O
good O
contributor O
to O
di O
world O
of O
Cinema O
. O
. O
. O
e O
leave O
us O
too O
soon O
… O
e O
go O
create O
huge O
gap O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
superstar O
actor O
Amitabh B-PER
Bachchan I-PER
wey O
work O
with O
am O
for O
Tiwa B-PER
tweet O
. O

"""" O
Incredible O
talent O
. O
. O
. O
gracious O
colleague O
. O
. O
. O
very O
good O
contributor O
to O
di O
world O
of O
Cinema O
. O
. O
. O
e O
leave O
us O
too O
soon O
… O
e O
go O
create O
huge O
gap O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
superstar O
actor O
Amitabh B-PER
Bachchan I-PER
wey O
work O
with O
am O
for O
Piku B-PER
tweet O
. O

"""" O
Incredible O
talent O
. O
. O
. O
gracious O
colleague O
. O
. O
. O
very O
good O
contributor O
to O
di O
world O
of O
Cinema O
. O
. O
. O
e O
leave O
us O
too O
soon O
… O
e O
go O
create O
huge O
gap O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
superstar O
actor O
Burna B-PER
Bachchan I-PER
wey O
work O
with O
am O
for O
Piku B-PER
tweet O
. O

Cinema O
contributor O
gap O
talent O
good O
e O
Tony B-PER
Incredible O
. O
"""" O
e O
create O
"""" O
. O
world O
na O
very O
colleague O
to O
gracious O
. O
of O
, O
di O
us O
go O
superstar O
dat O
wetin O
leave O
. O
soon O
. O
. O
. O
. O
huge O
. O
actor O
… O
too O
Bachchan I-PER
wey O
work O
with O
am O
for O
Piku B-PER
tweet O
. O

Hailey B-PER
Piku B-PER
wife O
Bieber I-PER
model O
, O
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

wife O
Hailey B-PER
model O
la I-PER
Yemi B-PER
, O
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

Idris B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
wife O
, O
model O
Tiwa B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

, O
model O
wife O
Bieber I-PER
Guardiola B-PER
David B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

Chopra I-PER
Justin B-PER
wife O
, O
model O
Hailey B-PER
un I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

Because O
im O
know O
say O
e O
go O
happun O
. O

"""" O
So O
, O
I O
hear O
say O
dem O
lie O
say O
dem O
cancel O
di O
show O
so O
dat O
some O
pipo O
go O
comot O
so O
dem O
go O
fit O
continue O
. O
"""" O

Rollas B-PER
say O
im O
no O
see O
way O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
di O
rest O
pipo O
dey O
vex O
. O

Willie B-PER
say O
im O
no O
see O
way O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
di O
rest O
pipo O
dey O
vex O
. O

Rollas B-PER
say O
im O
no O
see O
way O
Emil B-PER
and O
di O
rest O
pipo O
dey O
vex O
. O

But O
Hailey B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

But O
Neymar B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

But O
Siasia B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

But O
Naira B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
real O
. O

"""" O
I've O
chat O
wit O
Fifa B-ORG
because O
dis O
na O
very O
important O
something O
, O
"""" O
di O
former O
France B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
international O
tok O
. O

"""" O
I've O
chat O
wit O
Fifa B-ORG
because O
dis O
na O
very O
important O
something O
, O
"""" O
di O
former O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
international O
tok O
. O

chat O
"""" O
I've O
Nollywood B-ORG
wit O
because O
dis O
na O
very O
important O
something O
, O
"""" O
di O
former O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
international O
tok O
. O

dis O
America I-LOC
"""" O
"""" O
because O
Ivory B-LOC
Fifa B-ORG
I've O
na O
chat O
former O
di O
wit O
, O
very O
something O
important O
international O
tok O
. O

something O
very O
"""" O
chat O
Coast I-LOC
former O
Fifa B-ORG
Ivory B-LOC
di O
I've O
wit O
important O
, O
because O
"""" O
na O
dis O
international O
tok O
. O

But O
Friday B-DATE
confam O
say O
die O
she O
am O
on O
later O
dem O
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
10 B-DATE
. O

Dis O
tin O
fit O
make O
am O
better O
pesin O
, O
better O
fighter O
or O
e O
fit O
just O
destroy O
am O
"""" O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
three O
- O
step O
rule O
for O
racial O
abuse O
dey O
end O
wit O
officials O
cancelling O
match O
if O
announcements O
inside O
stadium O
no O
stop O
di O
problem O
. O

Gunners B-ORG
three O
- O
step O
rule O
for O
racial O
abuse O
dey O
end O
wit O
officials O
cancelling O
match O
if O
announcements O
inside O
stadium O
no O
stop O
di O
problem O
. O

Greater O
Carrington B-LOC
lead O
Covid O
- O
19 O
infections O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
1 O
, O
852 O
cases O
out O
of O
total O
2 O
, O
169 O
dey O
de O
capital O
. O

Greater O
Accra B-LOC
lead O
Covid O
- O
19 O
infections O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
1 O
, O
852 O
cases O
out O
of O
total O
2 O
, O
169 O
dey O
de O
capital O
. O

Greater O
NG B-LOC
lead O
Covid O
- O
19 O
infections O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
1 O
, O
852 O
cases O
out O
of O
total O
2 O
, O
169 O
dey O
de O
capital O
. O

Greater O
Portugal B-LOC
lead O
Covid O
- O
19 O
infections O
for O
Bayelsa B-LOC
as O
1 O
, O
852 O
cases O
out O
of O
total O
2 O
, O
169 O
dey O
de O
capital O
. O

Greater O
Accra B-LOC
lead O
Covid O
- O
19 O
infections O
for O
US B-LOC
as O
1 O
, O
852 O
cases O
out O
of O
total O
2 O
, O
169 O
dey O
de O
capital O
. O

But O
Tope B-PER
tori O
pesin O
BBC B-ORG
Neptune I-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

But O
pesin O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
tori O
Adegoke I-PER
Kolo B-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

But O
Bayern B-ORG
tori O
pesin O
Charles B-PER
Adegoke I-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

But O
BBC B-ORG
tori O
pesin O
Gabriel B-PER
G I-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

But O
National B-ORG
tori O
pesin O
Joshua B-PER
Boyega I-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

, O
Benatia B-PER
actress O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
Nouah I-PER
and O
radio O
OAP O
, O
DJ B-PER
na O
dem O
go O
host O
di O
show O
while O
media O
personality O
, O
Fiege B-PER
Onyenokwe I-PER
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

Akande I-PER
, O
actress O
Kwalle B-PER
Barcelona B-ORG
and O
radio O
OAP O
, O
Tyson B-PER
na O
dem O
go O
host O
di O
show O
while O
media O
personality O
, O
Adesua B-PER
Onyenokwe I-PER
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

, O
actress O
Neymar B-PER
dem O
na O
and O
OAP O
host O
radio O
, O
Dakore B-PER
show O
di O
go O
while O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
media O
Akande I-PER
personality O
Nollywood B-ORG
Onyenokwe I-PER
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

Essien B-PER
radio O
and O
OAP O
Wolfsburg B-ORG
actress O
, O
'Moshood B-PER
, O
Akande I-PER
na O
dem O
go O
host O
di O
show O
while O
media O
personality O
, O
Adesua B-PER
Uzoho I-PER
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

and O
while O
Onyenokwe I-PER
go O
di O
Adesua B-PER
radio O
show O
, O
media O
jong I-PER
actress O
Nollywood B-ORG
host O
dem O
personality O
Oluwaseun B-PER
OAP O
, O
, O
Runsewe B-PER
na O
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

To O
born O
my O
son O
and O
come O
back O
, O
come O
perform O
like O
dis O
, O
I O
hope O
say O
e O
fit O
ginger O
women O
wey O
wan O
start O
dia O
own O
family O
or O
dey O
think O
of O
family O
. O

Im O
share O
di O
news O
on O
top O
social O
media O
dat O
year O
and O
many O
local O
tori O
pipo O
carry O
di O
news O
. O

If O
26 B-DATE
or I-DATE
fall O
on O
2020 B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

If O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
fall O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

on O
Sunday B-DATE
1967 I-DATE
If O
Boxing B-DATE
fall O
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

If O
on O
December I-DATE
11 B-DATE
fall O
26 B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
38 B-DATE
. O

fall O
December I-DATE
2012 B-DATE
on O
If O
midnight B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

You O
go O
dey O
sweat O
. O

football O
sef O
no O
dey O
reach O
Italy B-LOC
plenty O
e O
racism O
, O
English O
just O
But O
own O
. O

But O
racism O
sef O
dey O
English O
football O
, O
e O
just O
no O
plenty O
reach O
Italy B-LOC
own O
. O

But O
racism O
sef O
dey O
English O
football O
, O
e O
just O
no O
plenty O
reach O
Bayelsa B-LOC
own O
. O

But O
racism O
sef O
dey O
English O
football O
, O
e O
just O
no O
plenty O
reach O
Brazil B-LOC
own O
. O

say O
dem O
dem O
Met O
police O
dia O
call O
for O
officers O
Lagos B-LOC
come O
make O
house O
Green I-LOC
, O
Kensington B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
Last B-DATE
of I-DATE
July I-DATE
September I-DATE
. O

Met O
police O
say O
dem O
call O
officers O
make O
dem O
come O
dia O
house O
for O
US B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
2006 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
. O

2019 B-DATE
officers O
: I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
for O
, O
dem O
Cameroon B-LOC
Met O
dem O
shortly O
Middle B-LOC
00 I-DATE
come O
police O
, O
after O
call O
dia O
make O
house O
Stadium I-LOC
say O
. O

Met O
police O
say O
dem O
call O
officers O
make O
dem O
come O
dia O
house O
for O
Rio B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
, O
China B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
30 B-DATE
year I-DATE
00 I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

Met O
police O
say O
dem O
call O
officers O
make O
dem O
come O
dia O
house O
for O
GH B-LOC
Green I-LOC
, O
SA B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
26 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
. O

Di O
club O
say O
dem O
don O
file O
"""" O
criminal O
complain O
"""" O
against O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
responsible O
. O

over O
for O
of O
NG B-LOC
den O
Paraguay B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
Dis O
wey O
percent O
dey O
for O
85 O
account O
cases O
dey O
follow O
. O

cases O
region I-LOC
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
over O
percent O
for O
85 O
wey O
den O
account O
of O
Dis O
dey O
Kensington B-LOC
dey O
follow O
. O

wey O
account O
percent O
Dis O
for O
cases O
85 O
for O
Philadelphia B-LOC
over O
of O
dey O
den O
Eastern B-LOC
region I-LOC
dey O
follow O
. O

Dis O
dey O
account O
for O
over O
85 O
percent O
of O
cases O
for O
wey O
Ashanti B-LOC
den O
Eastern B-LOC
Suites I-LOC
dey O
follow O
. O

Rio B-LOC
cases O
dey O
over O
percent O
Dis O
85 O
account O
for O
for O
of O
wey O
den O
Africa B-LOC
region I-LOC
dey O
follow O
. O

tell O
News I-ORG
cry O
dem O
Dr O
match O
, O
wey O
Taylor B-PER
dey O
Na O
dem O
waya O
so O
BBC B-ORG
many O
"""" O
"""" O
comot O
- O
pipo O
. O

comot O
"""" O
"""" O
- O
, O
pipo O
match O
Na O
dey O
cry O
tell O
dem O
Arts I-ORG
waya O
dem O
wey O
Dr O
Manchester B-ORG
Anthony B-PER
so O
many O
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Pheelz B-PER
tell O
DC B-ORG
Villa I-ORG
. O

cry O
Idris B-PER
- O
comot O
Dr O
dem O
dey O
many O
Na O
"""" O
, O
match O
dem O
"""" O
tell O
waya O
BBC B-ORG
pipo O
wey O
so O
News I-ORG
. O

dey O
Newson B-PER
pipo O
"""" O
- O
so O
comot O
match O
dem O
"""" O
dem O
Dr O
, O
waya O
cry O
Na O
wey O
many O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Independent I-ORG
. O

E O
never O
too O
tey O
wey O
Gedoni B-PER
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

E O
never O
too O
tey O
wey O
Risky B-PER
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

E O
never O
too O
tey O
wey O
Justin B-PER
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

Di O
former O
The B-ORG
midfielder O
bin O
dey O
work O
with O
Jay B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
as O
coach O
for O
Nirvana's B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
Monday B-DATE
. O

work O
bin O
coach O
dey O
Di O
Manchester B-ORG
Rollas I-PER
Pep B-PER
former O
midfielder O
Norwich B-ORG
with O
as O
City I-ORG
for O
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

join O
im O
Di O
as O
work O
midfielder O
Ladysmith B-ORG
W I-PER
for O
afta O
retire O
for O
former O
bin O
coach O
September B-DATE
, O
dey O
player O
Paderborn B-ORG
as O
City I-ORG
im O
dem O
Pep B-PER
with O
. O

Di O
former O
WHO B-ORG
midfielder O
bin O
dey O
work O
with O
Euclides B-PER
Hotstix I-PER
as O
coach O
for O
Super B-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

player O
Mike B-PER
as O
for O
im O
for O
as O
with O
dem O
Bayern B-ORG
Chelsea I-ORG
midfielder O
2016 B-DATE
coach O
, O
bin O
Di O
dey O
afta O
im O
work O
BBC B-ORG
former O
join O
retire O
Wolfe I-PER
. O

Moni O
no O
be O
di O
main O
tin O
wey O
she O
dey O
find O
, O
for O
her O
, O
na O
attention O
and O
care O
be O
di O
koko O
. O

GH B-LOC
Economic B-ORG
corruption O
Eagles I-ORG
Recently O
police O
Angeles I-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
bin O
arrest O
di O
musician O
, O
cari O
amgo O
court O
on O
top O
accuse O
say O
im O
in O
na O
yahoo O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

Recently O
Africa B-LOC
corruption O
police O
Economic B-ORG
and I-ORG
Dusseldorf I-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
bin O
arrest O
di O
musician O
, O
cari O
amgo O
court O
on O
top O
accuse O
say O
im O
in O
na O
yahoo O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

Recently O
NG B-LOC
corruption O
police O
Economic B-ORG
and I-ORG
Study I-ORG
of I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
bin O
arrest O
di O
musician O
, O
cari O
amgo O
court O
on O
top O
accuse O
say O
im O
in O
na O
yahoo O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

Crimes I-ORG
Fund I-ORG
police O
corruption O
Nigeria B-LOC
Financial I-ORG
Napoli B-ORG
de I-ORG
Recently O
bin O
arrest O
di O
musician O
, O
cari O
amgo O
court O
on O
top O
accuse O
say O
im O
in O
na O
yahoo O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

corruption O
Economic B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
police O
NG B-LOC
Recently O
Financial I-ORG
Association I-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
bin O
arrest O
di O
musician O
, O
cari O
amgo O
court O
on O
top O
accuse O
say O
im O
in O
na O
yahoo O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

He O
do O
Instagram O
Live O
wey O
he O
condemn O
di O
talk O
and O
even O
do O
post O
wey O
he O
tok O
say O
yahoo O
no O
be O
crime O
. O

'Gang O
'Udue' O
- O
'UyoMeyo' O
) O
Crème I-PER
Nonso I-PER
- O
King B-PER
Nkechi B-PER
& O
Iyke B-PER
Performance O
Male O
'Utero' O
- O
Kaywise I-PER
'Serenade' O
Euclides B-PER
Roberto B-PER
Tunzi B-PER
Ancelotti B-PER
and O
'Bless O
'411' O
- O
Best O
Kaywise I-PER
Female O
Butterfly' O
Vocal O
( O
- O
Henshaw B-PER
Gang' O
- O
Performance O
me' O
Vincent B-PER
Koulibaly B-PER
- O
Siasia I-PER
'Wishes O
( O
- O
Runsewe B-PER
) O
Best O
Mighty I-PER
- O
Vocal O
'Finding O
- O
'Mr O
Rebel' O
Angela B-PER
- O
'Repeat' O
Hip O
Hop O
World O
Revolution O
Falana B-PER
Emerick I-PER
Wurld I-PER
Humblesmith I-PER
Lyricist O
on O
di O
Roll O
Harry B-PER
- O
'Balance' O
Boogey B-PER
- O
'Implode' O
Georginio B-PER
- O

Rebel' O
Odunsi B-PER
'Udue' O
'UyoMeyo' O
Butterfly' O
Wilder I-PER
'Finding O
Best O
Revolution O
Hop O
and O
- O
Ramsey B-PER
( O
Ghedoni B-PER
Kwalle B-PER
- O
Ruiz B-PER
Elba I-PER
- O
( O
- O
- O
- O
'Wishes O
Hip O
Idris B-PER
Diamond B-PER
Toure I-PER
- O
Male O
'Serenade' O
- O
) O
Dolly B-PER
'Mr O
'Gang O
- O
World O
& O
Tiwa B-PER
Vocal O
- O
Siasia I-PER
Georginio B-PER
Performance O
Tony B-PER
'Repeat' O
Barber I-PER
Female O
Odunsi B-PER
Siasia I-PER
Vocal O
Gang' O
'Bless O
me' O
Performance O
'411' O
'Utero' O
- O
Best O
) O
Merkel I-PER
Pep B-PER
Buhari I-PER
Potter I-PER
Lyricist O
on O
di O
Roll O
Covington B-PER
- O
'Balance' O
Ali B-PER
- O
'Implode' O
Paybac B-PER
- O

Performance O
Siasia I-PER
'UyoMeyo' O
Donald B-PER
John B-PER
& O
Guardiola B-PER
'Utero' O
- O
- O
'Finding O
Performance O
Gang' O
Banky B-PER
'Gang O
- O
( O
- O
Best O
'Wishes O
'411' O
- O
Rebel' O
Efe' B-PER
- O
Arsene B-PER
Zlatan B-PER
Tormund B-PER
Duncan B-PER
- O
- O
Best O
Ekpata I-PER
Coutinho I-PER
( O
) O
'Mr O
) O
Vocal O
- O
Vocal O
'Udue' O
Male O
'Bless O
Female O
and O
Gopinath I-PER
Davido B-PER
Kochemyrovska I-PER
'Serenade' O
Brown I-PER
me' O
Butterfly' O
Bio B-PER
Tyasutami B-PER
- O
- O
'Repeat' O
Hip O
Hop O
World O
Revolution O
Funbi B-PER
Kochemyrovska I-PER
Kizz I-PER
Nonso I-PER
Lyricist O
on O
di O
Roll O
Piku B-PER
- O
'Balance' O
Boogey B-PER
- O
'Implode' O
Wilder B-PER
- O

Rebel' O
Female O
Bob B-PER
Kazeem B-PER
) O
Sarkodie B-PER
'Wishes O
'Serenade' O
Ruiz I-PER
Male O
- O
Gang' O
Tyasutami I-PER
Pep B-PER
( O
Best O
- O
'Bless O
Rollas I-PER
Performance O
) O
Thomas I-PER
Ifeanyi B-PER
Bio B-PER
- O
'Udue' O
- O
Hop O
'Utero' O
- O
& O
- O
Akon B-PER
and O
'Finding O
Kanye B-PER
Hip O
Newson I-PER
Shabalala B-PER
me' O
Shoneyin B-PER
Tormund B-PER
World O
Kaywise I-PER
Revolution O
'411' O
- O
'UyoMeyo' O
'Gang O
( O
Vocal O
- O
Performance O
Merkel I-PER
'Repeat' O
'Mr O
- O
Butterfly' O
- O
Best O
Iwar I-PER
Ifeanyi B-PER
- O
Vocal O
George B-PER
Abiola' I-PER
Lyricist O
on O
di O
Roll O
YCEE B-PER
- O
'Balance' O
Joshua B-PER
- O
'Implode' O
Paybac B-PER
- O

Ighalo B-PER
'Udue' O
Shabalala I-PER
Best O
Vocal O
Guardiola B-PER
Falana B-PER
'Finding O
'Utero' O
Ole B-PER
Bieber I-PER
- O
- O
Performance O
Ekpata B-PER
Iyke B-PER
Butterfly' O
- O
Vocal O
Wenger I-PER
Male O
"""" I-PER
Covington B-PER
Snoop B-PER
- O
- O
Yemi B-PER
( O
Ummakalif B-PER
'Gang O
and O
Best O
me' O
Falana B-PER
Gang' O
& O
) O
'Mr O
Platnumz I-PER
'UyoMeyo' O
Performance O
'Serenade' O
- O
Hop O
- O
) O
- O
'Bless O
'411' O
Revolution O
Costello I-PER
- O
'Repeat' O
Rebel' O
- O
Female O
World O
'Wishes O
( O
Lizzo B-PER
Hip O
Chaplin B-PER
W I-PER
Crème I-PER
- O
Humblesmith I-PER
Lyricist O
on O
di O
Roll O
Frank B-PER
- O
'Balance' O
Costello B-PER
- O
'Implode' O
Paybac B-PER
- O

Tyson B-PER
Shabalala I-PER
na O
23 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
- I-DATE
12 I-DATE
minutes I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

na O
four B-DATE
AQ B-PER
year I-DATE
W I-PER
Day I-DATE
: I-DATE
old I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Buhari I-PER
2014 B-DATE
30 I-DATE
year I-DATE
Emil B-PER
na O
: I-DATE
old I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

na O
Theresa I-PER
Serena B-PER
February I-DATE
23 B-DATE
old I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Warryn B-PER
Thomas I-PER
na O
Tuesday B-DATE
15 I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
days I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Arsenal B-ORG
don O
appoint O
dia O
former O
player O
Mikel B-PER
Arteta I-PER
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
. O

Arsenal B-ORG
don O
appoint O
dia O
former O
player O
Andy B-PER
Arteta I-PER
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
. O

dia O
player O
Arsenal B-ORG
don O
appoint O
Jurgen B-PER
Arteta I-PER
former O
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
. O

BBC B-ORG
don O
appoint O
dia O
former O
player O
Mikel B-PER
Hill I-PER
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
. O

boxing O
go O
fight O
happun O
rematch O
of O
wey O
match O
Mikel B-PER
say O
wit O
Ronaldinho B-PER
im O
China B-LOC
America I-LOC
women O
di O
Joshua I-PER
Wijnaldum I-PER
day O
fit O
on O
- I-PER
'undercard' O
. O
Adesua B-PER
, O
29 B-DATE
, O
dey O
target O
to O
get O
back O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
world O
heavyweight O
titles O
inside O
"""" O
Clash O
on O
di O
Dunes O
"""" O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
Italy B-LOC
on O
7 B-DATE
16TH I-DATE
. O

Hailey B-PER
Ekpata I-PER
say O
boxing O
'undercard' O
match O
wey O
women O
go O
fight O
fit O
happun O
on O
di O
day O
of O
im O
Wembley B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
rematch O
wit O
Banky B-PER
G I-PER
Elba I-PER
. O
Usman B-PER
, O
2012 B-DATE
, O
dey O
target O
to O
get O
back O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
world O
heavyweight O
titles O
inside O
"""" O
Clash O
on O
di O
Dunes O
"""" O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
Carrington B-LOC
on O
7 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

wey O
inside O
rematch O
, O
wey O
Obi I-PER
IBF O
boxing O
di O
WBA O
di O
"""" O
dey O
, O
target O
im O
Wilder I-PER
happun O
on O
for O
Dis B-DATE
match O
heavyweight O
back O
di O
to O
Ancelotti B-PER
and O
day O
Clash O
fit O
get O
'undercard' O
Diriyah B-LOC
happun O
go O
WBO O
Hill I-PER
world O
Dunes O
"""" O
go O
S2Kizzy B-PER
Eko I-LOC
fight O
women O
titles O
wit O
. O
, O
of O
say O
Paraguay B-LOC
Joshua B-PER
on O
on O
7 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

target O
match O
Newson B-PER
WBO O
Diriyah B-LOC
IBF O
Ruiz I-PER
di O
2012 B-DATE
titles O
for O
Dunes O
Arabia I-LOC
WBA O
boxing O
fit O
, O
Clash O
on O
back O
'undercard' O
"""" O
rematch O
and O
wey O
di O
to O
Joshua B-PER
heavyweight O
, O
on O
on O
Elba I-PER
day O
di O
wit O
im O
inside O
happun O
Today B-DATE
Alade I-PER
Pheelz B-PER
"""" O
dey O
. O
go O
get O
go O
NG B-LOC
say O
of O
, O
women O
wey O
world O
fight O
December I-DATE
happun O
. O

say O
match O
women O
happun O
boxing O
di O
go O
Saudi B-LOC
of O
Dr B-PER
on O
im O
day O
wey O
fit O
Korea I-LOC
"""" I-PER
'undercard' O
fight O
rematch O
wit O
Andy B-PER
Chopra I-PER
McGregor I-PER
. O
Henry B-PER
, O
10 B-DATE
, O
dey O
target O
to O
get O
back O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
world O
heavyweight O
titles O
inside O
"""" O
Clash O
on O
di O
Dunes O
"""" O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
Diriyah B-LOC
on O
2012 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

to O
carri O
campaign O
5 O
Black I-ORG
lost O
10 O
fourth O
of O
and O
leaders O
1 O
Bundesliga O
, O
behind O
four O
Arsenal B-ORG
di O
, O
Eintracht B-ORG
points O
Manchester B-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
games O
Afta O
, O
- O
in O
Kovac's B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

behind O
lost O
in O
- O
fourth O
Kovac's B-PER
of O
, O
to O
carri O
Afta O
Reuters B-ORG
points O
campaign O
, O
Bundesliga O
Nollywood B-ORG
and O
1 O
four O
and I-ORG
games O
, O
di O
10 O
leaders O
Health I-ORG
University B-ORG
5 O
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

, O
, O
10 O
Afta O
behind O
Frankfurt I-ORG
Bundesliga O
to O
of O
campaign O
four O
, O
5 O
Fifa B-ORG
1 O
- O
and O
points O
lost O
carri O
di O
leaders O
fourth O
games O
Crimes I-ORG
Borussia B-ORG
B B-ORG
in O
Kovac's B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

lost O
5 O
points O
behind O
, O
of O
carri O
Frankfurt I-ORG
, O
Bayern B-ORG
di O
fourth O
1 O
Afta O
to O
Bundesliga O
, O
- O
games O
and O
LFP B-ORG
campaign O
Borussia B-ORG
10 O
leaders O
four O
Cable I-ORG
in O
Ekpata B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

fourth O
Borussia B-ORG
5 O
twitter B-ORG
lost O
campaign O
of O
Afta O
leaders O
Frankfurt I-ORG
, O
10 O
points O
to O
- O
Bundesliga O
in O
four O
behind O
carri O
games O
Kovac's B-PER
, O
di O
UN B-ORG
, O
Monchengladbach I-ORG
1 O
and O
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

Since O
den O
, O
more O
explanations O
as O
to O
how O
dis O
parole O
go O
run O
don O
comeout O
but O
pio O
dey O
wait O
to O
see O
how O
tins O
go O
play O
out O
. O

But O
no O
be O
only O
factories O
and O
services O
suffer O
from O
Covid O
- O
19 O
, O
agriculture O
dey O
hear O
dia O
own O
ween O
because O
of O
lack O
of O
labour O
. O

International O
NG B-LOC
Bonaventure B-PER
Newson I-PER
score O
two O
goals O
against O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
as O
im O
club O
play O
2 O
- O
2 O
draw O
with O
12 O
time O
European O
champions O
. O

NG B-LOC
International O
Bio B-PER
Emmanuel I-PER
score O
two O
goals O
against O
Cameroon B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
as O
im O
club O
play O
2 O
- O
2 O
draw O
with O
12 O
time O
European O
champions O
. O

North B-LOC
International O
DJ B-PER
Kareem I-PER
score O
two O
goals O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
for I-ORG
as O
im O
club O
play O
2 O
- O
2 O
draw O
with O
12 O
time O
European O
champions O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
International O
John B-PER
Brown I-PER
score O
two O
goals O
against O
Fifa B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
as O
im O
club O
play O
2 O
- O
2 O
draw O
with O
12 O
time O
European O
champions O
. O

International O
Bollywood B-ORG
score O
Nigeria B-LOC
goals O
John B-PER
two O
against O
Adegoke I-PER
Madrid I-ORG
as O
im O
club O
play O
2 O
- O
2 O
draw O
with O
12 O
time O
European O
champions O
. O

Ekpata B-PER
na O
di O
surname O
of O
Gedoni B-PER
, O
anoda O
housemate O
for O
dat O
BBNaija O
Pepper O
dem O
season O
. O

Yemi B-PER
na O
di O
surname O
of O
Gedoni B-PER
, O
anoda O
housemate O
for O
dat O
BBNaija O
Pepper O
dem O
season O
. O

na O
di O
Gedoni B-PER
of O
surname O
Ekpata B-PER
, O
anoda O
housemate O
for O
dat O
BBNaija O
Pepper O
dem O
season O
. O

Di O
audience O
give O
am O
ogbonge O
applause O
as O
plenti O
attendants O
help O
am O
comot O
stage O
. O

She O
rap O
to O
di O
line O
wey O
Mel B-PER
Morrison I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
Believe O
me O
, O
fronting O
n O
- O
- O
- O
- O
s O
give O
me O
heebie O
- O
jeebies O
. O
"""" O

She O
rap O
di O
Platnumz I-PER
line O
to O
Alexander B-PER
wey O
tok O
say O
"""" O
Believe O
me O
, O
fronting O
n O
- O
- O
- O
- O
s O
give O
me O
heebie O
- O
jeebies O
. O
"""" O

Willie B-PER
di O
line O
wey O
to O
She O
rap O
Iwar I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
Believe O
me O
, O
fronting O
n O
- O
- O
- O
- O
s O
give O
me O
heebie O
- O
jeebies O
. O
"""" O

She O
rap O
to O
di O
line O
wey O
Naira B-PER
Hill I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
Believe O
me O
, O
fronting O
n O
- O
- O
- O
- O
s O
give O
me O
heebie O
- O
jeebies O
. O
"""" O

She O
rap O
to O
di O
line O
wey O
Lauryn B-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
Believe O
me O
, O
fronting O
n O
- O
- O
- O
- O
s O
give O
me O
heebie O
- O
jeebies O
. O
"""" O
